{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jamaica Inn?", "answers": ["William Steig", "Daphne du Maurier", "Alvin Schwartz", "Richard Connell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kinky Boots?", "answers": ["Ayi Kwei Armah", "Peter Mayle", "Harvey Fierstein", "Carol Higgins Clark"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Canadian short story?", "answers": ["Christy Brown", "S. E. Hinton", "Patricia Cornwell", "Michelle Gadpaille"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Great Expectations?", "answers": ["Lloyd C. Douglas", "Mark Z. Danielewski", "Charles Dickens", "Joseph Gibaldi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Village Blacksmith?", "answers": ["Henry Wadsworth Longfellow", "Sarat Chandra Chattopadhyay", "Christopher Brookmyre", "V\u0101tsy\u0101yana"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Day of the Triffids?", "answers": ["Stephen Molstad", "Bret Easton Ellis", "William S. Gray", "John Wyndham"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Diary of a worm?", "answers": ["Michael J. Losier", "Frederick Winslow Taylor", "John Knowles", "Doreen Cronin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Murder on the Orient Express?", "answers": ["John D. Voelker", "Robert Browning", "Rachel Carson", "Agatha Christie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Yertle the Turtle and Other Stories?", "answers": ["Gavin Maxwell", "Dr. Seuss", "Hal Moore", "Sara Corbett"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gospel of Mark?", "answers": ["James A. Michener", "Nicole Mones", "Edward Bond", "Mark the Evangelist"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hotel on the Corner of Bitter and Sweet?", "answers": ["Clive Barker", "Jamie Ford", "Jess Walter", "Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Name of the Wind?", "answers": ["Patrick Rothfuss", "Eleanor Coerr", "Lincoln Steffens", "Marianne Williamson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Genera Plantarum?", "answers": ["Paul Torday", "Herman J. Mankiewicz", "Carl Linnaeus", "Harvey Diamond"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Famished Road?", "answers": ["Noam Chomsky", "Ben Okri", "Stella Gibbons", "Rick Warren"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Generation X: Tales for an Accelerated Culture?", "answers": ["Douglas Coupland", "Elizabeth Jolley", "Jorge Luis Borges", "Margaret Peterson Haddix"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Strip Tease?", "answers": ["William R. Forstchen", "Carl Hiaasen", "Alan Moore", "Denise Mina"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peter and Wendy?", "answers": ["Brad Thor", "J. M. Barrie", "Franz Kafka", "Timothy Ferriss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The wire in the blood?", "answers": ["Val McDermid", "William Bradford", "Malorie Blackman", "Augusten Burroughs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Laughter The Best Medicine?", "answers": ["Beryl Markham", "Robert Holden", "Sara Pennypacker", "Compton Mackenzie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bridge to Terabithia?", "answers": ["Donna Diamond", "K\u00e1roly Pap", "Sylvia Nasar", "Bertrand Russell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bridge to Terabithia?", "answers": ["Fidel Castro", "Jean-Paul Sartre", "Katherine Paterson", "Elmore Leonard"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The tide of nationalism?", "answers": ["Elmore Leonard", "Harry Allard", "Jerry Spinelli", "Abba Eban"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?", "answers": ["J. K. Rowling", "Lisa Genova", "Nelson Mandela", "William Davis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Perfect Day for Bananafish?", "answers": ["J. D. Salinger", "Rebecca Skloot", "P\u0101\u1e47ini", "Jeremy Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Da Vinci Code?", "answers": ["Dan Brown", "Dean Hughes", "Jawanza Kunjufu", "Richard Adams"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Little Princess?", "answers": ["Debbie Macomber", "Lynne Reid Banks", "Bert V. Royal", "Frances Hodgson Burnett"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Cat in the Hat?", "answers": ["Kenneth Oppel", "Dr. Seuss", "Laurence Sterne", "Max Allan Collins"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peyton Place?", "answers": ["Norton Juster", "Grace Metalious", "Julie Brady", "Linda Sue Park"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ready Player One?", "answers": ["Ernest Cline", "Piper Kerman", "Julia Kristeva", "Kyle Onstott"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Day of the Jackal?", "answers": ["Dale Wasserman", "Fred Kaplan", "Sarat Chandra Chattopadhyay", "Frederick Forsyth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hudhud Hi Aliguyon?", "answers": ["Gertrude Chandler Warner", "Dan Brown", "Miguel \u00c1ngel Ruiz", "Amador Taguinod Daguio"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gospel of Luke?", "answers": ["Luke the Evangelist", "Jon Krakauer", "Jerry B. Jenkins", "Harry Allard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tax deductions for professionals?", "answers": ["Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn", "Joyce Lankester Brisley", "Lafcadio Hearn", "Stephen Fishman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Eragon?", "answers": ["Eric L. Haney", "Mark Helprin", "Alyson Noel", "Christopher Paolini"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Skellig?", "answers": ["David Soman", "Colin Wilson", "David Almond", "Diana Gabaldon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The World Is Flat?", "answers": ["Kate Cary", "Thomas L. Friedman", "Chris Gardner", "Bryce Courtenay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Revolutionary Road?", "answers": ["Christopher McDougall", "Ann Patchett", "Richard Yates", "Betty Friedan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dream a Little Dream of Me: The Life of Cass Elliot?", "answers": ["George Ade", "Shepherd Mead", "Eddi Fiegel", "Augustine of Hippo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Caillou at Grandma and Grandpa's?", "answers": ["Joceline Sanschagrin", "Rich Cohen", "Sloan Wilson", "M. Scott Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Robin Hood?", "answers": ["Brian Yorkey", "J. C. Holt", "Joe Klein", "Anthony Kiedis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The History of the Decline and Fall of the Roman Empire?", "answers": ["Adeline Yen Mah", "Edward Gibbon", "Mark the Evangelist", "Jim Gaffigan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Coma?", "answers": ["Herodotus", "Dave Thompson", "Elizabeth Jolley", "Robin Cook"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Salt?", "answers": ["Taslima Nasrin", "Mark Kurlansky", "Markus Zusak", "David McCullough"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Thousand Clowns?", "answers": ["Philip Pullman", "Paul Howard", "Herb Gardner", "Patricia Reilly Giff"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Crazy Love: Overwhelmed by a Relentless God?", "answers": ["Sogyal Rinpoche", "Washington Irving", "Miguel \u00c1ngel Ruiz", "Francis Chan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Crazy Love: Overwhelmed by a Relentless God?", "answers": ["Danae Yankoski", "Samuel Richardson", "Marianne Williamson", "Hal Moore"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Manifeste du Surr\u00e9alisme. Poisson soluble?", "answers": ["John-Michael Tebelak", "Elizabeth Strout", "Howard Lindsay", "Andr\u00e9 Breton"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Cask of Amontillado?", "answers": ["Christy Brown", "John Irving", "Edgar Allan Poe", "John Grogan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hit and Run?", "answers": ["Lurlene McDaniel", "Ira Wood", "Mickey Rapkin", "Rohinton Mistry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Elements of Style?", "answers": ["E. B. White", "Tom Perrotta", "George Samuel Clason", "Robert Boyle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Valley of the Dolls?", "answers": ["Jeff Probst", "Jacqueline Susann", "H. E. Bates", "Plato"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book M\u1e5bcchakatika?", "answers": ["Flora Thompson", "\u015a\u016bdraka", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco", "Joseph Bruchac"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Beach House?", "answers": ["John August", "Mary Alice Monroe", "Phillip Berman", "S. A. Bodeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Development as Freedom?", "answers": ["Beverly Lyon Clark", "Harriet Ann Jacobs", "Bill Gates", "Amartya Sen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The BFG?", "answers": ["Debbie Macomber", "Harold Pinter", "Jodi Picoult", "Roald Dahl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Troubled Sleep?", "answers": ["Tholkappiar", "Jean-Paul Sartre", "Yann Martel", "Ashley Gardner"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Prep?", "answers": ["James Stevens", "Henry James", "Niklaus Wirth", "Curtis Sittenfeld"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Noises Off?", "answers": ["Dorothy Allison", "Michael Frayn", "Richard Dawkins", "Kathryn Stockett"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cinder?", "answers": ["Marissa Meyer", "Charles Osborne", "Dan Poynter", "Robert Graves"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The three little pigs?", "answers": ["Lincoln Peirce", "Samantha Shannon", "Barry Moser", "Mark Z. Danielewski"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Caretaker?", "answers": ["Carol Sklenicka", "Harold Pinter", "Plato", "Gary Paulsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Barefoot in the Park?", "answers": ["Deborah Smith", "James Howe", "Neil Simon", "Edmond Rostand"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Age of Reason?", "answers": ["Thomas Paine", "Dick Roughsey", "Chris Van Allsburg", "Lincoln Child"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book American Idiot?", "answers": ["John Grogan", "Michael Mayer", "Javier Calvo", "Edward S. Herman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book American Idiot?", "answers": ["Jack London", "Billie Joe Armstrong", "Colette", "Elmore Leonard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Go Ask Alice?", "answers": ["Mikhail Lermontov", "Mark Bowden", "Dennis Lehane", "Beatrice Sparks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stone Soup?", "answers": ["Eric Van Lustbader", "Marcia Brown", "John Fowles", "Dick Roughsey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The C Programming Language?", "answers": ["Brian Kernighan", "Andrew Clements", "Daniel Goleman", "Sheila Lane"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The C Programming Language?", "answers": ["Jeremy Wilson", "Lisi Harrison", "Dennis Ritchie", "Andr\u00e9 Breton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blue Christmas CD?", "answers": ["Paul Torday", "John F. Kennedy", "Mary Kay Andrews", "Lloyd C. Douglas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Il Canzoniere?", "answers": ["Petrarch", "Jerome Lawrence", "Spencer Johnson", "Lauren Kate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Difference Engine?", "answers": ["William Gibson", "William Bradford", "Andrew Clements", "Jessie Redmon Fauset"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Difference Engine?", "answers": ["Mark Ribowsky", "Anita Shreve", "Craig Brown", "Bruce Sterling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fences?", "answers": ["Robert James Waller", "August Wilson", "Stan Redding", "Helen Hunt Jackson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Exorcist?", "answers": ["Jody Rosen", "Charles Perrault", "William Peter Blatty", "Rachel Carson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Flow?", "answers": ["Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi", "Michael Hollinger", "Frank Abagnale", "C. S. Lewis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Discovering Geometry?", "answers": ["Mazarine Pingeot", "Doreen Cronin", "Michael Serra", "Veronica Roth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sorcerer's Apprentice?", "answers": ["Marcia Brown", "Taslima Nasrin", "Devaki Nandan Khatri", "Johann Wolfgang von Goethe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Wolf of Wall Street?", "answers": ["Ben Mikaelsen", "William Henry Hudson", "Jordan Belfort", "Robert Newton Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo?", "answers": ["F. Scott Fitzgerald", "Stieg Larsson", "Rebecca Skloot", "Ira Wood"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Monarch of the Glen?", "answers": ["Compton Mackenzie", "Stephen Fishman", "Nick Stafford", "John Donne"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pilgrim's Progress?", "answers": ["Cassandra Golds", "Graham Greene", "John Bunyan", "Henri Charri\u00e8re"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Humanae Vitae?", "answers": ["Michael Hollinger", "Ernest Hemingway", "Pope Paul VI", "Jostein Gaarder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stranded?", "answers": ["Ishmael Beah", "Krishna Dharma", "Erich Maria Remarque", "Jeffrey Probst"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stranded?", "answers": ["Eva Ibbotson", "David Rabe", "Adam Johnson", "Chris Tebbetts"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stranded?", "answers": ["Robert Bloch", "Nancy Milford", "Caralyn Buehner", "Jeff Probst"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bone Season?", "answers": ["Debbie Macomber", "Gregory David Roberts", "Wendelin Van Draanen", "Samantha Shannon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Henry James: A Life?", "answers": ["Leon Edel", "Gary Ezzo", "Tim Tharp", "Irene Mecchi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Edward Scissorhands?", "answers": ["Tim Tharp", "James Clavell", "Matthew Bourne", "Robin Sharma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book HORROR STORIES: DAS BESTE VOM MEISTER DES UNHEIMLICHEN?", "answers": ["A. E. Cannon", "H. P. Lovecraft", "W. Bruce Cameron", "Marco Polo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pippi Longstocking?", "answers": ["Astrid Lindgren", "Richard Atwater", "Ferdowsi", "Sean Hannity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hoot?", "answers": ["John F. Kennedy", "Carl Hiaasen", "A. S. A. Harrison", "Anne Frank"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Vanity Fair?", "answers": ["William Makepeace Thackeray", "Glen Rounds", "Thomas Mann", "Guinness World Records"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bleak House?", "answers": ["James Stevens", "Lawrence Kasha", "Charles Dickens", "Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bell Curve?", "answers": ["Aldo Leopold", "Charles A. Murray", "Michael J. Mosley", "Confucius"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bell Curve?", "answers": ["Richard Herrnstein", "Edward Lear", "Harry Thompson", "Deborah Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Home Truths?", "answers": ["David Lodge", "Meredith Willson", "John Connolly", "Kevin Trudeau"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book If I Stay?", "answers": ["Thomas Harris", "Marco Polo", "Boris Pasternak", "Gayle Forman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Out of Africa?", "answers": ["Beverly Lewis", "Meredith Willson", "Karen Blixen", "Li Cunxin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Firefly Lane?", "answers": ["Robin Jones Gunn", "Kristin Hannah", "Elizabeth Gaskell", "Rick Riordan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Main Street?", "answers": ["Ben Carson", "Amos Oz", "Muhammad al-Bukhari", "Sinclair Lewis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blue Like Jazz?", "answers": ["Don Miller", "John Osborne", "Matthew Gregory Lewis", "John Caird"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Fable?", "answers": ["Marjorie Garber", "William Faulkner", "Alex Flinn", "Moli\u00e8re"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Madagascar: The Movie Storybook?", "answers": ["Eileen Christelow", "Bert V. Royal", "Christopher Collier", "Billy Frolick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book And did those feet in ancient time?", "answers": ["William Blake", "Philip Wylie", "Matthew Gregory Lewis", "Ben Carson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wit?", "answers": ["Ronald David Laing", "Margaret Edson", "Thucydides", "Malcolm Gladwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Seven Habits of Highly Effective People?", "answers": ["Joseph Gibaldi", "Boles\u0142aw Prus", "Jonathan Cahn", "Stephen Covey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book History of Rome?", "answers": ["Theodor Mommsen", "Michael Symon", "Baroness Emma Orczy", "Mario Vargas Llosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Number the Stars?", "answers": ["Harvey Diamond", "Zora Neale Hurston", "Nick Bentley", "Lois Lowry"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chandrakanta?", "answers": ["Cecil Frances Humphreys Alexander", "Devaki Nandan Khatri", "Ann Voskamp", "T. H. White"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Toward freedom?", "answers": ["Jawaharlal Nehru", "Samuel P. Huntington", "Michael Ende", "John Galsworthy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shiloh?", "answers": ["Thiruvalluvar", "Leslie Bricusse", "Michael Camille", "Phyllis Reynolds Naylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Casino Royale?", "answers": ["Henry David Thoreau", "Bede", "Ian Fleming", "Thomas Mann"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Autobiography of an Unknown Indian?", "answers": ["Nirad C. Chaudhuri", "Iris Johansen", "Gary Paulsen", "Jeffrey Eugenides"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beloved?", "answers": ["Toni Morrison", "T. S. Eliot", "George Dekker", "Raymond Briggs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Native Son?", "answers": ["Martin Seymour-Smith", "Jason Matthews", "Edgar Wallace", "Richard Wright"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Shame of the Cities?", "answers": ["Murasaki Shikibu", "Matt Baglio", "Lincoln Steffens", "Enid Bagnold"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Legally Blonde?", "answers": ["Nick Hornby", "Amanda Brown", "Janet Evanovich", "Friedrich Engels"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book No Country for Old Men?", "answers": ["Susan Cain", "Anne Frank", "Milton A. Rothman", "Cormac McCarthy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Spamalot?", "answers": ["David Wood", "Graham Greene", "Bill Gates", "Eric Idle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peter Taylor: A Writer's Life?", "answers": ["Daniel Woodrell", "Hubert Horton McAlexander", "Aristophanes", "Dean Koontz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lost World?", "answers": ["Lincoln Child", "Gordon Korman", "Charles Darwin", "Arthur Conan Doyle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Brave New World?", "answers": ["Chris Cleave", "A. C. H. Smith", "Aldous Huxley", "Jane Smiley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Breadwinner?", "answers": ["Deborah Ellis", "Roger O. Hirson", "Mario Batali", "Don Lynch"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Stand?", "answers": ["Katie Davis", "Manu (Lawgiver)", "Stephen King", "George Eliot"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Outsiders?", "answers": ["Todd Burpo", "Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg", "S. E. Hinton", "Barry Moser"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Devil Wears Prada?", "answers": ["Bill Yoast", "William James", "Floyd Mutrux", "Lauren Weisberger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sparrow?", "answers": ["Thomas More", "Mary Doria Russell", "Thomas Hardy", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hot Zone?", "answers": ["John Gunther", "Robin Jones Gunn", "Richard Preston", "Marilyn Diamond"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stoner?", "answers": ["Daniel Wallace", "Sarat Chandra Chattopadhyay", "John Edward Williams", "Kathryn Erskine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Asian drama; an inquiry into the poverty of nations?", "answers": ["Gunnar Myrdal", "Pete Dexter", "John Wyndham", "Jacqueline Winspear"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beautiful Creatures?", "answers": ["Andy McNab", "Erin Morgenstern", "Kami Garcia", "Wilbur A. Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beautiful Creatures?", "answers": ["Margaret Stohl", "Sophie Kinsella", "Susan Hill", "Albert Camus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Queen of the Damned?", "answers": ["Eleanor Estes", "Edward Bloor", "Catherine Clark", "Anne Rice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gorky Park?", "answers": ["Martin Cruz Smith", "Priscilla Cummings", "Barbara Park", "Eric Suben"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Good Man Is Hard To Find?", "answers": ["Flannery O'Connor", "Cornelius Ryan", "David Henry Hwang", "Helen Keller"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book American Satire?", "answers": ["Giles Andreae", "Steven D. Levitt", "John Reynolds Gardiner", "Nick Bakalar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Born To Run?", "answers": ["Henri Charri\u00e8re", "Nelson George", "Alice Raymon", "Christopher McDougall"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lamb to the Slaughter?", "answers": ["Tim Tharp", "Perseus Books Group", "Roald Dahl", "Willie Gilbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Michael Vey: The Prisoner of Cell 25?", "answers": ["Tony Kushner", "Helen Prejean", "Richard Paul Evans", "Robert Sobel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beautiful Ruins?", "answers": ["Neil Cross", "Whitney Stewart", "Haruki Murakami", "Jess Walter"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rhinoceros?", "answers": ["Darren Shan", "Arundhati Roy", "Marilyn Diamond", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book People of the Book?", "answers": ["Geraldine Brooks", "Alfred North Whitehead", "Fran\u00e7oise Sagan", "Barbara Kingsolver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Virgin Diet?", "answers": ["Alex Garland", "Jean M. Auel", "J. J. Virgin", "Fred Ebb"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A House Is Not a Home?", "answers": ["Erich Segal", "Polly Adler", "Koushun Takami", "Koushun Takami"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Othello?", "answers": ["Irving Shulman", "William Shakespeare", "Phoebe Atwood Taylor", "Bankim Chandra Chattopadhyay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bye Bye Birdie?", "answers": ["Michael Stewart", "Alex Haley", "Stephen Kendrick", "Brian Weiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peer Gynt?", "answers": ["Howard Fast", "Bob Woodward", "Henrik Ibsen", "Pamela Druckerman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Something borrowed?", "answers": ["Nicole Mones", "James Herriot", "Roger Zelazny", "Emily Giffin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sum of All Fears?", "answers": ["Linda Sue Park", "Sigmund Freud", "Henry James", "Tom Clancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How Much Land Does a Man Need??", "answers": ["Deirdre David", "Yasmina Khadra", "Mario Vargas Llosa", "Leo Tolstoy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Future Shock?", "answers": ["Mary Higgins Clark", "Leif Enger", "Alvin Toffler", "Peter Shaffer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Velveteen Rabbit?", "answers": ["David Treuer", "Susan Hill", "Guy de Maupassant", "Margery Williams"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Communist Manifesto?", "answers": ["Moli\u00e8re", "Eugene H. Peterson", "Jenny Downham", "Friedrich Engels"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Communist Manifesto?", "answers": ["David Mitchell", "Alice Sebold", "Cecily von Ziegesar", "Karl Marx"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Free Man of Color?", "answers": ["Edith Wharton", "John Guare", "Joanne Harris", "Christos Tsiolkas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book You Can't Go Home Again?", "answers": ["Thomas Wolfe", "T. S. Eliot", "Billie Joe Armstrong", "David Foster Wallace"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mourning Dove?", "answers": ["Neil Simon", "Fred Kaplan", "Mourning Dove", "Jeffery Deaver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Howl's Moving Castle?", "answers": ["Diana Wynne Jones", "Roger O. Hirson", "Shepherd Mead", "Ted Sorensen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Boys in the Boat: Nine Americans and Their Epic Quest for Gold at the 1936 Berlin Olympics?", "answers": ["Kimon Valaskakis", "Moli\u00e8re", "Hasan Azizul Huq", "Daniel James Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Boys in the Boat: Nine Americans and Their Epic Quest for Gold at the 1936 Berlin Olympics?", "answers": ["Daniel Brown", "T. Coraghessan Boyle", "Jamie Simons", "Lane Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Skinny Dip?", "answers": ["Mickey Rapkin", "Helaine Fendelman", "Carl Hiaasen", "Jon Ronson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Outer Banks Low Price?", "answers": ["Anne Rivers Siddons", "Arthur Miller", "Elizabeth Wurtzel", "Tom Jones"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Princess and the Pea?", "answers": ["Ron Hall", "Ernest Hemingway", "Janet Riehecky", "Helen Bannerman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Princess and the Pea?", "answers": ["Eduard Jose", "Dinabandhu Mitra", "Gary Jennings", "Sue Grafton"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Princess and the Pea?", "answers": ["Hans Christian Andersen", "Charles Darwin", "Ayi Kwei Armah", "Prosper M\u00e9rim\u00e9e"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hydraulic fracturing?", "answers": ["Thomas C. Holt", "Tara Meixsell", "Gene Stone", "Erich Segal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Clementine?", "answers": ["Sara Pennypacker", "Patrick Ness", "Amador Taguinod Daguio", "James Marshall"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Paul Bunyan?", "answers": ["Edwin Balmer", "Charles Reade", "James Stevens", "Irma S. Rombauer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Field of Blood?", "answers": ["Denise Mina", "Michael Morpurgo", "Thomas Seltzer", "Dale Carnegie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Magic Mountain?", "answers": ["Thomas Mann", "Joanna Cole", "Jennifer Worth", "Jane O'Connor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lost Horizon?", "answers": ["James Hilton", "Richard Paul Evans", "Arthur Ransome", "Else Holmelund Minarik"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The House of Mirth?", "answers": ["Edith Wharton", "John R. Erickson", "Thomas Hughes", "Raymond Queneau"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blind Faith?", "answers": ["Christopher Marlowe", "Jeannie Gunn", "Joe McGinniss", "David Auburn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book And the Truth Shall Set You Free?", "answers": ["Warren Casey", "David Icke", "Ernest Poole", "David Weber"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jack of Shadows?", "answers": ["Tyler Perry", "Roger Zelazny", "James Marshall", "Nick Hornby"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Something blue?", "answers": ["Samantha Shannon", "Rick Warren", "Emily Giffin", "Anita Loos"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Perks of Being a Wallflower?", "answers": ["Stephen Chbosky", "Bill Clinton", "Lorianne Siomades", "Jeff Probst"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wuthering Heights?", "answers": ["Emily Bront\u00eb", "Matt Lang", "Jeffery Deaver", "William Boyd"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book West with the Night?", "answers": ["Beryl Markham", "Ellen G. White", "Arthur Ashe", "Caitlin Moran"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Zombie Survival Guide?", "answers": ["Harry Turtledove", "Guru Nanak Dev", "Max Brooks", "Martin Dugard"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Art of War?", "answers": ["Sun Tzu", "Chris Kuzneski", "Judy Duarte", "Federico Garc\u00eda Lorca"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nil Darpan?", "answers": ["Dinabandhu Mitra", "Mikhail Lermontov", "Ayn Rand", "Sarah Gilbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Too Big to Fail?", "answers": ["Mark O'Donnell", "Elizabeth Wurtzel", "Harvey Fierstein", "Andrew Ross Sorkin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Life After Life?", "answers": ["Kate Atkinson", "Ira Levin", "Basil Copper", "Tyler Perry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Plains of Passage?", "answers": ["William Stobbs", "S. A. Bodeen", "Henri Charri\u00e8re", "Jean M. Auel"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Light Between Oceans?", "answers": ["M. L. Stedman", "Jane Austen", "Robert Penn Warren", "Mary Roach"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Earth in the Balance?", "answers": ["Al Gore", "John Osborne", "John Dempsey", "Amiri Baraka"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In Cold Blood?", "answers": ["Anthony Burgess", "Bankim Chandra Chattopadhyay", "Betsy Maestro", "Truman Capote"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Living On a Prayer?", "answers": ["Orson Scott Card", "Sheila Quigley", "Anna Quindlen", "Roger Sherman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chicka Chicka Boom Boom: Anniversary Edition?", "answers": ["John Archambault", "Gary Jennings", "Tom Jones", "George R. R. Martin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book De revolutionibus orbium coelestium?", "answers": ["Nicolaus Copernicus", "Mary Robinette Kowal", "Mark Twain", "Thomas Rockwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fences: Response Journal?", "answers": ["Pierre Boulle", "Margaret Elphinstone", "August Wilson", "Jeanne Wakatsuki Houston"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Guardian?", "answers": ["Kim Carpenter", "Lee Hall", "Nicholas Sparks", "John Gunther"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book And the Mountains Echoed?", "answers": ["Mario Puzo", "Khaled Hosseini", "Jeffrey Eugenides", "Alan Bennett"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Altar of Bones?", "answers": ["Munshi Premchand", "Laurie Halse Anderson", "Piers Anthony", "Penelope Williamson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Buddenbrooks?", "answers": ["Harper Lee", "Miguel de Cervantes", "Thomas Mann", "Angela Johnson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Wrinkle in Time?", "answers": ["Louis Fischer", "Helaine Fendelman", "Madeleine L'Engle", "E. M. Forster"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Forever...?", "answers": ["Henry James", "Plato", "Michael Ende", "Judy Blume"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tears of a Tiger?", "answers": ["Albert Facey", "Alan Davies", "Sharon Draper", "Watty Piper"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Roughing It?", "answers": ["Elie Wiesel", "Mark Twain", "Jahangir", "Langston Hughes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Clergyman's Daughter?", "answers": ["Ruth Stiles Gannett", "Thomas \u00e0 Kempis", "John Fowles", "George Orwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Vindication of the Rights of Woman: With Strictures on Political and Moral Subjects?", "answers": ["Mary Wollstonecraft", "William Faulkner", "Napoleon Hill", "Christopher Paul Curtis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bourne Legacy?", "answers": ["Thucydides", "Art Spiegelman", "William S. Burroughs", "Robert Ludlum"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bourne Legacy?", "answers": ["Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi", "Howard Pyle", "John Grogan", "Eric Van Lustbader"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Citadel?", "answers": ["Jennifer L. Holm", "A. J. Cronin", "Sara Gruen", "Elias Chacour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Minister's Black Veil?", "answers": ["Mary Wesley", "Roger Zelazny", "Chris Gardner", "Nathaniel Hawthorne"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Half a Life?", "answers": ["Russel Crouse", "Joseph Bruchac", "Betty Friedan", "V.S. Naipaul"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ring of bright water?", "answers": ["Susanna Kearsley", "Jean Webster", "Gavin Maxwell", "Floyd Mutrux"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Devdas?", "answers": ["Sarah Young", "Jacqueline Davies", "Peter Benchley", "Sarat Chandra Chattopadhyay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Eighteenth Century: Full Text Database: SGML Format?", "answers": ["Devaki Nandan Khatri", "James Boswell", "Edna Ferber", "Arthur Balfour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Eighteenth Century: Full Text Database: SGML Format?", "answers": ["Karl Marx", "Robert Ruark", "Tobias Smollett", "Stephanie Stuve-Bodeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Eighteenth Century: Full Text Database: SGML Format?", "answers": ["Thomas \u00e0 Kempis", "Caralyn Buehner", "Edward Young", "Thucydides"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Eighteenth Century: Full Text Database: SGML Format?", "answers": ["Wayne Short", "Henry James", "Edmond Halley", "Christina Hobbs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Eighteenth Century: Full Text Database: SGML Format?", "answers": ["Peter Mayle", "Rameck Hunt", "Samuel Richardson", "Michael Crichton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Eighteenth Century: Full Text Database: SGML Format?", "answers": ["Horace Walpole", "Marilyn Diamond", "Bede", "Pam Mu\u00f1oz Ryan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Eighteenth Century: Full Text Database: SGML Format?", "answers": ["Sir John Retcliffe", "Laurence Sterne", "Dean Koontz", "Helen Prejean"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cloud Cuckoo Land?", "answers": ["Guy Bolton", "Rick Elice", "Naomi Mitchison", "Eliyahu M. Goldratt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Room with a View?", "answers": ["E. M. Forster", "Jon Ronson", "Susan J Tolchin", "Louis L'Amour"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Alchemist - Gift Edition?", "answers": ["Eudora Welty", "Mourning Dove", "Lawrence Hill", "Paulo Coelho"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Seabiscuit: An American Legend?", "answers": ["Stella Gibbons", "Laura Hillenbrand", "John Keats", "W. Wilkins"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Three little pigs and the big bad wolf?", "answers": ["Paul Muldoon", "Anthony Powell", "John Milton", "Glen Rounds"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Black Betty: An Easy Rawlins Mystery?", "answers": ["Walter Mosley", "Harry Allard", "Quentin Tarantino", "Mridula Baljekar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nice Is Just a Place in France?", "answers": ["The Betches", "Narmad\u0101pras\u0101da Up\u0101dhy\u0101ya", "Michael Camille", "Harvey Fierstein"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Bend in the River?", "answers": ["V.S. Naipaul", "Robert Lopez", "Meredith Willson", "Ayn Rand"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book No Exit?", "answers": ["Enid Blyton", "Lawrence Kimbrough", "Jean-Paul Sartre", "William Saroyan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tangerine?", "answers": ["Ethan Hawke", "Noam Chomsky", "Edward Bloor", "Philip Caputo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Studies in Classic American Literature?", "answers": ["Joceline Sanschagrin", "Thornton Wilder", "D. H. Lawrence", "Alan Brennert"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book We of the Never Never?", "answers": ["Deja King", "Jeannie Gunn", "Michael Symon", "Theodore Taylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sharp Objects: A Novel?", "answers": ["Gillian Flynn", "Margaret Elphinstone", "Peter Shaffer", "George Dekker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jersey Boys?", "answers": ["Leslie Bricusse", "James Hilton", "Vincent Bugliosi", "Rick Elice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jersey Boys?", "answers": ["Gregory David Roberts", "Harvey Fierstein", "Margaret Mitchell", "Marshall Brickman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book An Autobiography?", "answers": ["Jawaharlal Nehru", "Jean-Dominique Bauby", "Amanda Lindhout", "Deja King"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The golden goose?", "answers": ["Sylvia Nasar", "Jim Bouton", "Caralyn Buehner", "Uri Shulevitz"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book War Horse?", "answers": ["Michael Morpurgo", "Gail Boushey", "Stacy Schiff", "Rachel Carson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Witch of Blackbird Pond?", "answers": ["Gerd Theissen", "Elizabeth George Speare", "Marcel Proust", "Ira Levin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book True Colors?", "answers": ["Tracey Garvis-Graves", "Ben Mezrich", "Kristin Hannah", "Kazuo Ishiguro"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Birds?", "answers": ["James Alexander Thom", "Daphne du Maurier", "William Bradford", "V.S. Naipaul"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Severed Head?", "answers": ["Iris Murdoch", "William S. Gray", "P. D. James", "Richard Stilgoe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My \u00c1ntonia?", "answers": ["Patrick Barlow", "Willa Cather", "Ben Mezrich", "Harriet Parker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Warm Bodies?", "answers": ["William Landay", "James Dashner", "Isaac Marion", "Mark Stewart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Spanish Tragedy?", "answers": ["Adolph Green", "Barbara Kingsolver", "Lincoln Peirce", "Thomas Kyd"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Robert B. Parker's Killing the Blues?", "answers": ["Arthur Golden", "Richard Bach", "Michael Brandman", "Richard O'Brien"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chicka Chicka Boom Boom?", "answers": ["Karen Traviss", "T. H. White", "Ted Hughes", "John Archambault"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book On Writing: A Memoir of the Craft?", "answers": ["Henri Charri\u00e8re", "Stephen King", "Niklaus Wirth", "Robert Munsch"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The principles and problems of federal finance?", "answers": ["Iris Chang", "Bhalchandra Pundlik Adarkar", "Stephen Fishman", "George Langelaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Devil in the White City?", "answers": ["Erik Larson", "Lisi Harrison", "Mario Vargas Llosa", "Laura Colker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lost Honour of Katharina Blum?", "answers": ["Rashid-al-Din Hamadani", "Christopher Marlowe", "Solomon Noethup", "Heinrich B\u00f6ll"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chitty-Chitty-Bang-Bang?", "answers": ["Robert Falls", "Betty Friedan", "William Ernest Henley", "Ian Fleming"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Animal Mind: A Text-book of Comparative Psychology?", "answers": ["Augustine of Hippo", "Ernest Poole", "James Weldon Johnson", "Margaret Floy Washburn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ice Station Zebra?", "answers": ["Alistair MacLean", "Frederic Loewe", "Mark Bowden", "Theodor Mommsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Taste of Honey?", "answers": ["Shelagh Delaney", "Gerome Ragni", "Ira Levin", "Robert Hillenbrand"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kama Sutra?", "answers": ["Helen Schucman", "Betty Comden", "V\u0101tsy\u0101yana", "Larry McMurtry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Someone like You?", "answers": ["Sarah Dessen", "Merriam-Webster", "Pam Mu\u00f1oz Ryan", "Frank Lauria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fiddler on the roof?", "answers": ["Jerry Bock", "Mary Kay Andrews", "Barry Moser", "Albert Camus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fiddler on the roof?", "answers": ["Joseph Stein", "Karen Traviss", "Sun Tzu", "Gaston Leroux"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In Her Shoes?", "answers": ["John Jakes", "Jennifer Weiner", "George Langelaan", "Ford Madox Ford"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book From Here to Eternity?", "answers": ["Anna Quindlen", "James Jones", "Lucy Maud Montgomery", "Bartolom\u00e9 de Las Casas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Experiencing God: Youth Leader Guide?", "answers": ["Rajendra Prasad", "Sophocles", "Henry Blackaby", "Pseudonymous Bosch"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bridge?", "answers": ["Franz Kafka", "Will Eisner", "R. C. Sherriff", "Bhalchandra Pundlik Adarkar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bliss?", "answers": ["Peter Carey", "John Jay", "Bhalchandra Pundlik Adarkar", "Stephen Hawking"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ozymandias?", "answers": ["Munshi Premchand", "Percy Bysshe Shelley", "Anthony Powell", "Christopher Ryan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Julius Caesar?", "answers": ["William Shakespeare", "James D. Houston", "Deborah Chiel", "John Jakes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dragon's Breath?", "answers": ["William F. Nolan", "Robert Burns", "E. D. Baker", "John Dickinson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Freedom at Midnight?", "answers": ["David Remnick", "K\u00e1roly Pap", "E. L. James", "Dominique Lapierre"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Freedom at Midnight?", "answers": ["George Orwell", "Larry Collins", "Patrick Ness", "Alice Raymon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Long Walk to Water?", "answers": ["Chris Crutcher", "Linda Sue Park", "Richard Harris", "Jody Rosen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Amy Foster?", "answers": ["Prentice Mulford", "Lauren Billings", "Petrarch", "Joseph Conrad"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Stranger?", "answers": ["Curtis Sittenfeld", "Charles de Lint", "Albert Camus", "Deja King"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Trainspotting?", "answers": ["Sun Tzu", "Henryk Sienkiewicz", "Irvine Welsh", "Craig Thomas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Spectacular Now?", "answers": ["Euripides", "Tim Tharp", "Thomas Malory", "Pierre de Beaumarchais"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Inside Delta Force?", "answers": ["James Herbert", "Flannery O'Connor", "Eric L. Haney", "Bankim Chandra Chattopadhyay"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Crucible?", "answers": ["John Clare", "Arthur Miller", "Jeremy Wilson", "Gary Ezzo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Freak the Mighty?", "answers": ["Stephen Crane", "Rodman Philbrick", "Nathaniel Hawthorne", "Poppy Z. Brite"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mrs Dalloway?", "answers": ["Charles A. Murray", "Wayne Short", "Virginia Woolf", "Fay Weldon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dream a Little Dream?", "answers": ["Johanna Spyri", "Ferdowsi", "Ransom Riggs", "Piers Anthony"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dream a Little Dream?", "answers": ["Edward S. Herman", "Pam Mu\u00f1oz Ryan", "Julie Brady", "John Boyne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Children Learn What They Live?", "answers": ["Rachel Harris", "Rumiko Takahashi", "Daniel James Brown", "Jane Cabrera"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dork Diaries: Tales From a Not-So-Fabulous Life?", "answers": ["William Stobbs", "Rachel Renee Russell", "David A. Adler", "Eric Kimmel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Carrie's War?", "answers": ["Nina Bawden", "W. R. Bolen", "Euripides", "Tom Rath"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Scarlet Pimpernel?", "answers": ["Darren Shan", "Curt Gentry", "William D. Cohan", "Baroness Emma Orczy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fire on the Mountain?", "answers": ["Cynthia Lord", "Deborah Chiel", "Helen Fielding", "Terry Bisson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rainbow Is Enuf?", "answers": ["Jeff Whitty", "Lynley Dodd", "Beverly D'Onofrio", "Ntozake Shange"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Silent Wife?", "answers": ["A. S. A. Harrison", "Harry Paul", "Francesca Simon", "Irvine Welsh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Magic School Bus Lost in the Solar System?", "answers": ["Michelle Magorian", "Richard Condon", "Charles Darwin", "Joanna Cole"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blue Moon?", "answers": ["Charles Frazier", "W. W. Jacobs", "Alyson Noel", "Jeremy Scahill"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Driving Miss Daisy?", "answers": ["Jon Ronson", "Penelope Williamson", "Michael Brandman", "Alfred Uhry"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Natural History?", "answers": ["Lucy Irvine", "Pliny the Elder", "James Ellroy", "Patrick Ness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ramona?", "answers": ["Christina Hobbs", "Bartolom\u00e9 de Las Casas", "Helen Hunt Jackson", "Anthony Powell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Devil's Dictionary?", "answers": ["Ambrose Bierce", "Terrance Dicks", "Hugh Wheeler", "Orson Scott Card"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book We Need to Talk About Kevin?", "answers": ["Lionel Shriver", "Kathryn Lasky", "Sofi Oksanen", "MacKinlay Kantor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Casanova's Chinese Restaurant?", "answers": ["Steven McShane", "Anthony Powell", "William Inge", "Kristin Cashore"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Alaska?", "answers": ["James A. Michener", "Piers Anthony", "Michael Symon", "Colette"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lucky One?", "answers": ["Howard Fast", "Caitlin Moran", "George R. R. Martin", "Nicholas Sparks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Poverty and Un-British Rule in India?", "answers": ["Jacques Rupnik", "Loretta Lynn", "Victor Hugo", "Dadabhai Naoroji"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Half the Sky: Turning Oppression into Opportunity for Women Worldwide?", "answers": ["Martin Handford", "Sheryl WuDunn", "Iris Johansen", "Susan Spencer-Wendel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Half the Sky: Turning Oppression into Opportunity for Women Worldwide?", "answers": ["Chris Crutcher", "Nicholas D. Kristof", "John Caird", "Theresa Karas Yianilos"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Democracy in America?", "answers": ["Kimon Valaskakis", "Koushun Takami", "Amy Vanderbilt", "Alexis de Tocqueville"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jekyll & Hyde?", "answers": ["Sandra Gilbert", "Leslie Bricusse", "Marion Kemp", "Desiderius Erasmus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book On a Clear Day You Can See Forever?", "answers": ["Alan Jay Lerner", "Bennett Cerf", "Margery Williams", "John Steinbeck"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Roses for English Gardens?", "answers": ["Gertrude Jekyll", "Marco Polo", "Ruth Westheimer", "Chris Cleave"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Black Dahlia?", "answers": ["Sonia Gandhi", "Raymond Briggs", "Erich Maria Remarque", "James Ellroy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Kiss Before Dying?", "answers": ["Clement Clarke Moore", "Gordon Korman", "Robert Ludlum", "Ira Levin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Black Pearl?", "answers": ["Mahatma Gandhi", "Candace Bushnell", "Scott O'Dell", "Reinhold Niebuhr"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Chorus Line?", "answers": ["James Kirkwood Jr.", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel", "Dennis Kelly", "Colin Escott"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Chorus Line?", "answers": ["Thomas Carlyle", "Roald Dahl", "Nicholas Dante", "Gregory David Roberts"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Everything is Illuminated?", "answers": ["Rachel Renee Russell", "Jonathan Safran Foer", "August Wilson", "Theodore Dreiser"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Thorn Birds?", "answers": ["Anne Rice", "Emma Clayton", "Colleen McCullough", "Florence Atwater"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ghosts?", "answers": ["Daniel Quinn", "Cassandra Clare", "Joseph Robinette", "Henrik Ibsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Train to Pakistan?", "answers": ["Tracy Letts", "Thor Heyerdahl", "Khushwant Singh", "William Thomas Stead"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The 4-Hour Workweek?", "answers": ["Margaret Edson", "Timothy Ferriss", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel", "William Howard Armstrong"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Little Bee?", "answers": ["Eve Adamson", "Chris Cleave", "Nicholas Evans", "Shannon Hale"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Once?", "answers": ["Spencer Johnson", "Enda Walsh", "W.E.B. Du Bois", "Muhammad al-Bukhari"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The wooing of Beppo Tate?", "answers": ["C. Everard Palmer", "Horace Silver", "Virgil", "Narmad\u0101pras\u0101da Up\u0101dhy\u0101ya"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Woman in Black?", "answers": ["Kathryn Lasky", "Susan Hill", "Alexander Hamilton", "Danae Yankoski"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Snow Falling on Cedars?", "answers": ["Markus Zusak", "David Guterson", "Natalie Babbitt", "Tim Tharp"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Driving Miss Daisy?", "answers": ["Jodi Picoult", "Wilson Rawls", "Che Guevara", "Alfred Uhry"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Forrest Gump?", "answers": ["John F. Kennedy", "Pam Mu\u00f1oz Ryan", "Andrew Ross Sorkin", "Winston Groom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Merchant of Venice?", "answers": ["Mark the Evangelist", "William Shakespeare", "Bryce Courtenay", "Ezra Jack Keats"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gremlins?", "answers": ["Emma Clayton", "Amador Taguinod Daguio", "Roald Dahl", "Koushun Takami"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Freckle Juice?", "answers": ["Henry James", "James Stevens", "Judy Blume", "Edith Wharton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Three Bears?", "answers": ["Paul Fleischman", "William Stobbs", "Sharon Flake", "David Henry Hwang"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Three Bears?", "answers": ["Nicky Hager", "Steven Curtis Chapman", "Robert Southey", "Charles Dickens"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Insurgent?", "answers": ["Joe R. Lansdale", "Lisa Genova", "Ann M. Martin", "Veronica Roth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wifey?", "answers": ["Stephenie Meyer", "Judy Blume", "Christina Hobbs", "Micky Dolenz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Richest Man In Babylon?", "answers": ["George Samuel Clason", "Daniel Woodrell", "Pervez Musharraf", "Roland Barthes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Proof?", "answers": ["Mary Schmich", "Adeline Yen Mah", "James Patterson", "David Auburn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Forever Amber?", "answers": ["Tholkappiar", "P. D. Eastman", "Michael Connelly", "Kathleen Winsor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book House of Cards?", "answers": ["Fania Oz-Salzberger", "Sarah Young", "William D. Cohan", "Umberto Eco"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Death in the Desert?", "answers": ["Sheryl WuDunn", "Willa Cather", "Mel Brooks", "Eleanor Coerr"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book John Dies at the End?", "answers": ["Tony Mendez", "David Wong", "Chris Ryan", "Barry M. Goldwater"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Emma?", "answers": ["Mike Leigh", "Christopher McDougall", "Jane Austen", "Bill Bryson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Evergreen?", "answers": ["Ayaan Hirsi Ali", "Barbara Ehrenreich", "Barbara Taylor Bradford", "Belva Plain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chicago?", "answers": ["Pam Mu\u00f1oz Ryan", "Fred Ebb", "Sir John Retcliffe", "John D. Voelker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chicago?", "answers": ["Herman Melville", "Isobel Lennart", "Maurine Dallas Watkins", "Mario Puzo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chicago?", "answers": ["John of Patmos", "Bob Fosse", "Richard Stilgoe", "John O'Hara"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Born Free: The Full Story?", "answers": ["Pamela Druckerman", "Joy Adamson", "Belle de Jour", "A. J. Cronin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Where the Heart Is?", "answers": ["Billie Letts", "Peter Barnes", "Kathleen Grissom", "Thomas Bell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Leviathan?", "answers": ["Paulo Lins", "Sue Monk Kidd", "Florence Nightingale", "Scott Westerfeld"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rear Window?", "answers": ["Cornell Woolrich", "Kate Chopin", "Dik A. Daso", "Jojo Moyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Flowers for Algernon?", "answers": ["Charles Portis", "Daniel Keyes", "George Dekker", "Boris Pasternak"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Bell for Adano?", "answers": ["Michael Serra", "John Hersey", "David Brauner", "Iris Chang"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chocolate Fever?", "answers": ["John Berendt", "Pierre de Beaumarchais", "Emma Clayton", "Robert Kimmel Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In a Different Voice?", "answers": ["Carol Gilligan", "Irvine Welsh", "James Baldwin", "Anne Rice"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Deathtrap?", "answers": ["Bruce Sterling", "Ira Levin", "H. P. Lovecraft", "Joseph Heller"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Auntie Mame?", "answers": ["Eowyn Ivey", "Patrick Dennis", "David Oliver Relin", "Bert Dodson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Secret Life of Bees?", "answers": ["Sue Monk Kidd", "Harry Turtledove", "Richard Bach", "Luke the Evangelist"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mass Effect: Revelation?", "answers": ["Stephen J. Dubner", "Joceline Sanschagrin", "Drew Karpyshyn", "Ethan Hawke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Night?", "answers": ["David Guterson", "Elie Wiesel", "Solomon", "Roddy Doyle"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Red Noses?", "answers": ["Peter Barnes", "Bibhutibhushan Bandopadhyay", "William Goldman", "Graham Greene"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Silent Spring?", "answers": ["Rachel Carson", "Harry Turtledove", "Arthur Ashe", "Homer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cyrano de Bergerac?", "answers": ["Edmond Rostand", "Axel Scheffler", "Edgar Wallace", "Robert Louis Stevenson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Algorithms + Data Structures = Programs?", "answers": ["Niklaus Wirth", "Rumiko Takahashi", "Jacqueline Wilson", "James C. Collins"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Purpose Driven Life: What on Earth Am I Here For??", "answers": ["R. Kelly Rainer", "Charles Nordhoff", "George Howe Colt", "Rick Warren"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tuesdays With Morrie?", "answers": ["Ethan Hawke", "Mitch Albom", "Kyle Onstott", "Wilhelm Grimm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Looking Unto Jesus?", "answers": ["Christina Hobbs", "Charles Dickens", "Charles Spurgeon", "Leon Edel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book MONKEY + CROCODILE PA+AUDIO?", "answers": ["Joanna C. Galdone", "John August", "Henry James", "Ouida"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Young Goodman Brown?", "answers": ["Nathaniel Hawthorne", "E. Annie Proulx", "Sigmund Freud", "Katie Davis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Attack?", "answers": ["Anne Mazer", "Liz Tuccillo", "James Thurber", "Yasmina Khadra"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Contemporary Jewish-American novelists?", "answers": ["Mark Bowden", "Jeremy Wilson", "Carl Sagan", "Joel Shatzky"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A cow called Boy?", "answers": ["Steven Curtis Chapman", "Taslima Nasrin", "C. Everard Palmer", "Luther Davis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes?", "answers": ["Arthur Conan Doyle", "R. J. Palacio", "Robert Wooster", "Ray Bradbury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ghetto?", "answers": ["Dorothy Wall", "Joshua Sobol", "Sylvia Nasar", "James Thurber"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I'm a believer?", "answers": ["Micky Dolenz", "Slavomir Rawicz", "W. C. Heinz", "Jeffrey Eugenides"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tibetan book of the dead?", "answers": ["Mary Chase", "Robert Harling", "Karma-glin\u0307-pa", "Horace Silver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sceptical Chymist?", "answers": ["Bede", "John Archambault", "Robert Boyle", "Michael Jackson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lieutenant Hornblower?", "answers": ["Euclid", "C. S. Forester", "Cormac McCarthy", "Maurine Dallas Watkins"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The monk's wedding?", "answers": ["Matthew Reilly", "Guy Bolton", "Raymond Queneau", "Conrad Ferdinand Meyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Firm?", "answers": ["John Grisham", "Arthur C. Clarke", "Steven D. Levitt", "Helaine Fendelman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Third Man?", "answers": ["James Marshall", "Aeschylus", "Lincoln Steffens", "Graham Greene"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Go-Between?", "answers": ["Shepherd Mead", "Simon Armitage", "L. P. Hartley", "Beverly Lewis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book conscience of a Conservative?", "answers": ["Virginia Woolf", "Robert Thornton Morrison", "Barry M. Goldwater", "Jerome K. Jerome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Count of Monte Cristo?", "answers": ["Alexandre Dumas", "Diana Hacker", "Jawaharlal Nehru", "Napoleon Hill"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Count of Monte Cristo?", "answers": ["J. Meade Falkner", "Winston Groom", "Auguste Maquet", "Ken Follett"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Hope They Serve Beer in Hell?", "answers": ["Farhat Ishtiaq", "John Knowles", "Tucker Max", "Gary D. Chapman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Father's Dragon?", "answers": ["Ruth Stiles Gannett", "James Joyce", "Friedrich Engels", "Thomas C. Holt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Portrait of a Lady?", "answers": ["David Margolick", "Henry James", "Barbara Ehrenreich", "Belle de Jour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Cape Cod Mystery?", "answers": ["Lloyd Jones", "Dan Poynter", "Phoebe Atwood Taylor", "Iain Banks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Help?", "answers": ["Kathleen Winsor", "Catherine Hapka", "Kathryn Stockett", "Kathryn Lasky"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blood brothers?", "answers": ["Deborah Ellis", "Nassim Nicholas Taleb", "Elias Chacour", "Corrie ten Boom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book As You Like It?", "answers": ["Rosalind Wiseman", "Michael Mayer", "William Shakespeare", "Bernard Malamud"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book If You Give a Mouse a Cookie?", "answers": ["Laura Numeroff", "Philip Carlo", "Steven Gould", "Wendy Mass"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tell-Tale Heart?", "answers": ["Edgar Allan Poe", "Clement Clarke Moore", "Tom Rob Smith", "Shelagh Delaney"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Guardian?", "answers": ["James Herriot", "Nicholas Sparks", "Robin Cook", "Jean Claverie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Che Guevara: A Revolutionary Life?", "answers": ["Margaret Peterson Haddix", "Jack London", "Jon Lee Anderson", "Ronald David Laing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Spirit of the Laws?", "answers": ["Todd Strasser", "Montesquieu", "Jean-Paul Sartre", "Anna Dewdney"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Almost Home?", "answers": ["Joseph Kesselring", "Debbie Macomber", "Rodman Philbrick", "Sarah Orne Jewett"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Almost Home?", "answers": ["Vincent Bugliosi", "J. G. Ballard", "Cathy Lamb", "Kristin Hannah"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Almost Home?", "answers": ["Reza Aslan", "Mary Carter", "Henry Bellamann", "Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Almost Home?", "answers": ["Stephen W. Garber", "Matthew the Apostle", "Abul Kalam Azad", "Judy Duarte"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The self-publishing manual?", "answers": ["Dan Poynter", "Desmond Barry", "Mark Kurlansky", "Thomas \u00e0 Kempis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bear?", "answers": ["Glen Rounds", "Robert Louis Stevenson", "Anton Chekhov", "Quiara Alegr\u00eda Hudes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The New Woman?", "answers": ["Mary Norton", "Ovid", "Boles\u0142aw Prus", "Abba Eban"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bad. Original Lyrics Lithography: Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Barbara Taylor Bradford", "James Herriot", "Michael Jackson", "Bill W."], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Marley & Me: Life and Love with the World's Worst Dog?", "answers": ["Fred Graver", "Walter Dean Myers", "John Grogan", "Adolf Hitler"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Rumor of War?", "answers": ["Sara Shepard", "Paul Fleischman", "Philip Caputo", "Whitney Stewart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cosmos?", "answers": ["Daniel Quinn", "Nan Knighton", "Carl Sagan", "Lloyd D. Newell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Artemis Fowl?", "answers": ["Jane Hamilton", "Barbara O'Connor", "Frank Wedekind", "Eoin Colfer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rajiv's World?", "answers": ["Sonia Gandhi", "H. A. Rey", "Henry James", "Greg Behrendt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rigveda: A Historical Analysis?", "answers": ["David Icke", "Amely Greeven", "Shrikant G. Talageri", "Linda Woolverton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The flight of Icarus?", "answers": ["Marghanita Laski", "Thornton Wilder", "Charles Darwin", "Raymond Queneau"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book American Beauty?", "answers": ["Aravind Adiga", "Anne Rice", "Lois Banner", "Frances Hodgson Burnett"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Raisin in the Sun?", "answers": ["Richard Bach", "Cynthia Kadohata", "Lorraine Hansberry", "Steven D. Levitt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Because of Winn-Dixie?", "answers": ["Alfred Noyes", "Eoin Colfer", "Michael Mayer", "Kate DiCamillo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Incidents in the Life of a Slave Girl?", "answers": ["Iris Murdoch", "Anthony Burgess", "Harriet Ann Jacobs", "Frank Lauria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rufus Jones: Essential Writings?", "answers": ["Alexis de Tocqueville", "Trent Lott", "Rufus Jones", "James Alexander Thom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book John Adams?", "answers": ["Willa Cather", "Aristophanes", "David McCullough", "Dave Barry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Am David?", "answers": ["William Manchester", "Mary Alice Monroe", "Anne Holm", "David Patterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A voice for freedom?", "answers": ["Herman J. Mankiewicz", "David Nicholls", "Anne Bront\u00eb", "Nayantara Sahgal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Marjorie Morningstar?", "answers": ["Herman Wouk", "Henry Beveridge", "Richard Adams", "Brian Kernighan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jaws?", "answers": ["Ronald David Laing", "Miriam Toews", "John Archambault", "Peter Benchley"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sounder?", "answers": ["William Howard Armstrong", "Loretta Lynn", "Fran\u00e7oise Sagan", "Carol Gilligan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Scarlet Pimpernel?", "answers": ["Irvine Welsh", "Daniel Quinn", "Nan Knighton", "Mike Resnick"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Shunning?", "answers": ["Katherine Mayo", "Beverly Lewis", "Arnold Rampersad", "Newt Gingrich"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gospel of Matthew?", "answers": ["Matthew the Apostle", "Tobias Wolff", "Nicholas Dante", "Naoki Higashida"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Monster Calls?", "answers": ["Harold Robbins", "Patrick Ness", "Germaine Greer", "Wayne Short"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Riptide?", "answers": ["Douglas Preston", "Piper Kerman", "Wendy Fonarow", "Sister Souljah"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Riptide?", "answers": ["Francine Rivers", "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", "Lincoln Child", "Alexandra Ripley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A More Perfect Union?", "answers": ["Janet Riehecky", "Liz Lark", "J. A. Jance", "Lionel Shriver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Inherit the Wind?", "answers": ["Stephen Mallatratt", "Ayi Kwei Armah", "Leon Uris", "Jerome Lawrence"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Inherit the Wind?", "answers": ["Robert Edwin Lee", "Harvey Diamond", "Josh McDowell", "Charles Spurgeon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cider with Rosie?", "answers": ["Laurie Lee", "Dale Carnegie", "Phoebe Atwood Taylor", "Franz Kafka"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Song of Hiawatha?", "answers": ["P. C. Wren", "George Vecsey", "Paige Turner", "Henry Wadsworth Longfellow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Song to David?", "answers": ["Christopher Smart", "Philip Caputo", "Jess Walter", "Faith Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Boy's Own Story?", "answers": ["Wallace Thurman", "Christopher Collier", "Poppy Z. Brite", "Edmund White"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rip Van Winkle?", "answers": ["James Ellroy", "Sri Aurobindo", "Washington Irving", "Erica Jong"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Joy Luck Club?", "answers": ["Ernest Poole", "John Gardner", "Amy Tan", "Katharine Holabird"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Catcher in the Rye?", "answers": ["George Stanley", "Helen Bannerman", "Dylan Thomas", "J. D. Salinger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chesapeake?", "answers": ["Nelson George", "James A. Michener", "Primo Levi", "Prosper M\u00e9rim\u00e9e"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book West Side Story?", "answers": ["Irving Shulman", "Alfred North Whitehead", "Sinclair Lewis", "Roger Lancelyn Green"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pied Piper of Hamelin?", "answers": ["Johann Wolfgang von Goethe", "David Hackett Fischer", "Dayananda Saraswati", "Joanna Cole"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pied Piper of Hamelin?", "answers": ["Ali", "Henry Beveridge", "Stephanie Stuve-Bodeen", "Robert Browning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Christmas Story: The Musical?", "answers": ["John Guare", "Sylvia Nasar", "William F. Brown", "Joseph Robinette"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Phantom Tollbooth?", "answers": ["Norton Juster", "Ashley Gardner", "Pete Earley", "Robert Graves"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gospel of John?", "answers": ["John the Evangelist", "A. J. Quinnell", "Christopher Isherwood", "Richard Castle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Metamorphosis?", "answers": ["Nicholas D. Kristof", "Lloyd C. Douglas", "Cornell Woolrich", "Franz Kafka"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Red Dwarf: Infinity Welcomes Careful Drivers?", "answers": ["Alan Dean Foster", "Frank Herbert", "David Lindsay-Abaire", "Rob Grant"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Red Dwarf: Infinity Welcomes Careful Drivers?", "answers": ["Jacob Grimm", "William Makepeace Thackeray", "David Guterson", "Doug Naylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fever Pitch?", "answers": ["Nicolaus Copernicus", "Joseph Conrad", "Nick Hornby", "Rex Pickett"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gargoyles of Notre Dame?", "answers": ["Philip Carlo", "India Knight", "Michael Camille", "Fred Graver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The magic porridge pot?", "answers": ["Diana Wynne Jones", "Douglas Carter Beane", "K. A. Applegate", "Paul Galdone"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Trial?", "answers": ["Arna Bontemps", "Franz Kafka", "E. L. Doctorow", "Basil Liddell Hart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beautiful Boy?", "answers": ["Bob Dylan", "Matt Stone", "Amartya Sen", "David Sheff"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Prince of Tides?", "answers": ["Carl Van Vechten", "Pat Conroy", "Roddy Doyle", "Kerry Patterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The House of Bernarda Alba?", "answers": ["Karen Blixen", "Federico Garc\u00eda Lorca", "Orson Scott Card", "John Osborne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Damn Yankees?", "answers": ["Douglass Wallop", "Reza Aslan", "Harold Kushner", "Ram Dass"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Damn Yankees?", "answers": ["Ira Wood", "George Abbott", "Charles Bukowski", "Virgil"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Law of Attraction?", "answers": ["Bobby Lynn Maslen", "Reginald Rose", "Michael J. Losier", "Robert Browning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bridget Jones's Diary?", "answers": ["Dave Thompson", "Bill Yoast", "Helen Fielding", "Michael Hollinger"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bared to You?", "answers": ["Sylvia Day", "Kathryn Erskine", "Robert Ludlum", "Lewis Carroll"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Message in a Bottle?", "answers": ["Nicholas Sparks", "Gordon Elliott", "T. H. White", "Sholem Asch"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Basketball Diaries?", "answers": ["John O'Grady", "Jim Carroll", "John Dempsey", "Phoebe Atwood Taylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Holes?", "answers": ["Mridula Baljekar", "Sofi Oksanen", "Dorothy Allison", "Louis Sachar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Woman in Berlin?", "answers": ["Marta Hillers", "Eduard Jose", "Sharon Mazel", "Sherman Alexie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fathers and Sons?", "answers": ["Milan Kundera", "Booth Tarkington", "Isaac Newton", "Ivan Turgenev"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Long Way from Chicago?", "answers": ["Maggie Stiefvater", "Richard Peck", "Lisa Genova", "Hunter S. Thompson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Where's Wally?: The Wonder Book?", "answers": ["Andrew Lloyd Webber", "Martin Handford", "Jim Bouton", "V\u0101tsy\u0101yana"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pearl?", "answers": ["Joel Shatzky", "John Steinbeck", "Sherry Argov", "Eric Berne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Before I Die?", "answers": ["Jenny Downham", "Zelda Fitzgerald", "Diana Gabaldon", "Shannon Hale"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Natural born killers?", "answers": ["Mark Medoff", "Marian Keyes", "Quentin Tarantino", "Paul Howard"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jonathan Livingston Seagull?", "answers": ["Richard Bach", "Susan Hill", "Richard Herrnstein", "Paramahansa Yogananda"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Producers?", "answers": ["Eleanor Coerr", "Amely Greeven", "Elizabeth Gaskell", "Mel Brooks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Producers?", "answers": ["Eva Ibbotson", "Nina Bawden", "Malcolm X", "Thomas Meehan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Swiss Family Robinson?", "answers": ["Johann David Wyss", "Robert Munsch", "Fay Weldon", "Virgil"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book God Don't Like Ugly?", "answers": ["John Banville", "Thomas Bell", "Desmond Barry", "Mary Alice Monroe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sister Carrie?", "answers": ["Halima Bashir", "Theodore Dreiser", "Marion Kemp", "Pittacus Lore"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Red kayak?", "answers": ["Priscilla Cummings", "Tyler Perry", "Nelson Mandela", "Ira Levin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book White Fang?", "answers": ["Ivan Turgenev", "Jack London", "Robyn Carr", "Jon Krakauer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Turner Diaries?", "answers": ["T. Colin Campbell", "William Luther Pierce", "Paige Turner", "Tom Clancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shane?", "answers": ["Jack Schaefer", "Tony Hillerman", "Doris Roettger", "Ishmael Beah"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Grumpy Cat?", "answers": ["Rudolph Besier", "Margaret Floy Washburn", "Grumpy Cat", "Jeanne DuPrau"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lady Vanishes?", "answers": ["Tobias Wolff", "Ethel Lina White", "Ori Brafman", "Ferenc Moln\u00e1r"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Silas Marner?", "answers": ["Marcia Brown", "George Eliot", "Kris Carr", "Erskine Caldwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Night Film?", "answers": ["Honor\u00e9 de Balzac", "Marisha Pessl", "Patrick Robinson", "Tom Rob Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gettysburg: A Novel of the Civil War?", "answers": ["Kamala Markandaya", "Walt Whitman", "Steve Sullivan", "Newt Gingrich"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gettysburg: A Novel of the Civil War?", "answers": ["Thomas C Foster", "Taro Gomi", "Francesca Simon", "William R. Forstchen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gentlemen Prefer Blondes?", "answers": ["Winston Groom", "Anita Loos", "Edwin Meese", "T. H. White"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kaleidoscope?", "answers": ["John Milton", "Jim Jacobs", "Harry Turtledove", "Ernest Poole"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kaleidoscope?", "answers": ["Malcolm Lowry", "Danielle Steel", "Jonathan Cahn", "Jodi Picoult"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fire and Ice?", "answers": ["Kate Cary", "John-Michael Tebelak", "Amartya Sen", "Murasaki Shikibu"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fire and Ice?", "answers": ["James Alexander Thom", "Victoria Holmes", "Elizabeth Jolley", "John Adams"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Swallows and Amazons?", "answers": ["Arthur Ransome", "Euclid", "Christa Faust", "Michael Morpurgo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Man in the Iron Mask?", "answers": ["Alexandre Dumas", "Pierre Boulle", "Sri Aurobindo", "Michael Symon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Paradise Lost?", "answers": ["John Milton", "Mary Chase", "Herman Koch", "Eric Berne"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Best Lesbian Romance?", "answers": ["Patrick Robinson", "Naomi Mitchison", "Angela Brown", "Ann M. Martin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Prophet?", "answers": ["Khalil Gibran", "William F. Nolan", "James Dashner", "Billie Joe Armstrong"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tuzk-e-Jahangiri?", "answers": ["Jahangir", "Jeannette Walls", "Heidi Murkoff", "Robert Hillenbrand"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Home to Big Stone Gap?", "answers": ["Rachel Harris", "Eleanor Farjeon", "Adriana Trigiani", "Amos Oz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nana?", "answers": ["Wallace Stegner", "Robert Browning", "Elmore Leonard", "\u00c9mile Zola"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Phantom of the Opera?", "answers": ["Andrew Lloyd Webber", "Ali", "Bibhutibhushan Bandopadhyay", "Greg Cox"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Phantom of the Opera?", "answers": ["Richard Stilgoe", "Jess Walter", "Christopher Paolini", "Jeffrey Zaslow"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Congo?", "answers": ["Michael Crichton", "Muhammad al-Bukhari", "Theodore Dreiser", "Esphyr Slobodkina"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Such a Long Journey?", "answers": ["Rohinton Mistry", "Patrick J. O'Brian", "Elizabeth Jolley", "Alice Schroeder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blowin' in the Wind?", "answers": ["Norton Juster", "Oscar Hammerstein II", "Bob Dylan", "Pat Conroy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Devil May Care?", "answers": ["Lucy Irvine", "Sebastian Faulks", "Pearl S. Buck", "Halima Bashir"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Manhattan Transfer?", "answers": ["Susan Beth Pfeffer", "Jean Craighead George", "Munro Leaf", "John Dos Passos"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Caine Mutiny?", "answers": ["Patrick Robinson", "Dav Pilkey", "Herman Wouk", "Jerry Hicks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Walk Two Moons?", "answers": ["Steve Eng", "Mitch Albom", "Sharon Creech", "Henry Bellamann"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Castaway?", "answers": ["John Irving", "Douglas Carter Beane", "Lucy Irvine", "Lois Lowry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pitch Black?", "answers": ["Munshi Premchand", "Gary D. Chapman", "Frank Lauria", "Fred Gipson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sh*t My Dad Says?", "answers": ["Jess Walter", "Joyce Carol Oates", "One Direction", "Justin Halpern"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ginger Pye?", "answers": ["Harold Bell Wright", "Enid Blyton", "Bruce Sterling", "Eleanor Estes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How Do I Love Thee?: The Love-letters of Robert Browning and Elizabeth Barrett?", "answers": ["Lionel Shriver", "Ellen Hopkins", "Elizabeth Barrett Browning", "Amrita Pritam"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Infinity Ring Book 7: The Iron Empire - Library Edition?", "answers": ["Saki", "James Dashner", "Homer", "Petrarch"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ivanhoe?", "answers": ["Walter Scott", "Else Holmelund Minarik", "Sharon Mazel", "Thor Heyerdahl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book MS. Found in a Bottle?", "answers": ["Brendan Behan", "Edgar Allan Poe", "Edmund Spenser", "Simon Dunstan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Misery?", "answers": ["Ellen G. White", "Jim Bouton", "Anthony Powell", "Stephen King"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Death of a Salesman?", "answers": ["Samuel Richardson", "Sheila Quigley", "Arthur Miller", "Kazuo Ishiguro"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lottery Ticket?", "answers": ["William Boyd", "Karen Traviss", "Stendhal", "Jules Verne"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Old Yeller?", "answers": ["Hugh Johnson", "Fred Gipson", "Mary Norton", "Mahatma Gandhi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to Win Friends and Influence People?", "answers": ["George Bernard Shaw", "Dale Carnegie", "Ellen Hopkins", "Owen Wister"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rules of the Road?", "answers": ["Sarat Chandra Chattopadhyay", "T. H. White", "Daniel Silva", "Joan Bauer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ash Wednesday?", "answers": ["Bert Dodson", "J. K. Rowling", "Shelagh Delaney", "Ethan Hawke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Verdict?", "answers": ["Barry Reed", "Michael Grace", "Pearl S. Buck", "Michael Brandman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Brighton Beach Memoirs?", "answers": ["Curt Gentry", "Neil Simon", "Robert R. McCammon", "Jerome Lawrence"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sammy Keyes and the Hotel Thief?", "answers": ["Ferdowsi", "Lane Becker", "A. J. Quinnell", "Wendelin Van Draanen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Orlando: A Biography?", "answers": ["Ben Mezrich", "Virginia Woolf", "Milton William Cooper", "Tom Rath"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ode to Joy?", "answers": ["Johann Christoph Friedrich von Schiller", "Lawrence Kimbrough", "Lois Banner", "Amos Oz"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Follow the Rabbit-Proof Fence?", "answers": ["Doris Pilkington Garimara", "Fyodor Dostoyevsky", "Elizabeth Wurtzel", "Jane Hamilton"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Frindle?", "answers": ["David Brauner", "Andrew Clements", "Philipp Melanchthon", "Malcolm Lowry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A White Heron: A Story of Maine?", "answers": ["Barbara Kingsolver", "Nan Knighton", "Sarah Orne Jewett", "Horace Silver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Shining?", "answers": ["James Joyce", "Michael Chabon", "Stephen King", "Michael Flatley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Out of This Furnace?", "answers": ["Jon Krakauer", "Thomas Bell", "Madeleine L'Engle", "Henry James"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book City of Joy?", "answers": ["Alexander Hamilton", "S. E. Hinton", "M. L. Stedman", "Dominique Lapierre"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close?", "answers": ["Irving Shulman", "Mary Higgins Clark", "Robert Newton Peck", "Jonathan Safran Foer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Square Egg?", "answers": ["Saki", "Robert Hillenbrand", "Stieg Larsson", "Hilary Mantel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The 48 Laws of Power?", "answers": ["Cecil Frances Humphreys Alexander", "Eric Carle", "Adriana Trigiani", "Robert Greene"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ransom of Red Chief?", "answers": ["Brian Yorkey", "Greil Marcus", "O. Henry", "Daniel Silva"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book All the Pretty Horses?", "answers": ["Steve Eng", "Angela Brown", "Cormac McCarthy", "Dr. Seuss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lucky Jim?", "answers": ["A. C. H. Smith", "Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie", "Angela Johnson", "Kingsley Amis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book King and Maxwell?", "answers": ["Mary Carter", "David Baldacci", "James Fenimore Cooper", "Uri Shulevitz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rum Diary?", "answers": ["Hunter S. Thompson", "Shashi Tharoor", "Alan Brennert", "Tahereh Mafi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Red Kayak?", "answers": ["Priscilla Cummings", "Lucy Irvine", "Jennifer L. Holm", "Charles de Lint"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Still Alice?", "answers": ["Lisa Genova", "Dean Hughes", "Sheila Quigley", "Washington Irving"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Atonement?", "answers": ["Edward Gibbon", "Ian McEwan", "Marilyn Diamond", "J. L. Carr"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Oh! Calcutta!?", "answers": ["Pearl Poet", "Alain Boublil", "Kenneth Tynan", "Ford Madox Ford"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tintin?", "answers": ["Katie Davis", "Harry Thompson", "Thomas Jefferson", "Koushun Takami"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peace Like a River?", "answers": ["Leif Enger", "Ted Sorensen", "J. D. Salinger", "Michael Grant"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Speak?", "answers": ["Eric Blehm", "O. Henry", "Laurie Halse Anderson", "Corrie ten Boom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Under the Dome?", "answers": ["E. L. Doctorow", "Munro Leaf", "Stephen King", "John R. Erickson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chicka Chicka Boom Boom?", "answers": ["John Archambault", "Thomas C Foster", "Eve Ensler", "Greg Mortenson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Satyarth Prakash?", "answers": ["Dayananda Saraswati", "Sarah Waters", "Charles de Lint", "Martin Amis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book He's Just Not That into You?", "answers": ["Liz Tuccillo", "Eddi Fiegel", "Elizabeth Jolley", "Erin Morgenstern"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book He's Just Not That into You?", "answers": ["David Mitchell", "Steven McShane", "Greg Behrendt", "Halima Bashir"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book John Brown's Body?", "answers": ["Harry Mazer", "Ford Madox Ford", "Stephen Vincent Ben\u00e9t", "Carlo Collodi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Twelve Steps and Twelve Traditions?", "answers": ["Kingsley Amis", "Alcoholics Anonymous", "Khalil Gibran", "Edgar Allan Poe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jabberwocky?", "answers": ["George Gipe", "Lewis Carroll", "Peter Shaffer", "Frank McCourt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nahj al-Balagha?", "answers": ["Stephen Fishman", "Timothy Ferriss", "Katherine Mayo", "Al-Sharif al-Radi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nahj al-Balagha?", "answers": ["Ali", "Bob Goff", "Maggie Stiefvater", "Lee Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book All the King's Men?", "answers": ["Robert Penn Warren", "James Dashner", "Gary Jennings", "Michael Cunningham"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Study guide to organic chemistry?", "answers": ["Karl Marx", "Margaret Edson", "Robert Thornton Morrison", "Chris Cleave"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Amityville Horror?", "answers": ["Moli\u00e8re", "Dante Alighieri", "Heidi Murkoff", "Jay Anson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Black Like Me?", "answers": ["Adolf Hitler", "John Howard Griffin", "David Foster Wallace", "Kathryn Stockett"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book So You Want To Write?", "answers": ["Richard Herrnstein", "Dick Roughsey", "Thomas Hardy", "Ira Wood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book So You Want To Write?", "answers": ["Marge Piercy", "Laura Hillenbrand", "Rumiko Takahashi", "James Stevens"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Les Liaisons dangereuses?", "answers": ["Friedrich Engels", "Mark Stewart", "William Thomas Stead", "Pierre Choderlos de Laclos"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Esperanza Rising?", "answers": ["Booth Tarkington", "Warren Lockhart", "L. Frank Baum", "Pam Mu\u00f1oz Ryan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lincoln: The Biography of a Writer?", "answers": ["Ezra Jack Keats", "Prentice Mulford", "Raina Telgemeier", "Fred Kaplan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jesus of Nazareth: The Infancy Narratives?", "answers": ["John Locke", "Pope Benedict XVI", "Kamala Markandaya", "R. J. Palacio"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book To Build a Fire?", "answers": ["Eduard Jose", "Jack London", "Julia Donaldson", "Naoki Higashida"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book \"A Child Called \"\"It\"\": One Child's Courage to Survive\"?", "answers": ["Nancy Milford", "Tatiana De Rosnay", "Dave Pelzer", "Roark Bradford"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dutchman?", "answers": ["Allen Ginsberg", "Barry Reed", "Amiri Baraka", "William Langland"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ah Sin?", "answers": ["Graham Greene", "Helene Hanff", "Alain Boublil", "Mark Twain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Perfect Storm?", "answers": ["Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn", "John Irving", "Sebastian Junger", "Stendhal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Four Agreements: A Practical Guide to Personal Freedom?", "answers": ["Javier Calvo", "Eugene O'Neill", "Miguel \u00c1ngel Ruiz", "Harriet Beecher Stowe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Half Broke Horses: A True-Life Novel?", "answers": ["Isabel Allende", "Ben Carson", "Justin Cronin", "Jeannette Walls"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Eudora: A Writer's Life?", "answers": ["George MacDonald Fraser", "William Howard Armstrong", "Ann Waldron", "Ethan Hawke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Llama Llama Plush?", "answers": ["Dave Eggers", "Ernest Hemingway", "Anna Dewdney", "Eckhart Tolle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Adventures of Huckleberry Finn?", "answers": ["Peter Barnes", "Barbara O'Connor", "Mark Twain", "Jack Higgins"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rocky Horror Show?", "answers": ["Richard O'Brien", "George Harrison", "Dennis Kelly", "Sogyal Rinpoche"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Contagion?", "answers": ["George Stanley", "Dick Roughsey", "Jason Gehlert", "Henry Miller"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Contagion?", "answers": ["Alfred Uhry", "Richard Preston", "Patrick Dennis", "Robin Cook"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book 1408?", "answers": ["Heather Hach", "Stephen King", "Sattar Memon", "Geoffrey of Monmouth"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Looking for Alibrandi?", "answers": ["Richard Matheson", "Susan Spencer-Wendel", "Jennifer L. Holm", "Melina Marchetta"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Elmer Gantry?", "answers": ["James Howard Kunstler", "Enda Walsh", "Sinclair Lewis", "Naomi Mitchison"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Behold a Pale Horse?", "answers": ["Eowyn Ivey", "Aleister Crowley", "Hubert Horton McAlexander", "Milton William Cooper"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Shipping News?", "answers": ["William S. Burroughs", "Roark Bradford", "E. Annie Proulx", "William Bradford"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tiger! Tiger!?", "answers": ["Sarah Kane", "Marjorie Garber", "Thomas J. Stanley", "Rudyard Kipling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The adulteress?", "answers": ["Eleanor Hibbert", "Raj\u0101\u02bc \u02bbAbd All\u0101h \u1e62\u0101ni\u02bb", "Jonathan Harr", "Eric S. Nylund"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Original Adventures of Hank the Cowdog?", "answers": ["Peter Carey", "Mulk Raj Anand", "John R. Erickson", "Prentice Mulford"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Godaan?", "answers": ["Stephen Templin", "Leonard Everett Fisher", "Lala Lajpat Rai", "Munshi Premchand"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Helter Skelter?", "answers": ["Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry", "Marisha Pessl", "Curt Gentry", "Laurie Lee"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Helter Skelter?", "answers": ["Pat Conroy", "Vincent Bugliosi", "Douglas Angus", "Robert Ruark"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hyperion Cantos?", "answers": ["Rajendra Prasad", "Victor Stafford Reid", "Dan Simmons", "Wendy Fonarow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book We're Going on a Bear Hunt?", "answers": ["Michael Rosen", "Dashiell Hammett", "Sara Gruen", "Virginia Woolf"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sarum?", "answers": ["M. NourbeSe Philip", "Kaui Hart Hemmings", "George Harrison", "Edward Rutherfurd"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Animal Farm?", "answers": ["George Orwell", "Jerry Hicks", "Anthony Burgess", "Tennessee Williams"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A worn path?", "answers": ["Eudora Welty", "George Ella Lyon", "Walter Lord", "Scott Turow"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book India-My-Dream: An Interactive Lectures Series Agenda for the Nation?", "answers": ["A. P. J. Abdul Kalam", "Ignatius L. Donnelly", "Kamala Markandaya", "Alexis de Tocqueville"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Farewell to Manzanar?", "answers": ["William Golding", "Jeanne Wakatsuki Houston", "Mao Zedong", "Harlan Coben"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Farewell to Manzanar?", "answers": ["Boles\u0142aw Prus", "Ben Mikaelsen", "James D. Houston", "Esther Forbes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sundara Kanda?", "answers": ["Charlotte Bront\u00eb", "Valmiki", "Mary Wollstonecraft", "J. A. Jance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The headless horseman?", "answers": ["William Stobbs", "Natalie Standiford", "Lisa Frazier Page", "Tara Meixsell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Story of Ferdinand?", "answers": ["Susan J Tolchin", "W.E.B. Du Bois", "Munro Leaf", "Virgil"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Me Before You?", "answers": ["Paulo Lins", "Jojo Moyes", "Baroness Emma Orczy", "Robert Bolt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?", "answers": ["Piers Paul Read", "Roald Dahl", "Ori Brafman", "Nayantara Sahgal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fish! A Remarkable Way to Boost Morale and Improve Results?", "answers": ["Eileen Christelow", "Harry Paul", "Barbara Kingsolver", "Eric Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fish! A Remarkable Way to Boost Morale and Improve Results?", "answers": ["Stephen C. Lundin", "Jacqueline Winspear", "Reverend W. Awdry", "Paulo Lins"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Storyteller?", "answers": ["Jodi Picoult", "Lauren Billings", "Steven D. Levitt", "Bell Hooks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Outlander?", "answers": ["Jerry Hicks", "A. S. Byatt", "Patricia Highsmith", "Diana Gabaldon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Streetcar Named Desire?", "answers": ["Richard Bach", "Susan J Tolchin", "Tara Meixsell", "Tennessee Williams"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Salmon Fishing in the Yemen?", "answers": ["E. Nesbit", "Eugene H. Peterson", "Douglas Carter Beane", "Paul Torday"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Adam! where are You?: Why Most Black Men Don't Go to Church?", "answers": ["Lurlene McDaniel", "Chinua Achebe", "George Stanley", "Jawanza Kunjufu"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Story of Tracy Beaker?", "answers": ["Mark Helprin", "Jacqueline Wilson", "Florence Atwater", "Eric Idle"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anandamath?", "answers": ["Samuel Shem", "William Luther Pierce", "Bankim Chandra Chattopadhyay", "Alain LeRoy Locke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bone Collector?", "answers": ["Jeffery Deaver", "Richard Preston", "Margaret Peterson Haddix", "Eric Litwin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Big Nate: In a Class by Himself?", "answers": ["Jeffrey Probst", "Graham Greene", "Lincoln Peirce", "Chris Crutcher"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Romeo and Juliet?", "answers": ["Fran\u00e7oise Sagan", "Ram Dass", "Gregory David Roberts", "William Shakespeare"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Story of Little Black Sambo?", "answers": ["Helen Bannerman", "Gail Boushey", "John R Maslen", "George Dekker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shooter?", "answers": ["Robin Cook", "Walter Dean Myers", "Cathy Lamb", "Plato"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book American Historical Fiction?", "answers": ["Lynda Adamson", "William S. Gray", "Emily Bront\u00eb", "Abe Burrows"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book It Takes a Village?", "answers": ["Rohinton Mistry", "John F. Kennedy", "Louis de Berni\u00e8res", "Hillary Rodham Clinton"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Apology of the Augsburg Confession?", "answers": ["Helen Hunt Jackson", "Piper Kerman", "Philipp Melanchthon", "Walter Lord"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Man of the House: The Life and Political Memoirs of Speaker Tip O'Neill?", "answers": ["Horace Walpole", "Sylvia Plath", "William Novak", "James Agee"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Crazy Sexy Cancer Tips?", "answers": ["Alistair MacLean", "John R. Erickson", "Kris Carr", "Khushwant Singh"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Streamers?", "answers": ["Hugh Johnson", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco", "Allen Ginsberg", "David Rabe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bringing Up Bebe: One American Mother Discovers the Wisdom of French Parenting?", "answers": ["Emily Giffin", "Beatrice Sparks", "Pamela Druckerman", "Betty Friedan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pudd'nhead Wilson?", "answers": ["Ayaan Hirsi Ali", "Alice Schroeder", "Mark Twain", "Eduard Jose"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blood Brothers?", "answers": ["James Agee", "Charles Nordhoff", "Sapphire", "Willy Russell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Save Me the Waltz?", "answers": ["Eric Idle", "Frank Wedekind", "Daphne du Maurier", "Zelda Fitzgerald"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book City of Thieves?", "answers": ["Madeleine L'Engle", "Edward S. Herman", "David Benioff", "Beryl Markham"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Luther: The Calling?", "answers": ["Uri Shulevitz", "Neil Cross", "Ernest Hemingway", "Arundhati Roy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Three Cups of Tea?", "answers": ["David Oliver Relin", "Umberto Eco", "Alastair Fowler", "India Knight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Three Cups of Tea?", "answers": ["Ayaan Hirsi Ali", "Jennifer Weiner", "Greg Mortenson", "Wally Lamb"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Immortals of Meluha?", "answers": ["Jos\u00e9 Saramago", "Amish Tripathi", "Gertrude Chandler Warner", "Sergey Lukyanenko"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Oliver Twist?", "answers": ["Alfred Uhry", "Art Spiegelman", "Sheila Lane", "Arundhati Roy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Oliver Twist?", "answers": ["Roger Zelazny", "Lloyd D. Newell", "Curtis Sittenfeld", "Charles Dickens"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Oliver Twist?", "answers": ["Agatha Christie", "Marion Kemp", "Rainer Maria Rilke", "Mary Norton"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Their Eyes Were Watching God?", "answers": ["Zora Neale Hurston", "Edward Rutherfurd", "Pete Earley", "Beatrice Sparks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book New experiments and observations on electricity?", "answers": ["Benjamin Franklin", "Noel Streatfeild", "Marcia Brown", "H. Rider Haggard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Lesson Before Dying?", "answers": ["Anthony Powell", "Ernest J. Gaines", "James Rado", "Mary Carter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Old Maid: (The 'fifties)?", "answers": ["Yann Martel", "Ivan Turgenev", "Edith Wharton", "Philip K. Dick"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sermon on the Mount?", "answers": ["William Goldman", "A. A. Milne", "Michael Dorris", "Emmet Fox"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Boba Fett: A Practical Man?", "answers": ["Pittacus Lore", "Amos Oz", "Karen Traviss", "Jim Butcher"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Day No Pigs Would Die?", "answers": ["Wilhelm Grimm", "Christopher McDougall", "James Bradley", "Robert Newton Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Once upon a time when we were colored?", "answers": ["Joceline Sanschagrin", "Dav Pilkey", "Betty Mahmoody", "Clifton Taulbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Faerie Queene?", "answers": ["Pam Mu\u00f1oz Ryan", "Trevanian", "Lorianne Siomades", "Edmund Spenser"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Simple Abundance?", "answers": ["Donna Diamond", "Sarah Ban Breathnach", "Marco Polo", "Paul O. Zelinsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pollyanna?", "answers": ["Eleanor H. Porter", "Margaret Atwood", "Michelle Magorian", "Robert Boyle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bourne Identity?", "answers": ["Robert Ludlum", "Richard Dawkins", "Johanna Spyri", "Umberto Eco"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tom Brown's School Days?", "answers": ["John Fowles", "Thomas Hughes", "Jim Jacobs", "Friedrich Nietzsche"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lawrence of Arabia?", "answers": ["Baldassare Castiglione", "Basil Liddell Hart", "Bob Woodward", "Edward Irving Wortis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Art of Arousal?", "answers": ["Nikki Gemmell", "Fareed Zakaria", "Ruth Westheimer", "J. M. Barrie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Left Foot?", "answers": ["Kim Carpenter", "Amish Tripathi", "Christy Brown", "Richard Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Picnic?", "answers": ["Carol Gilligan", "Anthony Kiedis", "Paul Galdone", "William Inge"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rosemary's Baby?", "answers": ["Ira Levin", "Fran\u00e7oise Sagan", "Nicola Kraus", "M. Scott Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The kindness of strangers?", "answers": ["John Boswell", "Jawaharlal Nehru", "J. L. Carr", "David Sheff"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Astanga Yoga: Connect to the Core with Power Yoga?", "answers": ["Danielle Steel", "John Ajvide Lindqvist", "Audrey Niffenegger", "Liz Lark"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Frozen Turbulence in Kashmir?", "answers": ["Mao Zedong", "Cecil Frances Humphreys Alexander", "Lynn Flewelling", "Jagmohan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The C++ Programming Language?", "answers": ["Marcia Brown", "Michael Ledwidge", "Bede", "Bjarne Stroustrup"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Harriet the Spy?", "answers": ["Theodor Mommsen", "Arnold Rampersad", "Louise Fitzhugh", "Alice Munro"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gigi?", "answers": ["Robert Munsch", "Phyllis Reynolds Naylor", "Dadabhai Naoroji", "Colette"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Of Plymouth Plantation?", "answers": ["Watty Piper", "Monica Dickens", "Euripides", "William Bradford"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Eugene Onegin?", "answers": ["Aleksandr Pushkin", "Robert Sobel", "Louise Fitzhugh", "Eugene H. Peterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The BFG?", "answers": ["Johanna Spyri", "Jon Ronson", "Katie Davis", "David Wood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sahih al-Bukhari?", "answers": ["Steven McShane", "Thomas Carlyle", "Muhammad al-Bukhari", "Nicholas Sparks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Babette's Feast?", "answers": ["Anne Fine", "Victor Hugo", "Karen Blixen", "Darin Strauss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Day of Doom?", "answers": ["Lauren Weisberger", "Charlotte Perkins Gilman", "Alfred North Whitehead", "Michael Wigglesworth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cloud Atlas?", "answers": ["David Mitchell", "Eugene O'Neill", "Norman Vincent Peale", "Robert Thornton Morrison"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The luck of Roaring Camp and other short stories?", "answers": ["Bret Harte", "Robyn Carr", "Jane Taylor", "David Landay"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Glass House?", "answers": ["Jean-Dominique Bauby", "Enda Walsh", "Marcia Brown", "Sonya Hartnett"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book John Henry?", "answers": ["John Grogan", "Roark Bradford", "William Hoffer", "James Bradley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy?", "answers": ["Douglas Adams", "Philip Carlo", "Roald Dahl", "Edward Conlon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mansfield Park?", "answers": ["Victor Hugo", "Jay Asher", "Reinhold Niebuhr", "Jane Austen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gnostic Gospels: A Startling Account of the Meaning of Jesus and the Origin of Christianity Based on Gnostic Gospels and Other Secret Texts?", "answers": ["Karen Traviss", "John Locke", "Robert Harris", "Elaine Pagels"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sadako and the Thousand Paper Cranes?", "answers": ["Hugh Wheeler", "Robert Boyle", "Eleanor Coerr", "Sarah Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to Read Novels Like a Professor?", "answers": ["Richard Thaler", "Thomas C Foster", "Mohsin Hamid", "Christopher Smart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Game: Penetrating the Secret Society of Pickup Artists?", "answers": ["Neil Strauss", "Joe Masteroff", "Michael Falconer Anderson", "Joy Adamson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Which Witch??", "answers": ["Rameck Hunt", "William R. Forstchen", "Gerome Ragni", "Eva Ibbotson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book National Velvet?", "answers": ["Harriet Parker", "Enid Bagnold", "Douglas Angus", "Ivan Turgenev"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Color Purple?", "answers": ["Ellen G. White", "Desmond Barry", "George Stanley", "Alice Walker"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book David Copperfield?", "answers": ["Patrick Barlow", "Charles Dickens", "Anthony Berkeley Cox", "Jerzy Kosi\u0144ski"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Double Indemnity?", "answers": ["James M. Cain", "Ferenc Moln\u00e1r", "George Langelaan", "Johann David Wyss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Color of Water: A Black Man's Tribute to His White Mother?", "answers": ["James Hurst", "Dan Brown", "James McBride", "Anthony Berkeley Cox"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Book of the Law?", "answers": ["David Hackett Fischer", "Wendy Mass", "Douglass Wallop", "Aleister Crowley"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The unabridged devil's dictionary?", "answers": ["Simon Armitage", "Ambrose Bierce", "Jim Jacobs", "Francis Lathom"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book West Side Story?", "answers": ["James Baldwin", "Aravind Adiga", "Arthur Laurents", "James Kirkwood Jr."], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Communion?", "answers": ["Frank Lauria", "\u00c9mile Zola", "Quiara Alegr\u00eda Hudes", "Jean-Dominique Bauby"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Communion?", "answers": ["Ally Condie", "Charles Spurgeon", "Eowyn Ivey", "Whitley Strieber"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Unbearable Lightness of Being?", "answers": ["Milan Kundera", "William Martin", "Danielle Steel", "Lorraine Hansberry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shades of Gray?", "answers": ["Thomas Kyd", "Carolyn Reeder", "John Archambault", "James Howe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Frankenstein?", "answers": ["James Hurst", "Herman J. Mankiewicz", "Mary Shelley", "William Diehl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Underworld?", "answers": ["Anthony Powell", "V\u0101tsy\u0101yana", "Greg Cox", "Joe Masteroff"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Angels & Demons - Movie Tie-In: A Novel?", "answers": ["Dan Brown", "Edwin Meese", "John Maynard Smith", "William Makepeace Thackeray"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Few Good Men?", "answers": ["Trevanian", "Daniel Woodrell", "Aaron Sorkin", "Alice Schroeder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Man of La Mancha?", "answers": ["Ignatius L. Donnelly", "Langston Hughes", "Dale Wasserman", "Paulo Herique"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chita?", "answers": ["Ben Okri", "Kathryn Stockett", "Lafcadio Hearn", "Patrick O'Brian"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Prime Suspect?", "answers": ["Lynda La Plante", "Tobias Smollett", "Christopher McDougall", "Watty Piper"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Why Men Love Bitches?", "answers": ["Clement Clarke Moore", "Nick Stafford", "Michael Ledwidge", "Sherry Argov"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Labyrinth?", "answers": ["One Direction", "Vikram Seth", "James Lapine", "Kate Mosse"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A hard road to glory--basketball?", "answers": ["Adam Parfrey", "Ethel Waters", "Arthur Ashe", "Kate Mosse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Six Degrees of Separation?", "answers": ["Auguste Maquet", "L. P. Hartley", "Shel Silverstein", "John Guare"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Little Night Music?", "answers": ["Desmond Morris", "Paul Fleischman", "Taro Gomi", "Hugh Wheeler"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sideways?", "answers": ["R. Kelly Rainer", "Rex Pickett", "Bartolom\u00e9 de Las Casas", "Helen Prejean"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Turn of the Screw?", "answers": ["Merriam-Webster", "Elizabeth Barrett Browning", "D. H. Lawrence", "Henry James"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Poverty and un-British rule in India?", "answers": ["Heather Hach", "Willy Russell", "Dadabhai Naoroji", "John Dickson Carr"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Noli Me T\u00e1ngere?", "answers": ["Dennis Lehane", "Jos\u00e9 Rizal", "Jon Krakauer", "Mary Roach"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cam Jansen?", "answers": ["Henri Charri\u00e8re", "Darren Shan", "David A. Adler", "Kenneth Oppel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Children of the Corn?", "answers": ["Stephen King", "Cecil Murphey", "Zora Neale Hurston", "Truman Capote"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book War with the Newts?", "answers": ["Michael Hollinger", "Karel \u010capek", "Cecily von Ziegesar", "Joceline Sanschagrin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The kindness of strangers?", "answers": ["J. R. R. Tolkien", "Miguel \u00c1ngel Ruiz", "Katrina Kittle", "Samuel Shem"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book He's a Rebel: Phil Spector - Rock and Roll's Legendary Producer?", "answers": ["Phillip Berman", "Petrarch", "Mark Ribowsky", "Douglas Carter Beane"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Strange Fruit.?", "answers": ["Barry Reed", "David Margolick", "Jeannette Walls", "James Herbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bell Jar?", "answers": ["J. L. Carr", "Sylvia Plath", "Martin Seymour-Smith", "Richard Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sword in the Stone?", "answers": ["Sterling Archer", "Judith Krantz", "Jim Carroll", "T. H. White"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Maggot?", "answers": ["Malcolm X", "Carl Sagan", "John Fowles", "A. S. A. Harrison"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Seascape?", "answers": ["Iain Banks", "Laura Colker", "V.S. Naipaul", "Edward Albee"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Adventures of Pinocchio?", "answers": ["Taro Gomi", "Mimi Spencer", "Kamala Markandaya", "Carlo Collodi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hundred and One Dalmatians?", "answers": ["Dodie Smith", "Winston Groom", "Ntozake Shange", "Mimi Spencer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Water Is Wide?", "answers": ["Pat Conroy", "Amy Tan", "William Thomas Stead", "Nick Bakalar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Maus?", "answers": ["Jean Claverie", "Art Spiegelman", "Frank Wedekind", "Sylvia Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Balfour Declaration?", "answers": ["Arthur Balfour", "James Joyce", "Kate Christensen", "Robert Wooster"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book TransAtlantic?", "answers": ["Maya Angelou", "Michael Brandman", "Colum McCann", "Cathy Lamb"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fiddler on the Roof?", "answers": ["Joseph Stein", "J. Alison James", "Cornelia Funke", "Joseph Kesselring"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Chew?", "answers": ["Paige Turner", "The Chew", "Hal Moore", "Arthur Balfour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Chew?", "answers": ["Sherry Argov", "Daphne Oz", "Paul Galdone", "Thomas Hobbes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Chew?", "answers": ["Gordon Elliott", "Mark Twain", "George Abbott", "Shelagh Delaney"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Chew?", "answers": ["Jonathan Swift", "Doris Roettger", "Mario Batali", "Nelson George"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Chew?", "answers": ["Foster W. Cline", "William Thomas Stead", "Mike Leigh", "Michael Symon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Chew?", "answers": ["Ezra Jack Keats", "John of Patmos", "Clinton Kelly", "Jeremy Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Chew?", "answers": ["Carla Hall", "Carlo Collodi", "Khalil Gibran", "John Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Every cloud has a silver lining?", "answers": ["Ian Serraillier", "Jeannie Gunn", "Kazuo Ishiguro", "Anne Mazer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Chronicles of Riddick?", "answers": ["Tennessee Williams", "Laura Colker", "Alan Dean Foster", "Conrad Ferdinand Meyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Diary of a Wimpy Kid: The Last Straw?", "answers": ["Jeff Kinney", "Eben Alexander", "Mary Doria Russell", "A. S. Byatt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Caps for Sale?", "answers": ["Esphyr Slobodkina", "Farhat Ishtiaq", "David Mamet", "Kathryn Erskine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Godspell?", "answers": ["John-Michael Tebelak", "Ethel Lina White", "Lafcadio Hearn", "John Hersey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ghost?", "answers": ["Don Brown", "Booker T. Washington", "Harvey Schmidt", "Robert Harris"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ghost?", "answers": ["Eve Bunting", "Peter Benchley", "E. Nesbit", "Mary Norton"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Guinness World Records 2013?", "answers": ["Guinness World Records", "David Wood", "Sebastian Junger", "Abba Eban"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Poor Richard's Almanack?", "answers": ["Hermann Hesse", "Clinton Kelly", "Benjamin Franklin", "Don Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Doctor Zhivago?", "answers": ["Boris Pasternak", "Denis Diderot", "Edgar Allan Poe", "Kris Carr"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mein Kampf?", "answers": ["Lewis Carroll", "Adolf Hitler", "Mark Ortman", "Polly Adler"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Doctor Faustus?", "answers": ["James Kirkwood Jr.", "Pearl Poet", "John Galsworthy", "Christopher Marlowe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peg Woffington?", "answers": ["Michael Brandman", "Francis Chan", "Bede", "Charles Reade"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book What Katy Did?", "answers": ["Jack London", "Jean Anouilh", "Belva Plain", "Sarah Chauncey Woolsey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Motherless Child?", "answers": ["Neil Cross", "Glen Hirshberg", "Ned Vizzini", "Deborah Chiel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Steve Jobs?", "answers": ["Walter Isaacson", "Kathleen Grissom", "David Mamet", "Kevin Carroll"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book War and Peace?", "answers": ["Rameck Hunt", "Allan Folsom", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel", "Leo Tolstoy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Northern Lights?", "answers": ["Daniel Woodrell", "Lincoln Child", "Nick Hornby", "Philip Pullman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Room?", "answers": ["Kathleen Grissom", "Helen Hunt Jackson", "Richard Peck", "Emma Donoghue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Three Men in a Boat?", "answers": ["Deja King", "Stieg Larsson", "Ethan Hawke", "Jerome K. Jerome"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Practical Magic?", "answers": ["Michael Frayn", "Robert Reich", "Karma-glin\u0307-pa", "Alice Hoffman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The old maid?", "answers": ["John Cleland", "Edith Wharton", "William Gibson", "Desiderius Erasmus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ashram?", "answers": ["Ashley Gardner", "Sattar Memon", "Joy Adamson", "Daniel Goleman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cat on a Hot Tin Roof?", "answers": ["Simon Dunstan", "Tennessee Williams", "Robert Graves", "Ethel Turner"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Writer of the Purple Rage?", "answers": ["Stephen Hawking", "Thor Heyerdahl", "John Coleman Burroughs", "Joe R. Lansdale"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The House of the Seven Gables?", "answers": ["Christopher Smart", "Arthur Miller", "Nathaniel Hawthorne", "Jeffrey Probst"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Red Dog?", "answers": ["Alexandra Ripley", "Watty Piper", "Simon Armitage", "Louis de Berni\u00e8res"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bomb: The Race to Build--and Steal--the World's Most Dangerous Weapon?", "answers": ["Christy Brown", "Phoebe Atwood Taylor", "Steve Sheinkin", "Carl Linnaeus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stone Fox?", "answers": ["Rodman Philbrick", "John Reynolds Gardiner", "William Makepeace Thackeray", "Patrick Ness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shirley Jones: A Memoir?", "answers": ["Robert Wooster", "Shirley Jones", "Jerome K. Jerome", "John van de Ruit"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Prince and the Pauper?", "answers": ["Mark Twain", "Joy Adamson", "Sue Grafton", "Else Holmelund Minarik"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Hunger Artist?", "answers": ["Franz Kafka", "Eudora Welty", "William Makepeace Thackeray", "Michelle Knudsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nothing But the Truth?", "answers": ["Edward Irving Wortis", "Sylvia Plath", "Mark Ortman", "R. Kelly Rainer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Thunderstruck?", "answers": ["Sara Corbett", "Billie Letts", "Erik Larson", "Eric L. Haney"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blue skies?", "answers": ["Maggie Stiefvater", "Robyn Carr", "Adam Parfrey", "Hal Moore"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dimboola?", "answers": ["Jack Hibberd", "Friedrich Engels", "Jack Weinstock", "John Fowles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mother India?", "answers": ["Barbara A. Shapiro", "Katherine Mayo", "William Thomas Stead", "Jeanne DuPrau"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Dog's Life: The Autobiography of a Stray?", "answers": ["Amiri Baraka", "Terry Bisson", "Ann M. Martin", "Gerome Ragni"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rebus - Three Great Novels?", "answers": ["Ian Rankin", "Li Cunxin", "Margaret Peterson Haddix", "Yasmina Khadra"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Moonfleet?", "answers": ["Jan Ormerod", "J. Meade Falkner", "Dalton Trumbo", "Gerome Ragni"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peter and the Starcatchers?", "answers": ["Dave Barry", "Eileen Christelow", "Jawaharlal Nehru", "Bernard Lewis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peter and the Starcatchers?", "answers": ["Norman Vincent Peale", "Ridley Pearson", "Christopher Paul Curtis", "Elias Chacour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shahnama?", "answers": ["Robert Hillenbrand", "Loretta Lynn", "Clive King", "John Dos Passos"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Island of the Blue Dolphins?", "answers": ["Hunter S. Thompson", "Scott O'Dell", "Mary Robinette Kowal", "Dyan Sheldon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Less Than Zero?", "answers": ["Bret Easton Ellis", "Theodore Taylor", "Emmet Fox", "Sarah Chauncey Woolsey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Clash of Civilizations and the Remaking of World Order?", "answers": ["Samuel P. Huntington", "Sarah Kane", "James Jones", "M. L. Stedman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jaws?", "answers": ["John Knowles", "Peter Benchley", "Dave Barry", "Ken Blanchard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Demonology?", "answers": ["Anthony Powell", "Rick Moody", "Eileen Christelow", "Dav Pilkey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Adventures of Tom Sawyer?", "answers": ["Mark Twain", "Margaret Stohl", "Nicholas Dante", "Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pygmalion?", "answers": ["Marshall Brickman", "David Lindsay-Abaire", "George Bernard Shaw", "Judah the Prince"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Amphitryon?", "answers": ["Libba Bray", "Plautus", "Stephen Kendrick", "Isabel Allende"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Green Eggs and Ham?", "answers": ["Dr. Seuss", "Hunter S. Thompson", "Barbara Hambly", "Jeffery Deaver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Perfect Stranger?", "answers": ["Neil Cross", "Alice Sebold", "Ben Carson", "Danielle Steel"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book His Family?", "answers": ["Marjorie W. Sharmat", "Alice Munro", "Ernest Poole", "Ernest Cline"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hollow Men?", "answers": ["Nicky Hager", "Arthur Balfour", "Jim Carroll", "Helen Keller"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Rose for Emily?", "answers": ["William Faulkner", "Muhammad al-Bukhari", "Aeschylus", "Aravind Adiga"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Westing Game?", "answers": ["C. Everard Palmer", "Robert Lindner", "Jean Anouilh", "Ellen Raskin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Shadow of the Wind?", "answers": ["Carlos Ruiz Zaf\u00f3n", "Ren\u00e9e Mauborgne", "Jacques Rupnik", "Charles W. Chesnutt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Old MacDonald Had a Farm?", "answers": ["Jacques Rupnik", "Steven D. Levitt", "James Dickey", "Mike Resnick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Necklace?", "answers": ["Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg", "Eowyn Ivey", "Horace Silver", "Guy de Maupassant"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Equus?", "answers": ["Fu Xi", "Helen Fielding", "Peter Shaffer", "Dean Hughes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rikki-Tikki-Tavi?", "answers": ["Kim Barnouin", "Herman J. Mankiewicz", "Rudyard Kipling", "\u015a\u016bdraka"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sound of Music?", "answers": ["Dean Koontz", "Truman Capote", "Russel Crouse", "Lawrence Kimbrough"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sound of Music?", "answers": ["Fritjof Capra", "Ian Rankin", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel", "Howard Lindsay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The angry American?", "answers": ["John Howard Griffin", "Patricia Highsmith", "Stephen J. Dubner", "Susan J Tolchin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Left Behind?", "answers": ["Ernest Poole", "Jerry B. Jenkins", "Christopher Hampton", "Lionel Bart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Left Behind?", "answers": ["Alan Jay Lerner", "Tim LaHaye", "Bob Fosse", "Danielle Steel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Swiftly Tilting Planet?", "answers": ["Alice Hoffman", "Madeleine L'Engle", "George Orwell", "Tim Tharp"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shrek!?", "answers": ["Steve Eng", "Winnie Holzman", "Adrian Martin", "William Steig"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Phantom of the Opera?", "answers": ["Tatiana De Rosnay", "Gaston Leroux", "Julie Smith", "Bob Goff"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book House of Cards?", "answers": ["Berry Gordy", "Harry Mazer", "Michael Dobbs", "Samuel P. Huntington"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shutter Island?", "answers": ["Dennis Lehane", "Sharon Creech", "Christopher Hitchens", "Rainer Maria Rilke"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Tale of Two Cities?", "answers": ["Daniel H. Pink", "Stephen Fishman", "Trey Parker", "Charles Dickens"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Midnight Sun?", "answers": ["Stephenie Meyer", "Ford Madox Ford", "Michael Chabon", "Augustine of Hippo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Miracle Worker?", "answers": ["Rajendra Prasad", "Jane Green", "Jess Walter", "William Gibson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Great Modern Short Stories?", "answers": ["Margaret Atwood", "Bennett Cerf", "Ransom Riggs", "Jeannie Gunn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Young Frankenstein?", "answers": ["Nikolai Gogol", "Thomas Meehan", "Steven McShane", "Daniel Defoe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Young Frankenstein?", "answers": ["Noam Chomsky", "Lorraine Hansberry", "Doug Naylor", "Mel Brooks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book All My Sons?", "answers": ["V. C. Andrews", "Pamela Druckerman", "Arthur Miller", "Reza Aslan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Way of Pilgrim&pil Contn?", "answers": ["Robert Reich", "W. Wilkins", "R.M. French", "John Grogan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book H. P. Lovecraft bibliography?", "answers": ["Lawrence Hill", "Robert Bolt", "Eric Suben", "H. P. Lovecraft"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Book of Wisdom?", "answers": ["Margret Rey", "Whitney Stewart", "Solomon", "Helen Fielding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book First Blood?", "answers": ["Jawanza Kunjufu", "David Morrell", "Nicholas Evans", "Pope Paul VI"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Loretta Lynn: Coal miner's daughter?", "answers": ["George Vecsey", "Beverly Lewis", "P. C. Wren", "Marian Keyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Loretta Lynn: Coal miner's daughter?", "answers": ["Loretta Lynn", "J. M. Barrie", "Ronald David Laing", "Federico Garc\u00eda Lorca"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Black Cat?", "answers": ["Joyce Lankester Brisley", "Melina Marchetta", "Edgar Allan Poe", "James Alexander Thom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tale of Genji?", "answers": ["Murasaki Shikibu", "Bimal Jalan", "Nicholas D. Kristof", "Pope Paul VI"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Histories?", "answers": ["Michael Connelly", "Mark Halperin", "Herodotus", "Amanda Lindhout"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lord of the Flies?", "answers": ["J. C. Holt", "Vanessa Diffenbaugh", "William Golding", "Alice Hoffman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lion King?", "answers": ["Doris Pilkington Garimara", "Irene Mecchi", "Ellen Raskin", "Theodor Mommsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lion King?", "answers": ["Raj\u0101\u02bc \u02bbAbd All\u0101h \u1e62\u0101ni\u02bb", "Sophocles", "Irvine Welsh", "Roger Allers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Eiger Sanction?", "answers": ["Paulo Lins", "Trevanian", "Michael Hollinger", "Richard Linklater"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sea Stories?", "answers": ["Ray Bradbury", "Margaret Elphinstone", "Joseph Robinette", "Jacqueline Winspear"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sea Stories?", "answers": ["A. C. H. Smith", "Desmond Barry", "Sol Yurick", "Clifford Odets"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Reluctant Fundamentalist?", "answers": ["Patrick Dennis", "Mohsin Hamid", "Elin Hilderbrand", "William Stobbs"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Life of Pi?", "answers": ["Larry Watson", "Scott O'Dell", "Ignatius L. Donnelly", "Yann Martel"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest?", "answers": ["Michael Ondaatje", "Frank Wedekind", "Ken Kesey", "Michel Faber"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Frog and Toad are Friends?", "answers": ["Arnold Lobel", "John Milton", "Arundhati Roy", "Anthony Berkeley Cox"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Little Women?", "answers": ["Allan Knee", "Toni Morrison", "W. H. Auden", "Joseph Robinette"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Little Women?", "answers": ["C. S. Godshalk", "Scott Smith", "Hal Moore", "Louisa May Alcott"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Fast Metabolism Diet?", "answers": ["David Wood", "Eve Adamson", "Betty Friedan", "Martin Amis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Fast Metabolism Diet?", "answers": ["Sue Grafton", "Arthur Laurents", "Joseph Gibaldi", "Haylie Pomroy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Of Mice and Men?", "answers": ["Arthur Hailey", "Alan Brennert", "John Steinbeck", "Marion Kemp"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Don Quixote?", "answers": ["Bobby Lynn Maslen", "Gertrude Jekyll", "Haruki Murakami", "Miguel de Cervantes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Safe Haven?", "answers": ["Ouida", "Robert Ruark", "Mark Ortman", "Nicholas Sparks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ragtime?", "answers": ["John Adams", "Kurt Vonnegut", "Laurie Halse Anderson", "Terrence McNally"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Secret History?", "answers": ["Donna Tartt", "Eve Adamson", "Poppy Z. Brite", "Richard Henry Horne"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book What a Wonderful World?", "answers": ["Guy Bolton", "Bob Thiele", "Robert Munsch", "Honor\u00e9 de Balzac"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Other Boleyn Girl?", "answers": ["Rameck Hunt", "Philippa Gregory", "Patricia Cornwell", "Amos Oz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Satanic Bible?", "answers": ["Kathleen Grissom", "Anton LaVey", "Lorianne Siomades", "Jostein Gaarder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Perry Mason: Seven Complete Novels?", "answers": ["Mary Roach", "Erle Stanley Gardner", "Homer", "George Harrison"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Principia Mathematica?", "answers": ["Eddi Fiegel", "Bertrand Russell", "William Golding", "Eugene O'Neill"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Principia Mathematica?", "answers": ["Iris Murdoch", "Beatrice Sparks", "Alfred North Whitehead", "Walter Lord"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sex and the City?", "answers": ["Douglas Adams", "Tony Blair", "Rainer Maria Rilke", "Candace Bushnell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Winter's Tale?", "answers": ["Mary Lewis Wang", "Marilyn Diamond", "Abul Kalam Azad", "Mark Helprin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Virgin Suicides?", "answers": ["Philip Caputo", "Jeffrey Eugenides", "Glen Berger", "Sandra Gilbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Idiot?", "answers": ["Joyce Lankester Brisley", "Jim Jacobs", "Katrina Kittle", "Fyodor Dostoyevsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Little Shop of Horrors?", "answers": ["Danae Yankoski", "John Clare", "Brad Thor", "Howard Ashman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The History of the Standard Oil Company?", "answers": ["Joanne Greenberg", "Loretta Lynn", "Kris Carr", "Ida Tarbell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book America the Beautiful: Rediscovering What Made This Nation Great?", "answers": ["J. L. Carr", "Margaret Edson", "Herb Gardner", "Ben Carson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Paul Scott?", "answers": ["Herman Melville", "Anthony Swofford", "Hilary Spurling", "John F. Kennedy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Nose?", "answers": ["Thomas C. Holt", "Darren Shan", "Donna Tartt", "Nikolai Gogol"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The 100 Most Influential Books Ever Written?", "answers": ["Shashi Tharoor", "Khalil Gibran", "Martin Seymour-Smith", "James Madison"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rabbit Is Rich?", "answers": ["Charles Webb", "Jon Scieszka", "John Updike", "Bret Witter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Manchurian Candidate?", "answers": ["Arthur Hailey", "Richard Condon", "Elin Hilderbrand", "Dennis Wainstock"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Put a Spell on You?", "answers": ["Ken Kesey", "Nina Simone", "Linda Woolverton", "Jacqueline Winspear"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Zelda?", "answers": ["Ben Mezrich", "Edmund Cooper", "Nancy Milford", "Charles Portis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sophie's World?", "answers": ["James Boswell", "Mary Carter", "Tholkappiar", "Jostein Gaarder"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Computer Architecture: A Quantitative Approach?", "answers": ["John L. Hennessy", "James Fenimore Cooper", "William Bradford", "George MacDonald Fraser"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Computer Architecture: A Quantitative Approach?", "answers": ["David Patterson", "Gordon Elliott", "Thomas More", "Robert R. Livingston"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Aeneid?", "answers": ["Virgil", "Tobias Wolff", "Jonathan Cahn", "Judy Blume"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Naked Ape?", "answers": ["Ford Madox Ford", "Daphne du Maurier", "Desmond Morris", "Saki"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Halo: The Fall of Reach?", "answers": ["Lincoln Child", "Francine Rivers", "J. M. Barrie", "Eric S. Nylund"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Martian Chronicles?", "answers": ["Halima Bashir", "Mike Resnick", "Jason Matthews", "Ray Bradbury"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Crank?", "answers": ["Ellen Hopkins", "Khaled Hosseini", "Niklaus Wirth", "Daniel Quinn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pather Panchali?", "answers": ["Bibhutibhushan Bandopadhyay", "Helen Keller", "Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa", "Brad Thor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Intimate Adventures of a London Call Girl?", "answers": ["Harold Bell Wright", "Peter Rinearson", "Edward Gibbon", "Belle de Jour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Girl Who Owned a City?", "answers": ["David Treuer", "O. T Nelson", "David Almond", "James Norman Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book On Becoming Baby Wise?", "answers": ["Richard Peck", "Arthur Conan Doyle", "Oliver Goldsmith", "Gary Ezzo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Things Fall Apart?", "answers": ["Michael Flatley", "Tom Stoppard", "Chinua Achebe", "Herman Melville"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book On the origin of species by means of natural selection?", "answers": ["Charles Darwin", "Karel \u010capek", "Gabriel Garc\u00eda M\u00e1rquez", "Sylvain Reynard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Invention of Hugo Cabret?", "answers": ["Anna Dewdney", "Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa", "Brian Selznick", "William F. Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gypsy: A Musical Fable?", "answers": ["Arthur Laurents", "Marge Piercy", "Louise Fitzhugh", "Greg Mortenson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Remember Me??", "answers": ["Rameck Hunt", "Haruki Murakami", "Sophie Kinsella", "Thomas J. Stanley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Mill on the Floss?", "answers": ["Mary Higgins Clark", "Louis Fischer", "Douglas Carter Beane", "George Eliot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The skin I'm in?", "answers": ["William Styron", "Sharon Flake", "Dyan Sheldon", "Miguel \u00c1ngel Ruiz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Untouchable?", "answers": ["Christopher McDougall", "Amy Vanderbilt", "Mulk Raj Anand", "Eric Suben"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Vivian Grey?", "answers": ["Simone Elkeles", "C. Everard Palmer", "Benjamin Disraeli", "Jim Gaffigan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Les Femmes Savantes?", "answers": ["Moli\u00e8re", "Steven McShane", "Piers Paul Read", "Euripides"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Let Go and Let God: Steps in Victorious Living?", "answers": ["Albert E Cliffe", "Cornelius Ryan", "James Frey", "Mary Claire Helldorfer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book For Want of a Nail?", "answers": ["Robert Sobel", "MacKinlay Kantor", "Rex Pickett", "William Makepeace Thackeray"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Million Little Pieces?", "answers": ["Roger Sherman", "Paul Howard", "James Frey", "Sun Tzu"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Commitments?", "answers": ["Natalie Babbitt", "Geraldine Brooks", "Sebastian Junger", "Roddy Doyle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cityboy: 50 Ways to Survive the Crunch?", "answers": ["Geraint Anderson", "Giovanni Boccaccio", "Larry Sloman", "Lynn Sherr"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lark Rise to Candleford. Trilogy?", "answers": ["Flora Thompson", "Arthur Ransome", "Basil Copper", "John F. Kennedy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Go Tell It on the Mountain?", "answers": ["Malcolm X", "Mahatma Gandhi", "John Reynolds Gardiner", "James Baldwin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book World's End?", "answers": ["T. Coraghessan Boyle", "John Bradshaw", "Reinhold Niebuhr", "Sigmund Freud"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Crying of Lot 49?", "answers": ["Thomas Pynchon", "Robert Boyle", "Franklin Lacey", "Jon Scieszka"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Owl and the Pussycat?", "answers": ["John Keir Cross", "Pierre Choderlos de Laclos", "Maya Angelou", "Doreen Cronin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Owl and the Pussycat?", "answers": ["Edward Lear", "Rumiko Takahashi", "Sally Morgan", "Winston Groom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The End of America: Letter of Warning to a Young Patriot?", "answers": ["Naomi Wolf", "Douglas Adams", "Bell Hooks", "Henry Bellamann"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Last Song?", "answers": ["Dianne Watkins Stuart", "Cathy Lamb", "Nicholas Sparks", "Robert Bloch"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book There Was an Old Lady Who Swallowed a Fly?", "answers": ["Rodman Philbrick", "Joshua Sobol", "Sun Tzu", "Simms Taback"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lord of the Rings?", "answers": ["Rajendra Prasad", "J. R. R. Tolkien", "Emily Bront\u00eb", "Astrid Lindgren"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Road Less Travelled?", "answers": ["Milan Kundera", "M. Scott Peck", "Peter S. Beagle", "Christopher McDougall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Theogony?", "answers": ["Robert Greene", "Amartya Sen", "Arnold Lobel", "Hesiod"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Handmaid's Tale?", "answers": ["Margaret Atwood", "Richard Hakluyt", "Ram Dass", "Christopher Hitchens"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Raymond Briggs' The snowman?", "answers": ["P. D. James", "Mark Haddon", "Michelle Knudsen", "Michael Rosen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Raymond Briggs' The snowman?", "answers": ["Sara Corbett", "Raymond Briggs", "John Wyndham", "David Icke"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bridge?", "answers": ["Iain Banks", "Allen Ginsberg", "Jeff Whitty", "Arna Bontemps"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Game: Penetrating the Secret Society of Pickup Artists?", "answers": ["Dean Koontz", "Neil Strauss", "Stephanie Stuve-Bodeen", "Betty Friedan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sahih Muslim?", "answers": ["Booker T. Washington", "Heinrich B\u00f6ll", "Muslim ibn al-Hajjaj", "Kathleen Grissom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book \"Kevin Trudeau's Free Money \"\"they\"\" Don't Want You to Know about\"?", "answers": ["Katrina Kittle", "Ravinder Singh", "Richard Nelson", "Kevin Trudeau"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Under the Volcano?", "answers": ["Malcolm Lowry", "Rosa Parks", "Ethel Waters", "Mary Shelley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book All Fools' Day?", "answers": ["Carla Hall", "Edmund Cooper", "Danny Wallace", "Sloan Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Luke Short: A Biography?", "answers": ["Wayne Short", "Rory Freedman", "Dorothy B. Hughes", "Rosa Parks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Catching Fire?", "answers": ["Ida Tarbell", "Eric Suben", "Jay Thompson", "Suzanne Collins"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Spring Awakening?", "answers": ["Ori Brafman", "Emma Donoghue", "Danielle Steel", "Frank Wedekind"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cloud Nine?", "answers": ["Dinabandhu Mitra", "Chaim Potok", "Curtis Sittenfeld", "Caryl Churchill"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ross O'Carroll-Kelly?", "answers": ["Debbie Macomber", "Isaac Marion", "Paul Howard", "Jack Higgins"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Beach?", "answers": ["Jeffrey Zaslow", "Roger Lancelyn Green", "Dale Wasserman", "Alex Garland"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kisses from Katie: A Story of Relentless Love and Redemption?", "answers": ["Katie Davis", "Muslim ibn al-Hajjaj", "Peter Spier", "Robert Edwin Lee"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bluest Eye?", "answers": ["Toni Morrison", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel", "Ida Tarbell", "Charles Spurgeon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Grendel?", "answers": ["Francesca Simon", "John Gardner", "P. G. Wodehouse", "Chris Van Allsburg"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Glass House?", "answers": ["Michael Flatley", "Tatiana De Rosnay", "Wil Haygood", "Ashley Gardner"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Castle?", "answers": ["Ruta Sepetys", "Harold Bell Wright", "Malcolm Pasley", "Jay Thompson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Castle?", "answers": ["Franz Kafka", "Tony Blair", "Gary D. Chapman", "Jacqueline Susann"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Love Story?", "answers": ["Terrance Dicks", "Jon Krakauer", "Erich Segal", "Charles Perrault"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book King Arthur and his Knights of the Round Table?", "answers": ["Roger Lancelyn Green", "Erich Segal", "Corrie ten Boom", "Ian Fleming"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Not without my daughter?", "answers": ["William Hoffer", "Guy Bolton", "John Maynard Smith", "Mourning Dove"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Not without my daughter?", "answers": ["Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry", "Betty Mahmoody", "Wilbur A. Smith", "Michael Flatley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Witches?", "answers": ["Janet Stevens", "Tom Perrotta", "John Howard Griffin", "Roald Dahl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Seagull?", "answers": ["J. C. Holt", "Gregory David Roberts", "Christopher McDougall", "Anton Chekhov"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Female Eunuch?", "answers": ["Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg", "Joceline Sanschagrin", "J. Alison James", "Germaine Greer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dead Man Walking?", "answers": ["Francis Lathom", "Helen Prejean", "Jeff Kinney", "Carlos Ruiz Zaf\u00f3n"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beautiful Disaster?", "answers": ["Mario Batali", "M. Scott Peck", "Ron Powers", "Jamie McGuire"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Goodnight Mister Tom?", "answers": ["Michael Falconer Anderson", "Mary Kay Andrews", "Michelle Magorian", "Jane Hamilton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Personal witness?", "answers": ["Abba Eban", "Cormac McCarthy", "Ransom Riggs", "Nancy Farmer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Electra?", "answers": ["P. C. Wren", "Sigmund Freud", "John Clare", "Sophocles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hours?", "answers": ["Solomon", "Manu (Lawgiver)", "Ellen Hopkins", "Michael Cunningham"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Adam Bede?", "answers": ["Richmal Crompton", "George Eliot", "Ray Russell", "A. P. J. Abdul Kalam"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Millionaire Next Door: The Surprising Secrets of America's Wealthy?", "answers": ["Thomas J. Stanley", "Sandra Cisneros", "Khushwant Singh", "Foster W. Cline"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Watership Down?", "answers": ["Patricia Cornwell", "Tom Wolfe", "Harry Allard", "Richard Adams"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle?", "answers": ["Robert Barnard", "Amanda Brown", "Bob Mayer", "Edward Irving Wortis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Art Forger?", "answers": ["Dennis Lehane", "Fred Ebb", "Barbara A. Shapiro", "Thomas C. Holt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to write science fiction?", "answers": ["Allan Knee", "Prentice Mulford", "Sebastian Junger", "Matthew J. Costello"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Watsons Go to Birmingham \u2013 1963?", "answers": ["Boris Pasternak", "No\u00ebl Coward", "Christopher Paul Curtis", "Whitney Stewart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hugh Walpole?", "answers": ["R. J. Palacio", "Howard Pyle", "Rupert Hart-Davis", "Irene Mecchi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Queen Zixi of Ix?", "answers": ["David Foster Wallace", "L. Frank Baum", "Jayne Ann Krentz", "Bell Hooks"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shall I compare thee to a summer's day??", "answers": ["Rameck Hunt", "Sterling Archer", "Eleanor Coerr", "William Shakespeare"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book One Hundred Years of Solitude?", "answers": ["W. C. Heinz", "Gabriel Garc\u00eda M\u00e1rquez", "John F. Kennedy", "Boris Pasternak"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Purple Hibiscus?", "answers": ["Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie", "Mickey Rapkin", "Darin Strauss", "Alex Garland"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Night to Remember?", "answers": ["Helen Hunt Jackson", "Edmond Rostand", "Walter Lord", "Aldo Leopold"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Red Badge of Courage?", "answers": ["Cormac McCarthy", "John Coleman Burroughs", "Enid Blyton", "Stephen Crane"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How far we slaves have come!?", "answers": ["Percy Bysshe Shelley", "George MacDonald Fraser", "Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa", "Fidel Castro"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How far we slaves have come!?", "answers": ["John Dempsey", "Nelson Mandela", "John R Maslen", "E. D. Baker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gracias a la Vida?", "answers": ["Evelyn Waugh", "Phillip Berman", "Thornton Wilder", "Kyle Onstott"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Awakening?", "answers": ["Perseus Books Group", "Bert V. Royal", "Kate Chopin", "Richard Linklater"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The White Man's Burden?", "answers": ["Rudyard Kipling", "Gregory Maguire", "Marjorie W. Sharmat", "S. A. Bodeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tibetan Book Of The Dead: The Great Liberation Through Hearing In The Bardo?", "answers": ["Tobias Smollett", "Paramahansa Yogananda", "Francesca Fremantle", "Wilbur A. Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Compound?", "answers": ["Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry", "Reza Aslan", "Shirley Jones", "S. A. Bodeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Compound?", "answers": ["James Weldon Johnson", "Stephanie Stuve-Bodeen", "Muhammad al-Bukhari", "Jean M. Auel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Spud?", "answers": ["John van de Ruit", "Loretta Lynn", "Beverly Lewis", "Polly Adler"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Glass Castle?", "answers": ["Jeannette Walls", "Halima Bashir", "Thor Heyerdahl", "Robert Goolrick"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Law of Attraction?", "answers": ["Susan J Tolchin", "Napoleon Hill", "Christopher Hampton", "John Jakes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Law of Attraction?", "answers": ["Carla Hall", "Prentice Mulford", "P. G. Wodehouse", "Florence Nightingale"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Law of Attraction?", "answers": ["Jennifer Weiner", "Erin Morgenstern", "Wallace Wattles", "Kinky Friedman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Percy Jackson and the Olympians 5-book Boxed Set?", "answers": ["Leo Tolstoy", "Rick Riordan", "Jack Hibberd", "Richard Gravil"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Humsafar?", "answers": ["Lisa Genova", "Jason Gehlert", "Farhat Ishtiaq", "Thor Muller"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book MLA Style Manual?", "answers": ["Lauren Kate", "Edmund White", "Jonathan Swift", "Joseph Gibaldi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The rainbow fish?", "answers": ["Allen C. Guelzo", "Caldwell Esselstyn", "Roger Allers", "J. Alison James"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Butler: A Witness to History?", "answers": ["Wil Haygood", "Michelle Alexander", "Nayantara Sahgal", "Jerry Hicks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In Search of Lost Time?", "answers": ["Paul Howard", "Jean-Dominique Bauby", "Marcel Proust", "Terry Bisson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Out of My Mind?", "answers": ["Stella Gibbons", "Sharon Draper", "Leon Uris", "R.M. French"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Casual Vacancy?", "answers": ["J. K. Rowling", "Bob Dylan", "Anita Diamant", "Harriet Beecher Stowe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fallen?", "answers": ["Clifford Sawhney", "Michael Camille", "Lauren Kate", "Eleanor Hibbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Couples?", "answers": ["Jim Gaffigan", "John Updike", "Erich von D\u00e4niken", "Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book What Dreams May Come?", "answers": ["E. L. Doctorow", "E. M. Forster", "Robert Graves", "Richard Matheson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bug?", "answers": ["Willy Russell", "A. E. Housman", "Dr. Seuss", "Tracy Letts"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Who Moved My Cheese? An Amazing Way to Deal with Change in Your Work and in Your Life?", "answers": ["William Stobbs", "Lisa Genova", "Spencer Johnson", "Robert Newton Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book ParaNorman: A Novel?", "answers": ["David Wong", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel", "Eowyn Ivey", "Eugene O'Neill"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chains?", "answers": ["Alex Garland", "Steve Sullivan", "Laurie Halse Anderson", "Sigmund Freud"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Goldilocks and the Three Bears?", "answers": ["James Marshall", "Robert Harling", "Robert Falls", "Ashley Gardner"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Heart Is a Lonely Hunter?", "answers": ["Liz Tuccillo", "Mikhail Lermontov", "Carson McCullers", "Malorie Blackman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Herding Cats: A Life in Politics?", "answers": ["Carlo Collodi", "Debbie Macomber", "Ferenc Moln\u00e1r", "Trent Lott"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bonjour Tristesse?", "answers": ["Robert Southey", "Michelle Magorian", "Norman Vincent Peale", "Fran\u00e7oise Sagan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hindu Gods and Goddesses?", "answers": ["W. Wilkins", "Abba Eban", "Margaret Elphinstone", "Simon Armitage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Black Swan: The Impact of the Highly Improbable?", "answers": ["Stephen Hawking", "Diana Hacker", "Nassim Nicholas Taleb", "Henry Williamson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rainbow Serpent?", "answers": ["Vladimir Vladimirovich Nabokov", "John Steinbeck", "Foster W. Cline", "Dick Roughsey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Call of the Wild?", "answers": ["Stendhal", "William Saroyan", "Jack London", "Ethel Lina White"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Scandal in Belgravia?", "answers": ["Robert Barnard", "Philip Pullman", "Elaine Pagels", "Ken Kesey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Iceman Cometh?", "answers": ["Sarah Dessen", "Irving Shulman", "Eugene O'Neill", "William Manchester"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Roses Are Red?", "answers": ["Richard Blackaby", "David Weber", "Enid Blyton", "James Patterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The elves and the shoemaker?", "answers": ["Jeffrey Probst", "Eric Suben", "Patrick Rothfuss", "Craig Thomas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In a Lonely Place?", "answers": ["Marianne Williamson", "Dorothy B. Hughes", "Mario Batali", "Kingsley Amis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Souls of Black Folk?", "answers": ["Andy McNab", "James Fenimore Cooper", "Phoebe Atwood Taylor", "W.E.B. Du Bois"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Hero of Our Time?", "answers": ["Wendelin Van Draanen", "Mikhail Lermontov", "Rebecca Skloot", "Dmitry Glukhovsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Austenland?", "answers": ["Raymond Chandler", "John Caird", "Shannon Hale", "Dalton Trumbo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chronicle of a Death Foretold?", "answers": ["Ayn Rand", "Tyler Perry", "Gabriel Garc\u00eda M\u00e1rquez", "Robert Holden"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Death of the Author?", "answers": ["Alice Munro", "Cameron Crowe", "Roland Barthes", "Mary Shelley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Soldier Boys?", "answers": ["Dean Hughes", "Douglas Adams", "James Frey", "Owen Wister"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Matched?", "answers": ["Katherine Paterson", "Melvin Belli", "Ally Condie", "Frank Wedekind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book We're Going on a Bear Hunt?", "answers": ["Michael Rosen", "Sterling Archer", "Clifford Sawhney", "Ron Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jews and Words?", "answers": ["Roark Bradford", "William Howard Armstrong", "Amos Oz", "Thomas Hardy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Evita?", "answers": ["Mary Wollstonecraft", "Tim Rice", "John Reynolds Gardiner", "Marcus Luttrell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Guys and Dolls?", "answers": ["John Locke", "Miguel de Cervantes", "Henry Blackaby", "Jo Swerling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Guys and Dolls?", "answers": ["Moli\u00e8re", "Euclid", "Kaui Hart Hemmings", "Abe Burrows"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Clear and Present Danger?", "answers": ["Simon Armitage", "John Locke", "Chinua Achebe", "Tom Clancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fit for Life?", "answers": ["Zo\u00eb Heller", "Marilyn Diamond", "Ayaan Hirsi Ali", "Jerome Lawrence"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Empty Mansions: The Mysterious Life of Huguette Clark and the Spending of a Great American Fortune?", "answers": ["Elizabeth George Speare", "George Bernard Shaw", "Bill Dedman", "Sarah Chauncey Woolsey"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shantaram?", "answers": ["David Henry Hwang", "Richard O'Brien", "Gregory David Roberts", "Rachel Renee Russell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Creative Curriculum?", "answers": ["Diane Trister. Dodge", "Jhumpa Lahiri", "Edmond Rostand", "Thomas Pynchon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Creative Curriculum?", "answers": ["Fania Oz-Salzberger", "Laura Colker", "Maggie Stiefvater", "Robert Greene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Go Dog Go?", "answers": ["P. D. Eastman", "Bell Hooks", "John Cleland", "Susan Sontag"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jane Eyre?", "answers": ["Richard Peck", "Helen Fielding", "Mark Ortman", "John Caird"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Harrison Bergeron?", "answers": ["Pat Conroy", "Kurt Vonnegut", "Edmund Spenser", "Allan Knee"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Who Do You Think You Are??", "answers": ["Greg Cox", "Steven Gould", "Alice Munro", "Anne Rivers Siddons"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Panchatantra?", "answers": ["Lincoln Child", "Krishna Dharma", "Martin Fridson", "Mario Puzo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Urban Romance?", "answers": ["Steven D. Levitt", "Nelson George", "Milton A. Rothman", "Bartolom\u00e9 de Las Casas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Andromeda Strain?", "answers": ["T. H. White", "Michael Crichton", "Glenn Beck", "Jules Verne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dance of Death?", "answers": ["Douglas Preston", "Shirley Jones", "Sharon Flake", "Sylvain Reynard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dance of Death?", "answers": ["Lincoln Child", "Henry Wadsworth Longfellow", "Lucretius", "Jawanza Kunjufu"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Poor Relations?", "answers": ["Compton Mackenzie", "Barbara O'Connor", "Virginia Woolf", "James McBride"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dr. Spock's Baby and Childcare?", "answers": ["Chris Ryan", "Benjamin Spock", "Shrikant G. Talageri", "Kevin Barry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Fair Lady - Stage Vocal Selections: Piano/Vocal/Guitar?", "answers": ["Beverly Lewis", "Alan Jay Lerner", "E. Nesbit", "F. Scott Fitzgerald"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Fair Lady - Stage Vocal Selections: Piano/Vocal/Guitar?", "answers": ["Frederic Loewe", "Tony Mendez", "Compton Mackenzie", "Frank McCourt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Storm of Swords?", "answers": ["Arthur Whitelaw", "Ellen Hopkins", "Audrey Niffenegger", "George R. R. Martin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stargirl?", "answers": ["Christopher Smart", "Jerry Spinelli", "David Sheff", "David Treuer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Secretariat?", "answers": ["William Nack", "Douglas Angus", "Iris Johansen", "Brad Thor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Autobiography of a Yogi?", "answers": ["Paramahansa Yogananda", "Jean-Dominique Bauby", "Valmiki", "John Keir Cross"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Cryptogram?", "answers": ["David Mamet", "Horace Walpole", "Adriana Trigiani", "Walter Isaacson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Little Men?", "answers": ["Mark Tully", "Patrick Barlow", "Louisa May Alcott", "Sol Yurick"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Volcano Lover?", "answers": ["Eve Adamson", "Alvin Schwartz", "Susan Sontag", "Ignatius L. Donnelly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cousin Bette?", "answers": ["Honor\u00e9 de Balzac", "Bryce Courtenay", "Stephen Kendrick", "Tholkappiar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Case-Book of Sherlock Holmes?", "answers": ["Robyn Carr", "Arthur Conan Doyle", "Munro Leaf", "Eddi Fiegel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Legend of Sleepy Hollow?", "answers": ["Tahir Shah", "Carolyn Reeder", "Washington Irving", "Alice Raymon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book J'accuse?", "answers": ["\u00c9mile Zola", "Thomas Harris", "Steven Sater", "Jack Weinstock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Power of One?", "answers": ["John Berendt", "Mourning Dove", "Bryce Courtenay", "Franklin Lacey"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Night Watch?", "answers": ["Richard Carlson", "Sergey Lukyanenko", "Arnold Lobel", "Ann Voskamp"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Planet of the Apes?", "answers": ["Steven McShane", "Ron Hall", "Pierre Boulle", "Dayananda Saraswati"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Aviator's Wife?", "answers": ["Eric Berne", "Melanie Hauser", "Ethel Turner", "Karel \u010capek"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks?", "answers": ["Dave Thompson", "Francis Chan", "Christa Faust", "Rebecca Skloot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Magnificent Obsession?", "answers": ["Lloyd C. Douglas", "Barbara O'Connor", "Sheryl WuDunn", "Betty Comden"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ladybug Girl?", "answers": ["Clinton Kelly", "David Soman", "Emily Giffin", "Craig Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ladybug Girl?", "answers": ["Tom Rob Smith", "Jacky Davis", "Kevin J. Anderson", "Kevin J. Anderson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Confederacy of Dunces?", "answers": ["John Kennedy Toole", "One Direction", "David Goldblatt", "Daniel Handler"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Streams in the Desert?", "answers": ["Carlo Collodi", "Wally Lamb", "L. B. Cowman", "William James"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Boy's Life?", "answers": ["Franz Kafka", "Robert R. McCammon", "William S. Gray", "Gyan C. Jain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book De rerum natura?", "answers": ["Margaret Stohl", "Lucretius", "Matt Bissonnette", "Margaret Mitchell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Crime and Punishment?", "answers": ["Pierre Boulle", "David Weber", "William Stobbs", "Fyodor Dostoyevsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Call Me Madam?", "answers": ["Russel Crouse", "Alan Moore", "Elizabeth Wurtzel", "Don Miller"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Call Me Madam?", "answers": ["Carl Van Vechten", "Howard Lindsay", "J. Alison James", "Wilson Rawls"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Age of Innocence?", "answers": ["Cecily von Ziegesar", "J. Alison James", "Edith Wharton", "Louis de Berni\u00e8res"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Natural Woman: A Memoir?", "answers": ["C. Everard Palmer", "Carole King", "Samuel Taylor Coleridge", "George Bernard Shaw"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Which Side are You On?: The Story of a Song?", "answers": ["Adolph Green", "George Ella Lyon", "Gennifer Choldenko", "Irving Shulman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Critical Thinking?", "answers": ["A. J. Cronin", "Richard Parker", "Sinclair Lewis", "James Wesley Rawles"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Yes Man?", "answers": ["Danny Wallace", "Deja King", "Anne Fine", "Belva Plain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sway: The Irresistible Pull of Irrational Behavior?", "answers": ["Oscar Wilde", "Sheryl WuDunn", "Rom Brafman", "Dashiell Hammett"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sway: The Irresistible Pull of Irrational Behavior?", "answers": ["Ruth Westheimer", "Emily Giffin", "Lois Lowry", "Ori Brafman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Touch of Frost?", "answers": ["Sophie Kinsella", "Prentice Mulford", "Francis Lathom", "R. D. Wingfield"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Last of the Mohicans?", "answers": ["Rashid-al-Din Hamadani", "Eddi Fiegel", "James Fenimore Cooper", "Joe R. Lansdale"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pact?", "answers": ["Jodi Picoult", "David Goldblatt", "Sogyal Rinpoche", "Ishmael Beah"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pact?", "answers": ["David Oliver Relin", "Bob Thiele", "Margaret Wise Brown", "Alice Raymon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Mighty Fortress?", "answers": ["David Weber", "Robert Lindner", "Robert Holden", "Chris Gardner"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Guide?", "answers": ["Thomas Hardy", "R. K. Narayan", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel", "Richard Hakluyt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Aryabhatiya?", "answers": ["Richard Connell", "Jon Lee Anderson", "Hugh Wheeler", "Aryabhata"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kira-Kira?", "answers": ["Mary Norton", "Cynthia Kadohata", "Elizabeth Strout", "Boris Pasternak"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Malcolm X?", "answers": ["Kevin Trudeau", "Walter Dean Myers", "Alejandro Junger", "John Webster"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The White Road?", "answers": ["John Connolly", "Fritjof Capra", "John August", "Eva Ibbotson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gregor the Overlander?", "answers": ["Albert Facey", "Suzanne Collins", "Drew Karpyshyn", "Pittacus Lore"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Confession?", "answers": ["Cheryl Wall", "Sarah Young", "Thomas Keneally", "Leo Tolstoy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Attack?", "answers": ["Cornelius Ryan", "Herb Gardner", "Yasmina Khadra", "Jos\u00e9 Rizal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Das Kapital?", "answers": ["Brian Kernighan", "Noel Streatfeild", "Luke the Evangelist", "Karl Marx"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sweet and Low: A Family Story?", "answers": ["Paige Turner", "Rich Cohen", "Ray Kurzweil", "Thor Heyerdahl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tales of a Fourth Grade Nothing?", "answers": ["Arthur Hailey", "Jacky Davis", "Kate Cary", "Judy Blume"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book True Grit?", "answers": ["Ouida", "Lisi Harrison", "Ellen G. White", "Charles Portis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Life A User's Manual?", "answers": ["John Dos Passos", "Guru Nanak Dev", "Brian Kernighan", "Georges Perec"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Splatterpunks II?", "answers": ["Pliny the Elder", "Peter Rinearson", "Thomas Paine", "Clive Barker"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Splatterpunks II?", "answers": ["John Edward Williams", "Raj\u0101\u02bc \u02bbAbd All\u0101h \u1e62\u0101ni\u02bb", "Erich Maria Remarque", "Poppy Z. Brite"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Splatterpunks II?", "answers": ["Loretta Lynn", "Martin Amis", "Anna Dewdney", "Evelyn Waugh"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Splatterpunks II?", "answers": ["Art Spiegelman", "David Rabe", "Eric Van Lustbader", "Christa Faust"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Diary of Ellen Rimbauer: My Life at Rose Red?", "answers": ["John van de Ruit", "James Ellroy", "Ridley Pearson", "Homer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Midnight's Children?", "answers": ["Arthur Miller", "Norman Maclean", "Salman Rushdie", "Erich Segal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The English Patient?", "answers": ["James Boswell", "Michael Ondaatje", "Charles Bukowski", "E. Annie Proulx"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kindness/Strangers?", "answers": ["Julie Smith", "Gabrielle-Suzanne Barbot de Villeneuve", "Michael J. Losier", "Phyllis Reynolds Naylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Kite Runner?", "answers": ["William P. Young", "Khaled Hosseini", "Henrik Ibsen", "E. L. James"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wonderful world?", "answers": ["Martin Dugard", "Berry Gordy", "Javier Calvo", "Michael Hollinger"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying?", "answers": ["Thomas Keneally", "Foxfire Fund Inc.", "Richard Wright", "Jack Weinstock"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying?", "answers": ["James Rado", "Fu Xi", "Pearl S. Buck", "Willie Gilbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying?", "answers": ["William Diehl", "Arthur Balfour", "Abe Burrows", "Murasaki Shikibu"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Paul Bunyan 20th Anniversary Edition?", "answers": ["Herman J. Mankiewicz", "Steven Kellogg", "Munshi Premchand", "Rachel Carson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book To a Mouse?", "answers": ["Wendy Fonarow", "Elizabeth Kostova", "Robert Burns", "Lisa Genova"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Black Beauty?", "answers": ["Richard Stilgoe", "Kathryn Stockett", "Anna Sewell", "Joseph Stein"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Curious George?", "answers": ["Eben Alexander", "Marcia Brown", "David Morrell", "Margret Rey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Curious George?", "answers": ["Laozi", "Sofi Oksanen", "Joanna Cole", "H. A. Rey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Simple Guide to Marketing Your Book: What an Author and Publisher Can Do to Sell More Books?", "answers": ["Richard Blackaby", "Mark Ortman", "Natalie Babbitt", "Pearl Poet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hound of the Baskervilles?", "answers": ["Nicholas D. Kristof", "Arthur Conan Doyle", "V. C. Andrews", "J. Meade Falkner"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Don Quixote?", "answers": ["Eduard Jose", "Miguel de Cervantes", "John Keats", "Ian McEwan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Outsider?", "answers": ["Terrence McNally", "William D. Cohan", "Piers Paul Read", "Colin Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Devil in a Blue Dress?", "answers": ["Walter Mosley", "Matt Stone", "Scott Turow", "British Library"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Topaz?", "answers": ["Leon Uris", "Lynley Dodd", "Spencer Johnson", "Fareed Zakaria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Same Kind of Different As Me?", "answers": ["James Hilton", "Guy Bolton", "Ron Hall", "Matt Baglio"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Snow Child?", "answers": ["Rory Freedman", "Eowyn Ivey", "K. A. Applegate", "Linda Sue Park"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book It's Kind of a Funny Story?", "answers": ["Raymond Briggs", "Randy Pausch", "Ned Vizzini", "Frederick Winslow Taylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Schindler's Ark?", "answers": ["Patrick Dennis", "Simone Elkeles", "Thomas Keneally", "Susan Beth Pfeffer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Best Business Books Ever: The 100 Most Influential Management Books You'll Never Have Time to Read?", "answers": ["Bill Dedman", "William F. Nolan", "Perseus Books Group", "Ram Dass"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Beautiful Mind: The Life of Mathematical Genius and Nobel Laureate John Nash?", "answers": ["Ernestine Gilbreth Carey", "Sylvia Nasar", "Anne Bront\u00eb", "Ayi Kwei Armah"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Into Thin Air: A Personal Account of the Mt. Everest Disaster?", "answers": ["Ken Kesey", "E.T.A. Hoffmann", "Jon Krakauer", "John R. Erickson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jane Eyre?", "answers": ["Stephen Templin", "Eckhart Tolle", "Sharon Draper", "Charlotte Bront\u00eb"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mutiny on the Bounty?", "answers": ["Che Guevara", "James Norman Hall", "Frederic Loewe", "Robert Graves"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mutiny on the Bounty?", "answers": ["Katherine Mayo", "Harold Pinter", "Charles Nordhoff", "David Patterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Song of Solomon?", "answers": ["Toni Morrison", "Gertrude Jekyll", "Mohsin Hamid", "Philip Carlo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Very Hungry Caterpillar?", "answers": ["Virgil", "Ellen Hopkins", "Eric Carle", "Ridley Pearson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book City of Bones?", "answers": ["Jon Krakauer", "William Styron", "Cassandra Clare", "Anna Sewell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rapunzel?", "answers": ["Bert Dodson", "Eudora Welty", "Michael Connelly", "A. J. Quinnell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The new joy of sex?", "answers": ["Raina Telgemeier", "Christopher Paul Curtis", "Alex Comfort", "Chris Kuzneski"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fifty Shades of Grey?", "answers": ["Anna Dewdney", "William Stobbs", "Gary Jennings", "E. L. James"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Theseus and the Minotaur?", "answers": ["Greg Mortenson", "Guinness World Records", "Leonard Everett Fisher", "Milton A. Rothman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lorna Doone?", "answers": ["Dean Fuller", "Reza Aslan", "R. D. Blackmore", "Robyn Carr"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Monster High?", "answers": ["Matt Baglio", "Noam Chomsky", "Lisi Harrison", "Dorothy Fields"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book This Charming Man?", "answers": ["Marian Keyes", "Jamie Simons", "Stieg Larsson", "Fran\u00e7ois Rabelais"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Morning has broken?", "answers": ["Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings", "George Langelaan", "Eleanor Farjeon", "Jon Ronson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Good Earth?", "answers": ["Joceline Sanschagrin", "Diana Wynne Jones", "Pearl S. Buck", "Lane Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book City of Bones?", "answers": ["R. K. Narayan", "Rodman Philbrick", "R.M. French", "Michael Connelly"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lost and found?", "answers": ["Rumiko Takahashi", "Malcolm Gladwell", "Fred Graver", "Jayne Ann Krentz"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Awakenings?", "answers": ["Oliver Sacks", "Kenneth E. Boulding", "Robert Sobel", "Wendelin Van Draanen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Steel Magnolias?", "answers": ["William Easterly", "Rufus Jones", "Robert Harling", "Dean Koontz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Young Warriors?", "answers": ["Victor Stafford Reid", "Charlotte Perkins Gilman", "Ethel Turner", "Graham Greene"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Strange Case of Origami Yoda?", "answers": ["Robert Greene", "Wendelin Van Draanen", "Hermann Hesse", "Tom Angleberger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anthem?", "answers": ["Ayn Rand", "Poppy Z. Brite", "Isabel Allende", "Judith Krantz"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Middle School: The Worst Years of My Life?", "answers": ["Chris Crutcher", "James Patterson", "Muslim ibn al-Hajjaj", "Laura Colker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Motown: The Musical?", "answers": ["Libba Bray", "Stephen Hawking", "Berry Gordy", "Richard Castle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Piers Plowman?", "answers": ["P. D. James", "Ann Rinaldi", "William Langland", "Dee Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Travels with Charley: In Search of America?", "answers": ["Berry Gordy", "John Steinbeck", "Honor\u00e9 de Balzac", "Faith Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Maggot?", "answers": ["Paul Muldoon", "Jeff Probst", "Walter Francis White", "Ovid"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Remains of the Day?", "answers": ["Daniel Silva", "P. C. Wren", "Andrew Clements", "Kazuo Ishiguro"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My experiments with untruth?", "answers": ["Gyan C. Jain", "Dan Poynter", "Johann David Wyss", "Rumiko Takahashi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chinese Cinderella?", "answers": ["Jerry Spinelli", "Andrew S. Tanenbaum", "Bryce Courtenay", "Adeline Yen Mah"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Waste Land?", "answers": ["T. S. Eliot", "Barry M. Goldwater", "Rich Cohen", "Joseph Gibaldi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Schooled?", "answers": ["John Gardner", "Patrick Dennis", "Deborah Ellis", "Gordon Korman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gruffalo?", "answers": ["Mike Piazza", "Kenneth Grahame", "Julia Donaldson", "Christopher Brookmyre"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Look Back in Anger?", "answers": ["Adam Mansbach", "Marghanita Laski", "Jacqueline Winspear", "John Osborne"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Fall of Five?", "answers": ["James Hurst", "Nevil Shute", "Pittacus Lore", "Banjo Paterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Unwind?", "answers": ["Malcolm Lowry", "Neal Shusterman", "Flora Thompson", "Jacqueline Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book This is the house that Jack built?", "answers": ["Daniel Keyes", "Simms Taback", "Thor Heyerdahl", "Mark Ortman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Babbitt?", "answers": ["David Lodge", "Sinclair Lewis", "Mary Norton", "John Gunther"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Any Human Heart?", "answers": ["Mickey Rapkin", "Caryl Churchill", "William Boyd", "Dean Fuller"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fight Club?", "answers": ["Steve Eng", "Rustichello da Pisa", "Chuck Palahniuk", "Edith Wharton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Annie?", "answers": ["Tess Mallos", "Patricia Highsmith", "Thomas Meehan", "Greg Farshtey"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Seedfolks?", "answers": ["Helen Prejean", "Paul Fleischman", "Sara Gruen", "Stephanie Stuve-Bodeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Outbreak?", "answers": ["Robin Cook", "Arthur Miller", "Jonathan Cahn", "Libba Bray"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Follow the River?", "answers": ["Daniel Goleman", "Natalie Babbitt", "A. E. W. Mason", "James Alexander Thom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Merriam-Webster Dictionary?", "answers": ["Harvey Fierstein", "Jerry Bock", "Merriam-Webster", "Nelson George"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jesus Christ Superstar?", "answers": ["Tim Rice", "Jon Lee Anderson", "Crockett Johnson", "Gennifer Choldenko"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jesus Christ Superstar?", "answers": ["Christopher Collier", "John Osborne", "Andrew Lloyd Webber", "Colin Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pet Sematary?", "answers": ["William Ernest Henley", "Stephen King", "Tyler Perry", "Arthur Golden"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hair?", "answers": ["Richard Bach", "Jamie McGuire", "Gerome Ragni", "Bill Dedman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hair?", "answers": ["James Rado", "Elizabeth Kostova", "Beverly Lyon Clark", "Margaret Edson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Until I Say Good-Bye: My Year of Living with Joy?", "answers": ["Bret Witter", "Alfred Noyes", "Paul O. Zelinsky", "Fidel Castro"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Until I Say Good-Bye: My Year of Living with Joy?", "answers": ["Doris Pilkington Garimara", "Susan Spencer-Wendel", "J. A. Jance", "Cassandra Golds"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The League of Extraordinary Gentlemen?", "answers": ["V\u0101tsy\u0101yana", "John Grisham", "Dan Poynter", "Kevin J. Anderson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book City of God?", "answers": ["Augustine of Hippo", "William Golding", "Ethel Waters", "Douglas Adams"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Skinny Bitch?", "answers": ["Fern Michaels", "Rory Freedman", "Lurlene McDaniel", "Franz Kafka"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Skinny Bitch?", "answers": ["Kate Atkinson", "Kim Barnouin", "Jo Swerling", "Richard Preston"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chess?", "answers": ["Thomas Paine", "Adeline Yen Mah", "Richard Nelson", "Eddi Fiegel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Eleven?", "answers": ["Lauren Myracle", "Sarah Waters", "Friedrich Nietzsche", "S. A. Bodeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea?", "answers": ["Elaine Pagels", "Jules Verne", "Bruce Sterling", "Ignatius L. Donnelly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Psychopath Test?", "answers": ["John Keir Cross", "Neil Gaiman", "Lois Lowry", "Jon Ronson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Law Of Attraction?", "answers": ["Esther Hicks", "David Lodge", "Ford Madox Ford", "Art Spiegelman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Law Of Attraction?", "answers": ["Martin Fridson", "Jerry Hicks", "Dorothy Allison", "Henry Williamson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Just William?", "answers": ["Richmal Crompton", "David Brauner", "Enid Blyton", "Cameron Crowe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shirley Valentine?", "answers": ["James Herriot", "Laurie Halse Anderson", "Willy Russell", "Pierre Choderlos de Laclos"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Little Match Girl?", "answers": ["Megan McDonald", "Hans Christian Andersen", "Montesquieu", "Doris Pilkington Garimara"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lost in Translation?", "answers": ["Eddi Fiegel", "Debbie Macomber", "Bharati Krishna Tirthaji", "Edward Willett"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lost in Translation?", "answers": ["Nicole Mones", "John Fowles", "S. J. Watson", "Angela Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fever 1793?", "answers": ["Kyle Onstott", "Laurie Halse Anderson", "Stephen Covey", "Lois Duncan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Mist?", "answers": ["Stephen King", "Jerome Lawrence", "Mark Helprin", "Arthur Laurents"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Abyss?", "answers": ["Anthony Kiedis", "Peter S. Beagle", "James Lapine", "Orson Scott Card"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Inferno?", "answers": ["Diane Trister. Dodge", "Mulk Raj Anand", "Dante Alighieri", "Terry Goodkind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The red badge of courage and The veteran?", "answers": ["Truman Capote", "Norman Vincent Peale", "Daniel Goleman", "Stephen Crane"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tale of Mrs. Tiggy-Winkle?", "answers": ["Daniel Handler", "Matt Baglio", "Beatrix Potter", "Thomas C. Holt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rent?", "answers": ["W. W. Jacobs", "Jonathan Larson", "Ann Voskamp", "Sylvain Reynard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book King Rat?", "answers": ["Wendy Fonarow", "Robert A. Heinlein", "James Clavell", "Jennifer Weiner"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Breadwinner?", "answers": ["Charlotte Perkins Gilman", "Bertolt Brecht", "Richard Hakluyt", "Deborah Ellis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lemonade War?", "answers": ["Jacqueline Winspear", "Edward S. Herman", "Jacqueline Davies", "Steve Eng"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Far Away?", "answers": ["Sterling Allen Brown", "Jean M. Auel", "Dare Wright", "Caryl Churchill"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The White Road?", "answers": ["Bill O'Reilly", "Lynn Flewelling", "Niccol\u00f2 Machiavelli", "Jerry Spinelli"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Returned?", "answers": ["Rachel Harris", "Eva Ibbotson", "Rabindranath Tagore", "Jason Mott"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Seven Summers?", "answers": ["Gordon Elliott", "E. D. Baker", "Eric Berne", "Mulk Raj Anand"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Heard the Bells on Christmas Day?", "answers": ["Jerzy Kosi\u0144ski", "P. C. Wren", "Lloyd D. Newell", "Gertrude Chandler Warner"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fanny Hill?", "answers": ["John Cleland", "Paige Turner", "Kurt Vonnegut", "Guinness World Records"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book One Day at a Time?", "answers": ["Sylvain Reynard", "Friedrich Engels", "Danielle Steel", "Richard Preston"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book League of Their Own?", "answers": ["Jenny Downham", "Susan Beth Pfeffer", "Sarah Gilbert", "Clifton Taulbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book City of God?", "answers": ["Nevil Shute", "Geoffrey of Monmouth", "Paulo Lins", "Gordon Elliott"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gone with the Wind?", "answers": ["Margaret Mitchell", "Sister Souljah", "Dale Carnegie", "Ernest Thompson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beach Music?", "answers": ["Charles T. Horngren", "Pat Conroy", "Friedrich Nietzsche", "Tim LaHaye"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Love Dare?", "answers": ["Elizabeth Jolley", "Stephen Kendrick", "Alice Munro", "John Dempsey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Love Dare?", "answers": ["Edward Willett", "Clement Clarke Moore", "Edmund White", "Alex Kendrick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Love Dare?", "answers": ["Bernard Malamud", "Lawrence Kimbrough", "William Cullen Bryant", "James Herriot"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fast Times at Ridgemont High: A True Story?", "answers": ["Margret Rey", "Cameron Crowe", "Michael Crichton", "J. Meade Falkner"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Are You My Mother??", "answers": ["Paramahansa Yogananda", "P. D. Eastman", "Jim Bouton", "Paulo Herique"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas?", "answers": ["John Boyne", "Christopher Isherwood", "William Landay", "Eric Blehm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Book of the Courtier?", "answers": ["Arthur Kopit", "John Heilemann", "Hillary Rodham Clinton", "Baldassare Castiglione"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lolita?", "answers": ["Vladimir Vladimirovich Nabokov", "Kathryn Stockett", "Dorothy Wall", "Albert E Cliffe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Raymond Carver: A Writers Life?", "answers": ["Eleanor Estes", "Daniel Goleman", "Carol Sklenicka", "Walter Dean Myers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Milk and Honey: A Novel?", "answers": ["Elizabeth Jolley", "Beverly Lewis", "Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dallas justice?", "answers": ["Melvin Belli", "Thomas Wolfe", "Ian Fleming", "A. J. Cronin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Snowball: Warren Buffett and the Business of Life?", "answers": ["Alice Schroeder", "Spencer Johnson", "Ayn Rand", "Donald Margulies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Japji Sahib: The Song of the Soul?", "answers": ["Bram Stoker", "Lisa Genova", "Guru Nanak Dev", "Jonathan Swift"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bookclub-In-A-Box Discusses the Novel Bel Canto by Ann Patchett?", "answers": ["Henry Beveridge", "Daniel Brown", "Ann Patchett", "Lafcadio Hearn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Shoemaker's Wife?", "answers": ["A. A. Milne", "Adriana Trigiani", "Kimon Valaskakis", "Esphyr Slobodkina"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Collector?", "answers": ["Fania Oz-Salzberger", "Nancy Farmer", "John Fowles", "Daniel Handler"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Aida?", "answers": ["David Henry Hwang", "John Donne", "Laurie Lee", "Mary Kay Andrews"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Aida?", "answers": ["Jody Rosen", "Lisa Frazier Page", "E. Annie Proulx", "Robert Falls"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Aida?", "answers": ["Ally Condie", "William Golding", "Linda Woolverton", "Sheila Quigley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Motorcycle Diaries?", "answers": ["Che Guevara", "Bertrand Russell", "Nick Hornby", "Frank McCourt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pay It Forward?", "answers": ["H. G. Wells", "Curtis Sittenfeld", "Gustave Flaubert", "Catherine Ryan Hyde"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gunga Din?", "answers": ["Al Gore", "Timothy Ferriss", "Lisa Genova", "Rudyard Kipling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Black List?", "answers": ["Richard Gravil", "Edwin Balmer", "Brad Thor", "Jean Marzollo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tiny Alice?", "answers": ["Anne Rivers Siddons", "Eric Kimmel", "Edward Conlon", "Edward Albee"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Oklahoma!?", "answers": ["Hasan Azizul Huq", "Alan Moore", "Stephen Covey", "Oscar Hammerstein II"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Namesake?", "answers": ["John Guare", "John Locke", "Jhumpa Lahiri", "Thomas Kyd"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tarka the Otter?", "answers": ["Henry Williamson", "Charles W. Chesnutt", "Herman Koch", "Mitch Albom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Long Shot?", "answers": ["Rex Pickett", "Mike Piazza", "Ben Okri", "Donald R. Bear"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Book Thief?", "answers": ["Aesop", "Bertolt Brecht", "Markus Zusak", "Charles Portis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lovely Bones?", "answers": ["Mark O'Donnell", "Greg Mortenson", "Robert Barnard", "Alice Sebold"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Angela's Ashes?", "answers": ["Jahangir", "Frank McCourt", "Marsha Norman", "Richard Thaler"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Graveyard Book?", "answers": ["Pittacus Lore", "David Baldacci", "Neil Gaiman", "Jack Weinstock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hairspray?", "answers": ["Dave Eggers", "Mark O'Donnell", "William Howard Armstrong", "Patrick J. O'Brian"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hairspray?", "answers": ["Thomas Hardy", "Thomas Meehan", "India Knight", "Lynne Reid Banks"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Back to the Future: A Novel?", "answers": ["Jeanne DuPrau", "Grumpy Cat", "Phillip Berman", "George Gipe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The General's Daughter?", "answers": ["Nelson DeMille", "Samuel P. Huntington", "J. L. Carr", "Jacqueline Susann"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Interpretation of Dreams?", "answers": ["Douglas Angus", "Craig Hansen Werner", "Sigmund Freud", "Dashiell Hammett"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Wheels on the Bus - Nursery Rhyme Sound Book?", "answers": ["Joy Adamson", "Primo Levi", "Maurine Dallas Watkins", "Penny Dann"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Absolutely True Diary of a Part-Time Indian?", "answers": ["John Dos Passos", "Sherman Alexie", "Dale Carnegie", "Ira Wood"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Prayer for Owen Meany?", "answers": ["John Irving", "Harvey Fierstein", "Amos Oz", "Jennifer L. Holm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Frog and toad are friends?", "answers": ["Munshi Premchand", "Thomas C Foster", "Fareed Zakaria", "Doris Roettger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Dear Departed: A Comedy in One Act?", "answers": ["Andrew Carnegie", "Herman Wouk", "Stanley Houghton", "R. D. Wingfield"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The New Jim Crow?", "answers": ["Charles Reade", "Michelle Alexander", "William P. Young", "Ellen Hopkins"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Roar?", "answers": ["Emma Clayton", "Tom Rath", "Priscilla Cummings", "John Edward Williams"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book White Christmas?", "answers": ["Jody Rosen", "Walter Francis White", "Charles Webb", "Dave Eggers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The City of Ember?", "answers": ["Jeanne DuPrau", "Foxfire Fund Inc.", "Mark the Evangelist", "Countee Cullen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cabaret?", "answers": ["Ravinder Singh", "Ted Sorensen", "Joe Masteroff", "Lois Banner"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A change is gonna come?", "answers": ["Bob Fosse", "Jack Weinstock", "Robert Frost", "Craig Hansen Werner"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Protocols of the Elders of Zion?", "answers": ["Luigi Pirandello", "Euclid", "Joseph Heller", "Sir John Retcliffe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Coraline?", "answers": ["Mary Lewis Wang", "Neil Gaiman", "William Langland", "Watty Piper"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Roll Me Up and Smoke Me When I Die: Musings from the Road?", "answers": ["Kinky Friedman", "Aldo Leopold", "Reverend W. Awdry", "Rich Cohen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Roll Me Up and Smoke Me When I Die: Musings from the Road?", "answers": ["David Sheff", "Willie Nelson", "Guy de Maupassant", "Philip Wylie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The sultan of Sulu?", "answers": ["Rebecca Skloot", "George Ade", "Marjorie W. Sharmat", "Greg Farshtey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Don't Sweat the Small Stuff in Love?", "answers": ["Richard Harris", "Richard Carlson", "Bernard Pomerance", "David Pringle"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hiding Place?", "answers": ["Corrie ten Boom", "Albert Facey", "Baldassare Castiglione", "Alain Boublil"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Golden Gate?", "answers": ["Elizabeth Cody Kimmel", "Alistair MacLean", "Stephen Crane", "Gordon Elliott"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Get Lucky?", "answers": ["Anna Quindlen", "Maurine Dallas Watkins", "Willie Gilbert", "Lane Becker"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Get Lucky?", "answers": ["Frank Herbert", "Thor Muller", "Betsy Maestro", "Jeff Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book What to Expect When You're Expecting?", "answers": ["Susan Hill", "Sharon Mazel", "Paul Fleischman", "Alain Boublil"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book What to Expect When You're Expecting?", "answers": ["Donna Tartt", "Eric L. Haney", "Zo\u00eb Heller", "Heidi Murkoff"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Secret of Crickley Hall?", "answers": ["James Lincoln Collier", "British Library", "India Knight", "James Herbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Heidi?", "answers": ["Ben Carson", "Johanna Spyri", "Vladimir Vladimirovich Nabokov", "Bill Bryson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Boy In the Striped Pajamas?", "answers": ["Gyan C. Jain", "John Boyne", "Amish Tripathi", "Ralph Ellison"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Sand County Almanac?", "answers": ["Aldo Leopold", "Arnold Lobel", "Catherine Johnson", "Caryl Churchill"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Once Upon a Mattress?", "answers": ["Ken Follett", "Dean Fuller", "Geraldine Brooks", "Paulo Herique"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Once Upon a Mattress?", "answers": ["Jeffrey Probst", "Jay Thompson", "Denise Mina", "No\u00ebl Coward"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Once Upon a Mattress?", "answers": ["Norman Maclean", "John Maynard Smith", "Marshall Barer", "Sonia Gandhi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Inherit the Wind?", "answers": ["Henrik Ibsen", "Jerome Lawrence", "Mary Doria Russell", "Guru Arjan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Inherit the Wind?", "answers": ["Anonymous", "Stephen Mallatratt", "Leon Edel", "Robert Edwin Lee"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Frangipani house?", "answers": ["Banjo Paterson", "Maggie Stiefvater", "Raymond Chandler", "Beryl Gilroy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Next to Normal?", "answers": ["Brian Yorkey", "William Henry Hudson", "Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa", "Ernest Hemingway"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Starlight Express?", "answers": ["John Edward Williams", "Richard Stilgoe", "Ken Blanchard", "Roger Allers"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Serenity Prayer?", "answers": ["Emmet Fox", "Reinhold Niebuhr", "Laurence Sterne", "Cynthia Kadohata"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Perfect Chemistry?", "answers": ["Melvin Belli", "Robert Thornton Morrison", "Paulo Coelho", "Simone Elkeles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book India Divided?", "answers": ["E. Nesbit", "Christopher Brookmyre", "Rajendra Prasad", "Neal Shusterman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The ant and the dove?", "answers": ["Kerry Patterson", "Mary Lewis Wang", "Steven McShane", "Kris Carr"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Howl?", "answers": ["Dee Brown", "Fritjof Capra", "Allen Ginsberg", "Samantha Shannon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Myra Breckinridge?", "answers": ["Gregory Maguire", "Gore Vidal", "Richard Gravil", "Harvey Fierstein"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Enormous Turnip?", "answers": ["Stephen Vincent Ben\u00e9t", "Aaron Sorkin", "Aleksey Nikolayevich Tolstoy", "Winston Groom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book On Photography?", "answers": ["Susan Sontag", "Bill Clinton", "Gaston Leroux", "Sergey Lukyanenko"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tartuffe?", "answers": ["Moli\u00e8re", "Lauren Weisberger", "P. G. Wodehouse", "Richard Preston"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Art of Racing in the Rain?", "answers": ["J. K. Rowling", "Garth Stein", "Francis Chan", "Neil Simon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gettysburg: The Last Invasion?", "answers": ["Allen C. Guelzo", "Carl Bernstein", "Malcolm Gladwell", "Gail Boushey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Toad of Toad Hall?", "answers": ["Valmiki", "A. A. Milne", "Jay Anson", "Johann Christoph Friedrich von Schiller"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Charlotte's Web?", "answers": ["Austin Winsberg", "E. B. White", "Charles A. Murray", "Amy Vanderbilt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Scruples?", "answers": ["John Green", "Piper Kerman", "Judith Krantz", "Sheila Lane"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Miguel Street?", "answers": ["Beverly Lewis", "Boles\u0142aw Prus", "V.S. Naipaul", "Mike Resnick"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Child 44?", "answers": ["Barbara Ehrenreich", "Tom Rob Smith", "Rumiko Takahashi", "Richard Condon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Song of Ice and Fire?", "answers": ["Lynn Sherr", "P. D. Eastman", "William Martin", "George R. R. Martin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Little Lord Fauntleroy?", "answers": ["Solomon", "Neil Simon", "Frances Hodgson Burnett", "Gunnar Myrdal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Threepenny Opera?", "answers": ["Bertolt Brecht", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel", "Jane Taylor", "Richard Wright"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In Our Time?", "answers": ["Neal Shusterman", "Joanna Cole", "Ernest Hemingway", "V.S. Naipaul"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mr. Popper's Penguins?", "answers": ["Paul Muldoon", "Richard Atwater", "Deborah Smith", "Michael Ondaatje"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mr. Popper's Penguins?", "answers": ["William F. Nolan", "Neil Simon", "Lloyd C. Douglas", "Florence Atwater"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Complete Greek Cookbook?", "answers": ["Chuck Palahniuk", "Percy Bysshe Shelley", "Theresa Karas Yianilos", "Sapphire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hunchback of Notre Dame?", "answers": ["Robert Burns", "Victor Hugo", "Judah the Prince", "Gene Stone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Flowers in the Attic?", "answers": ["Val McDermid", "Diana Wynne Jones", "V. C. Andrews", "Sara Shepard"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gospel of Wealth?", "answers": ["Matthew the Apostle", "Rick Riordan", "Curtis Sittenfeld", "Andrew Carnegie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book American Psycho?", "answers": ["Zo\u00eb Heller", "Margaret Edson", "Bret Easton Ellis", "David Auburn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Indian Cookbook?", "answers": ["Bhalchandra Pundlik Adarkar", "Sheryl WuDunn", "Chris Gardner", "Shehzad Husain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Indian Cookbook?", "answers": ["Mridula Baljekar", "R.M. French", "Jeannette Walls", "Ralph Woodrow"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The laws of Manu?", "answers": ["Jon Krakauer", "Manu (Lawgiver)", "Thomas Hughes", "Caitlin Moran"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Anarchist Cookbook?", "answers": ["E. D. Baker", "Joseph Stein", "Robert Kimmel Smith", "William Powell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Man Who Mistook His Wife for a Hat?", "answers": ["James Marshall", "Tracy Letts", "Doris Pilkington Garimara", "Oliver Sacks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wonderstruck?", "answers": ["W. Chan Kim", "James Howard Kunstler", "Nan Knighton", "Brian Selznick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lonely Doll?", "answers": ["No\u00ebl Coward", "Dare Wright", "Jay Anson", "Marguerite Henry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jack and the Beanstalk?", "answers": ["Howard Pyle", "Steven Kellogg", "Peter Carey", "Niccol\u00f2 Machiavelli"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Watchmen?", "answers": ["Lala Lajpat Rai", "Dave Gibbons", "John R. Erickson", "John Gardner"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Watchmen?", "answers": ["Alan Moore", "Lois Lowry", "William Manchester", "Anita Diamant"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The decision to drop the atomic bomb?", "answers": ["Dennis Wainstock", "Jeanne DuPrau", "Enda Walsh", "Jean Anouilh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Seven Little Australians?", "answers": ["Ethel Turner", "Paul Howard", "E. B. White", "Irma S. Rombauer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Art of Intrusion?", "answers": ["Robert Barnard", "Kevin Mitnick", "Arthur Ashe", "Fritjof Capra"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Dog's Life: The Autobiography of a Stray?", "answers": ["Rainer Maria Rilke", "George Abbott", "Stephen W. Garber", "Ann M. Martin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Firefox?", "answers": ["Craig Thomas", "Claude McKay", "Anne Bront\u00eb", "Anthony Burgess"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Big Book?", "answers": ["Danielle Steel", "Bill W.", "Christopher Paul Curtis", "Kazuo Ishiguro"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Time to Kill?", "answers": ["Jack Weinstock", "John Grisham", "Ira Levin", "Amish Tripathi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rock of Ages?", "answers": ["Beryl Markham", "Chris D'Arienzo", "Whitney Stewart", "Eric Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lady Chatterley's Lover?", "answers": ["D. H. Lawrence", "A. J. Quinnell", "Basil Liddell Hart", "Jerry Pinkney"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jumper?", "answers": ["Peter Barnes", "Harlan Ellison", "Steven Gould", "Samuel Beckett"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A. J. Cronin: The Man Who Created Dr Finlay?", "answers": ["Alan Davies", "Robert Harris", "Kristin Cashore", "Drew Karpyshyn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Scat?", "answers": ["Zora Neale Hurston", "Francesca Simon", "Ted Sorensen", "Carl Hiaasen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rebecca?", "answers": ["Alex Kendrick", "Daphne du Maurier", "David Brauner", "Confucius"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book John Carter of Mars?", "answers": ["Gerd Theissen", "Edgar Rice Burroughs", "Lynne Reid Banks", "George Langelaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book John Carter of Mars?", "answers": ["Patrick Robinson", "John Coleman Burroughs", "George Ade", "Katharine Holabird"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Thomas Jefferson: Author of America?", "answers": ["Mary Claire Helldorfer", "J. G. Ballard", "Christopher Hitchens", "Thomas Hardy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Life Divine?", "answers": ["Tom Jones", "Sri Aurobindo", "Krishna Dharma", "Sebastian Faulks"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Experiencing God: Knowing and Doing the Will of God?", "answers": ["Bede", "Stephen C. Lundin", "Henry Blackaby", "Marilyn Diamond"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gift of the Magi?", "answers": ["C. S. Godshalk", "O. Henry", "Solomon Noethup", "Nicolaus Copernicus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book El filibusterismo?", "answers": ["Noam Chomsky", "Jos\u00e9 Rizal", "John the Evangelist", "Narmad\u0101pras\u0101da Up\u0101dhy\u0101ya"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Fault in Our Stars?", "answers": ["John Green", "Ntozake Shange", "Shirley Conran", "Guy de Maupassant"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Before the Fact?", "answers": ["Sara Pennypacker", "Beatrice Sparks", "Anthony Berkeley Cox", "Walt Whitman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Total Recall?", "answers": ["P. C. Wren", "Piers Anthony", "Alain-Ren\u00e9 Lesage", "Sampson Davis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lightning Thief?", "answers": ["Mary Kay Andrews", "Michael Ledwidge", "Rick Riordan", "Nicholas D. Kristof"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Great Controversy?", "answers": ["Leif Enger", "Anne Mazer", "Marge Piercy", "Ellen G. White"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book An Occurrence at Owl Creek Bridge?", "answers": ["Michelle Knudsen", "Alan Dean Foster", "Ambrose Bierce", "Helen DeWitt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ondine?", "answers": ["Thor Heyerdahl", "Richard Linklater", "Marta Hillers", "Jean Giraudoux"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book An Gruffalo?", "answers": ["Aristotle", "Axel Scheffler", "Dennis Lehane", "Clement Clarke Moore"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book An Gruffalo?", "answers": ["Tim Tharp", "Mitch Albom", "Julia Donaldson", "Raina Telgemeier"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Man from Snowy River?", "answers": ["H. A. Rey", "Banjo Paterson", "William R. Forstchen", "Robert Penn Warren"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Shack: Where Tragedy Confronts Eternity?", "answers": ["Thiruvalluvar", "William P. Young", "Gary Ezzo", "Daniel Handler"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rats?", "answers": ["Shrikant G. Talageri", "Rick Moody", "Walter Lord", "James Herbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Republic?", "answers": ["Drew Karpyshyn", "S. J. Watson", "Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa", "Plato"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book City of Bohane?", "answers": ["Kevin Barry", "Shirley Jones", "Alfred Uhry", "Lauren Billings"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Slaughterhouse-Five?", "answers": ["Reginald Rose", "Ruta Sepetys", "Kurt Vonnegut", "Heather Hach"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Red Tent?", "answers": ["Anne Fine", "Anita Diamant", "Henry Bellamann", "Frederick M. Avolio"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Death of a city?", "answers": ["Albert Camus", "William Dean Howells", "Erik Larson", "Amrita Pritam"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Walden?", "answers": ["Taslima Nasrin", "Mark Z. Danielewski", "Chris Ryan", "Henry David Thoreau"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jake's Thing?", "answers": ["Kingsley Amis", "Alex Garland", "A. S. A. Harrison", "William Makepeace Thackeray"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Divided Self: An Existential Study in Sanity and Madness?", "answers": ["Kevin Maurer", "Julian Fellowes", "Ronald David Laing", "Alain LeRoy Locke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Confession?", "answers": ["Rich Cohen", "Dalton Trumbo", "John Grisham", "Rachel Harris"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ain't I a Woman??", "answers": ["Hasan Azizul Huq", "Bert V. Royal", "Bell Hooks", "David Brauner"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ship of Fools?", "answers": ["Katherine Anne Porter", "Lois Lowry", "Sir John Retcliffe", "Terry Goodkind"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Glimpses of World History?", "answers": ["Jawaharlal Nehru", "T. H. White", "John Howard Griffin", "Philip K. Dick"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kismet?", "answers": ["Christos Tsiolkas", "Carlo Collodi", "John Edward Williams", "Luther Davis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kismet?", "answers": ["Cacilda Jeth\u00e1", "Sylvia Nasar", "Fred Gipson", "Charles Lederer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Slam!?", "answers": ["Iris Murdoch", "Howard Lindsay", "Walter Dean Myers", "John Jakes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Raft?", "answers": ["Betty Mahmoody", "Cassandra Golds", "Stephen King", "Raj\u0101\u02bc \u02bbAbd All\u0101h \u1e62\u0101ni\u02bb"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Journal of a Novel: The East of Eden Letters?", "answers": ["Charles Portis", "David Lindsay-Abaire", "John Steinbeck", "Robert Harling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Zodiac?", "answers": ["Pierre de Beaumarchais", "Robert Boyle", "Robert Graysmith", "W. Bruce Cameron"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Garden of Earthly Delights?", "answers": ["Barbara O'Connor", "Tatiana De Rosnay", "Joyce Carol Oates", "Augustine of Hippo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Wave?", "answers": ["Todd Strasser", "Melanie Hauser", "Marilyn Diamond", "Jack Kerouac"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Wind in the Willows?", "answers": ["Catherine Ryan Hyde", "Kenneth Grahame", "Richard Blackaby", "Mary Shelley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Fine Balance?", "answers": ["Paul Howard", "Rohinton Mistry", "Alice Hoffman", "H. A. Rey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sybil?", "answers": ["Flora Rheta Schreiber", "E. L. Doctorow", "Richard Thaler", "Neil Cross"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Darling Buds of May?", "answers": ["Jay Anson", "H. E. Bates", "James Patterson", "Michael Mayer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Thousand Acres?", "answers": ["Gregory Maguire", "Jane Smiley", "William Gibson", "Christopher Smart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Do not go gentle into that good night?", "answers": ["Ren\u00e9e Mauborgne", "Dylan Thomas", "Edmund Cooper", "Lincoln Peirce"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Area 51?", "answers": ["Bob Mayer", "Zora Neale Hurston", "Adam Smith", "Lydia Flem"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Endymion?", "answers": ["John Keats", "Paul O. Zelinsky", "Fay Weldon", "Aleksey Nikolayevich Tolstoy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ordinary People?", "answers": ["Maurine Dallas Watkins", "A. C. H. Smith", "Debbie Macomber", "Judith Guest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Over in the meadow?", "answers": ["Joyce Carol Oates", "Ezra Jack Keats", "Chris Tebbetts", "Enid Bagnold"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Aladdin and the magic lamp?", "answers": ["Chris Cleave", "Joanna C. Galdone", "James Howard Kunstler", "Billy Graham"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Confessions of St. Augustine?", "answers": ["Fannie Flagg", "Augustine of Hippo", "Billie Letts", "Jos\u00e9 Saramago"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Infinite Jest?", "answers": ["David Foster Wallace", "Evelyn Waugh", "Daniel James Brown", "Don Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The marshes of Glynn?", "answers": ["Victor Stafford Reid", "Barbara Ehrenreich", "Sidney Lanier", "Frederick Winslow Taylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tenant of Wildfell Hall?", "answers": ["Rufus Jones", "J. M. Barrie", "Harvey Diamond", "Anne Bront\u00eb"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book King Kong?", "answers": ["John Green", "Douglas Carter Beane", "Herman Wouk", "Merian C. Cooper"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book King Kong?", "answers": ["Dante Alighieri", "Jane Hamilton", "Delos W. Lovelace", "Meg Cabot"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Brigadoon?", "answers": ["Joseph Bruchac", "Alan Jay Lerner", "Jane O'Connor", "Mike Resnick"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Four Feathers?", "answers": ["Philip Kerr", "A. E. W. Mason", "Stacy Schiff", "Sharon Draper"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Devdas: A Novel?", "answers": ["Herbert Fields", "Nicolaus Copernicus", "Mridula Baljekar", "Sarat Chandra Chattopadhyay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The History Boys?", "answers": ["George Clayton Johnson", "Ron Powers", "Alan Bennett", "Jonathan Harr"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anatomy of a murder?", "answers": ["Philip Carlo", "Margaret Mitchell", "Whitley Strieber", "John D. Voelker"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Race?", "answers": ["Ian Rankin", "Doreen Cronin", "David Mamet", "Mark Bowden"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Autobiography of Benjamin Franklin?", "answers": ["Benjamin Franklin", "Javier Calvo", "Helen Prejean", "Auguste Maquet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fear of Flying?", "answers": ["Eileen Christelow", "Mark Twain", "Fania Oz-Salzberger", "Erica Jong"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Primary Colors?", "answers": ["Jeff Probst", "Joe Klein", "Aldous Huxley", "Anita Loos"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shelter?", "answers": ["Max Brooks", "Harlan Coben", "Nelson George", "M. Scott Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mister Pip?", "answers": ["Dmitry Glukhovsky", "Lionel Bart", "Lloyd Jones", "Kami Garcia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book All the President's Men?", "answers": ["Walter Francis White", "Carl Bernstein", "Irene Mecchi", "Khaled Hosseini"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book All the President's Men?", "answers": ["Bob Woodward", "Robert Southey", "Thomas Meehan", "David Treuer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Clan of the Cave Bear?", "answers": ["Theresa Karas Yianilos", "Jean M. Auel", "Andrew Ross Sorkin", "Thomas J. Stanley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Elephant Man?", "answers": ["James C. Collins", "John Updike", "Bernard Pomerance", "Francis Lathom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hunt for Red October?", "answers": ["Giles Andreae", "Tom Clancy", "Henry Wadsworth Longfellow", "Don Lynch"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book \"A Child Called \"\"It\"\"\"?", "answers": ["Dave Barry", "Bari Weissman", "Don Piper", "Dave Pelzer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Snakes on a Plane?", "answers": ["Christa Faust", "Gertrude Jekyll", "Tony Kushner", "Wu Cheng'en"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Message?", "answers": ["James Boswell", "Eugene H. Peterson", "James Dashner", "Margery Williams"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Odd Thomas?", "answers": ["Dean Koontz", "Steven Kellogg", "Greil Marcus", "Dave Eggers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kiss the Girls?", "answers": ["Eric Idle", "John Heilemann", "James Patterson", "Curt Gentry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Walk on the Wild Side?", "answers": ["Anita Shreve", "George Langelaan", "Lurlene McDaniel", "Nelson Algren"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Touching Spirit Bear?", "answers": ["James McBride", "Edgar Rice Burroughs", "Todd Burpo", "Ben Mikaelsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Month in the Country?", "answers": ["Esther Forbes", "Aung San Suu Kyi", "Mary Kay Andrews", "J. L. Carr"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Island of Doctor Moreau?", "answers": ["David Patterson", "H. G. Wells", "Chris Kuzneski", "Astrid Lindgren"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Xanadu?", "answers": ["Jerry Pinkney", "Niklaus Wirth", "Douglas Carter Beane", "Rohinton Mistry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Confessions of a Teenage Drama Queen?", "answers": ["Dyan Sheldon", "Joseph Heller", "Allan Folsom", "Louise Fitzhugh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book \"\"\"A\"\" is for Alibi\"?", "answers": ["V\u0101tsy\u0101yana", "Todd Burpo", "Sue Grafton", "Roger Lancelyn Green"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Steppenwolf?", "answers": ["Edward Lear", "Alexandre Dumas", "Alan Dean Foster", "Hermann Hesse"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Trinity?", "answers": ["Nikos Kazantzakis", "Bernard Malamud", "Richard Peck", "Leon Uris"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Casanova: The Man who Really Loved Women?", "answers": ["Lydia Flem", "Abba Eban", "Tony Mendez", "Robert Harris"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fantastic Mr Fox?", "answers": ["James Baldwin", "Roald Dahl", "Lynn Flewelling", "Anne Rivers Siddons"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Where the Wild Things Are?", "answers": ["Kyle Onstott", "Astrid Lindgren", "Maurice Sendak", "Sara Pennypacker"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mutton?", "answers": ["Jostein Gaarder", "Carl Van Vechten", "India Knight", "Heidi Murkoff"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Odd Couple?", "answers": ["M. L. Stedman", "Brian Yorkey", "Christopher Hitchens", "Neil Simon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Northanger Abbey?", "answers": ["James Alexander Thom", "Jane Austen", "David Oliver Relin", "Charles Lederer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tibetan Book of Living and Dying?", "answers": ["Walter Dean Myers", "Jeffery Deaver", "Sogyal Rinpoche", "Alvin Toffler"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book 101 Dalmatians?", "answers": ["Michael Wigglesworth", "Arthur Balfour", "Dodie Smith", "Guy de Maupassant"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Armageddon: A Novel of Berlin?", "answers": ["Owen Wister", "Leon Uris", "Arthur Ashe", "Jo Swerling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How To Write?", "answers": ["Amrita Pritam", "Kenneth E. Boulding", "Alastair Fowler", "Asa Earl Carter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book All Things Bright and Beautiful?", "answers": ["Betsy Thornton", "William F. Brown", "Cecil Frances Humphreys Alexander", "Samuel Noah Kramer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book God's Little Acre?", "answers": ["Erskine Caldwell", "Anita Diamant", "W. Somerset Maugham", "E.T.A. Hoffmann"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book King Solomon's Mines?", "answers": ["Billy Frolick", "H. Rider Haggard", "Emma Donoghue", "Tracy Letts"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Grimm's Fairy Tales?", "answers": ["Zelda Fitzgerald", "Abba Eban", "Eowyn Ivey", "Wilhelm Grimm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Grimm's Fairy Tales?", "answers": ["Candace Bushnell", "Jacob Grimm", "Laura Colker", "Adrian Martin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Very Potter Musical?", "answers": ["Lee Hall", "Matt Lang", "Floyd Mutrux", "James Agee"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Antigone?", "answers": ["Roger Sherman", "Jean Anouilh", "Gerome Ragni", "Elizabeth George Speare"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bring It On the Musical?", "answers": ["Jeff Whitty", "Sophie Kinsella", "Jean-Jacques Rousseau", "Thomas C. Holt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Get Shorty?", "answers": ["Jean le Rond d'Alembert", "Laurence Sterne", "Elmore Leonard", "Grace Metalious"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stranded?", "answers": ["Compton Mackenzie", "John of Patmos", "Ben Mikaelsen", "Jess Walter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Moll Flanders?", "answers": ["Daniel Defoe", "Shashi Tharoor", "A. S. Byatt", "Arthur Golden"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Neverending Story?", "answers": ["Elias Chacour", "Jostein Gaarder", "Petrarch", "Michael Ende"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Newsies?", "answers": ["Harvey Fierstein", "Judith Guest", "Loretta Lynn", "Elizabeth Barrett Browning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Just As I Am: The Autobiography of Billy Graham?", "answers": ["Billy Graham", "Jim Gaffigan", "Evelyn Waugh", "Thor Heyerdahl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Swindle?", "answers": ["Lauren Kate", "Gordon Korman", "Henry James", "Mark the Evangelist"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The James Bond Books?", "answers": ["Ian Fleming", "Steven Kellogg", "Charles Portis", "Devaki Nandan Khatri"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Beach House?", "answers": ["Euclid", "Abe Burrows", "James Patterson", "Washington Irving"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Good to Great: Why Some Companies Make the Leap...and Others Don't?", "answers": ["James C. Collins", "David Nicholls", "Nina Bawden", "Shehzad Husain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chrysanthemum?", "answers": ["John Heilemann", "Kevin Henkes", "Bob Fosse", "Kathleen Winsor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Great Gatsby?", "answers": ["F. Scott Fitzgerald", "Eleanor H. Porter", "Simon Dunstan", "Edward Lear"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Words Their Way?", "answers": ["Joseph Gibaldi", "Donald R. Bear", "Nancy Milford", "James Weldon Johnson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Geet Govinda?", "answers": ["Kate Christensen", "Dianne Watkins Stuart", "Narmad\u0101pras\u0101da Up\u0101dhy\u0101ya", "Nicholas D. Kristof"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Robert's Rules of Order?", "answers": ["Scott Westerfeld", "Taslima Nasrin", "Henry Martyn Robert", "Thomas Hobbes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book 'Salem's Lot?", "answers": ["Lois Duncan", "Mao Zedong", "Stephen King", "Matt Bissonnette"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Monk: A Romance?", "answers": ["Thomas C. Holt", "Charles Dickens", "Nathan Myhrvold", "Matthew Gregory Lewis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Le Morte d'Arthur?", "answers": ["David Lindsay-Abaire", "Diana Hacker", "George Langelaan", "Thomas Malory"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Modest Proposal?", "answers": ["Jonathan Swift", "Carlos Ruiz Zaf\u00f3n", "Laozi", "David Wong"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Secret Life of Walter Mitty?", "answers": ["Fern Michaels", "James Thurber", "Pope Benedict XVI", "Nicole Mones"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sendmail: Theory and Practice?", "answers": ["Frederick M. Avolio", "Astrid Lindgren", "Bibhutibhushan Bandopadhyay", "Cornell Woolrich"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sendmail: Theory and Practice?", "answers": ["Paul Vixie", "Bertrand Russell", "William Inge", "Billy Graham"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Yours Forever?", "answers": ["Robin Jones Gunn", "Judy Blume", "Basil Copper", "Don Winslow"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Oedipus the King?", "answers": ["Sophocles", "Katie Davis", "Arthur Balfour", "L. Ron Hubbard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book StrengthsFinder 2.0?", "answers": ["Jacqueline Winspear", "Tom Rath", "James Herriot", "Mark O'Donnell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Riding in Cars with Boys: Confessions of a Bad Girl who Makes Good?", "answers": ["Amely Greeven", "Austin Winsberg", "James Thurber", "Beverly D'Onofrio"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Let the Great World Spin?", "answers": ["Colum McCann", "Nicholas Sparks", "Jeremy Wilson", "Ellen DeGeneres"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Don't Sweat the Small Stuff?", "answers": ["Sri Aurobindo", "Lucy Irvine", "Richard Carlson", "Harlan Ellison"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Charlotte's Rose?", "answers": ["Kevin J. Anderson", "A. E. Cannon", "Robert Penn Warren", "Wallace Thurman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Miss Saigon?", "answers": ["Jeanne Wakatsuki Houston", "Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg", "Neal Shusterman", "Tony Blair"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Miss Saigon?", "answers": ["David Goldblatt", "Alain Boublil", "Dayananda Saraswati", "British Library"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Private Lives?", "answers": ["Jules Verne", "Kirk Mitchell", "No\u00ebl Coward", "Howard Ashman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mockingjay?", "answers": ["Suzanne Collins", "Owen Wister", "Wilbur A. Smith", "Eric Van Lustbader"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Little Birds?", "answers": ["Ana\u00efs Nin", "Sinclair Lewis", "Hesiod", "Lynn Flewelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Logan's Run?", "answers": ["Jean Claverie", "Tom Perrotta", "George Clayton Johnson", "Marshall Barer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Logan's Run?", "answers": ["Grace Metalious", "William F. Nolan", "Devaki Nandan Khatri", "Steven Curtis Chapman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How the Grinch Stole Christmas!?", "answers": ["Pamela Druckerman", "Dr. Seuss", "Katherine Paterson", "Bert V. Royal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Thanatopsis?", "answers": ["T. Colin Campbell", "William Cullen Bryant", "Alexandra Ripley", "David Henry Hwang"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book 1776?", "answers": ["William S. Gray", "Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn", "David Morrell", "Peter Stone"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tropic of Cancer?", "answers": ["Bernard Malamud", "Marcel Proust", "Al Gore", "Henry Miller"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Twelve Angry Men?", "answers": ["Lionel Bart", "Philipp Melanchthon", "Esther Hicks", "Reginald Rose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Carmen?", "answers": ["Susan Hill", "Prosper M\u00e9rim\u00e9e", "Angela Johnson", "Sandra Gilbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Five on a Treasure Island?", "answers": ["Andrew Ross Sorkin", "Baldassare Castiglione", "Matthew Reilly", "Enid Blyton"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fireproof?", "answers": ["Sarah Chauncey Woolsey", "Alice Raymon", "Anne Mazer", "Eric Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Maltese Falcon?", "answers": ["Sri Aurobindo", "Dashiell Hammett", "William Davis", "Reginald Rose"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wolf Hall?", "answers": ["Hilary Mantel", "Bertrand Russell", "Thor Heyerdahl", "Neil Cross"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book King Arthur and His Knights of the Round Table?", "answers": ["Hilary Spurling", "Michel Faber", "Roger Lancelyn Green", "Julie Brady"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Three Musketeers?", "answers": ["Eric L. Haney", "Alexandre Dumas", "Robert James Waller", "Ann Waldron"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book All Summer in a Day?", "answers": ["John Peck", "Lloyd Jones", "Harlan Coben", "Ray Bradbury"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Short Stories by Latin American Women : The Magic and the Real (The Modern Library Classics)?", "answers": ["Aaron Sorkin", "Isabel Allende", "Dante Alighieri", "V\u0101tsy\u0101yana"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book CloudCuckooLand?", "answers": ["Samantha Shannon", "James Hurst", "Augusten Burroughs", "Simon Armitage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Management Information Systems?", "answers": ["Michael Symon", "Johann Christoph Friedrich von Schiller", "R. Kelly Rainer", "Harvey Fierstein"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shatter Me?", "answers": ["Luther Davis", "Frank Herbert", "J. L. Carr", "Tahereh Mafi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book August: Osage County?", "answers": ["Leonard Everett Fisher", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco", "Tracy Letts", "Christopher Hitchens"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Man for All Seasons?", "answers": ["Robert Bolt", "J. A. Jance", "Steve Sheinkin", "Alistair MacLean"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anna of the Five Towns?", "answers": ["Arnold Bennett", "Henri Charri\u00e8re", "Malcolm Lowry", "Jean Webster"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The social contract?", "answers": ["James Dashner", "Jean-Jacques Rousseau", "Daniel Goleman", "Kathryn Erskine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nate the Great?", "answers": ["Carol Sklenicka", "Marjorie W. Sharmat", "Clifford Odets", "Frederic Loewe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Abigail's Party?", "answers": ["Mike Leigh", "L. P. Hartley", "Hubert Horton McAlexander", "David Morrell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tobacco Road?", "answers": ["Nicky Hager", "Primo Levi", "Shelagh Delaney", "Erskine Caldwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anne of Avonlea?", "answers": ["Mary Schmich", "Mark Halperin", "Marguerite Henry", "Lucy Maud Montgomery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sunshine Boys?", "answers": ["Neil Simon", "Eoin Colfer", "Richard Nelson Bolles", "Helene Hanff"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The golden fleece?", "answers": ["Booth Tarkington", "Robert Graves", "John Dempsey", "Stephen J. Dubner"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Foxfire Book?", "answers": ["Foxfire Fund Inc.", "Theodore Taylor", "Robert A. Heinlein", "Robert Newton Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Warriors?", "answers": ["Charlotte Bront\u00eb", "Sol Yurick", "Peter Benchley", "Tony Mendez"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Every Soul a Star?", "answers": ["Wendy Mass", "Lawrence Kasha", "James A. Michener", "Joanne Greenberg"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Seventh Son?", "answers": ["Michelle Gadpaille", "Ira Levin", "Sara Corbett", "Orson Scott Card"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The French Revolution: A History?", "answers": ["Thomas Carlyle", "William Steig", "Samuel Beckett", "Ruta Sepetys"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Infidel?", "answers": ["John Boswell", "Cynthia Lord", "Else Holmelund Minarik", "Ayaan Hirsi Ali"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Talented Mr. Ripley?", "answers": ["Charles Dudley Warner", "Li Cunxin", "Patricia Highsmith", "Eben Alexander"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Agnes Grey?", "answers": ["Joceline Sanschagrin", "John D. Voelker", "Anne Bront\u00eb", "William Diehl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Adi Granth?", "answers": ["Dante Alighieri", "Koushun Takami", "Andrew Carnegie", "Guru Arjan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bel Canto?", "answers": ["Charles Perrault", "Richard Gravil", "Joy Adamson", "Ann Patchett"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hobbit?", "answers": ["J. R. R. Tolkien", "Jonathan Larson", "James Howe", "Annie Jacobsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Snow White?", "answers": ["A. P. J. Abdul Kalam", "Phyllis Reynolds Naylor", "Colin Wilson", "Wilhelm Grimm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Snow White?", "answers": ["K\u00e1roly Pap", "Jules Verne", "Elizabeth George Speare", "Jacob Grimm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Girlfriend in a Coma?", "answers": ["Gene Stone", "Colette", "Douglas Coupland", "Frank McCourt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Emotional Intelligence?", "answers": ["Karen Traviss", "Tatiana De Rosnay", "Sarah Orne Jewett", "Daniel Goleman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book True Colors?", "answers": ["Angela Brown", "Jojo Moyes", "Jacob Grimm", "Kristin Hannah"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Reliable Wife?", "answers": ["Paul Torday", "Clifford Sawhney", "Ben Carson", "Robert Goolrick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Great Santini?", "answers": ["Muriel Spark", "Pat Conroy", "Sebastian Faulks", "Arthur Laurents"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Before sunrise?", "answers": ["Mary Claire Helldorfer", "Curtis Sittenfeld", "David Wood", "Richard Linklater"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Avenue Q?", "answers": ["John Peck", "Jeff Whitty", "Charles Osborne", "Anthony Powell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Everyone Poops?", "answers": ["Taro Gomi", "Richard Condon", "Kathleen Grissom", "Lauren Kate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ode on a Grecian Urn?", "answers": ["John Keats", "Michael Dobbs", "Steven McShane", "Henry Martyn Robert"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Marriage of Figaro?", "answers": ["Lydia Flem", "Pierre de Beaumarchais", "Mary Lewis Wang", "Gerome Ragni"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Barretts of Wimpole Street?", "answers": ["Sebastian Faulks", "Floyd Mutrux", "Sylvia Nasar", "Rudolph Besier"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shakespeare's Ghost Writers?", "answers": ["Carolyn Reeder", "Marjorie Garber", "Walter Dean Myers", "Viktor Frankl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Freakonomics: A Rogue Economist Explores the Hidden Side of Everything?", "answers": ["Desmond Barry", "Jean Giraudoux", "Steven D. Levitt", "Iain Banks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Freakonomics: A Rogue Economist Explores the Hidden Side of Everything?", "answers": ["Jeanne Wakatsuki Houston", "Stephen J. Dubner", "William Gibson", "Aleksandr Pushkin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book East of Eden?", "answers": ["John Steinbeck", "Quentin Tarantino", "Amanda Lindhout", "Jeremy Scahill"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Doctor Faustus?", "answers": ["Howard Fast", "Roald Dahl", "Thomas Mann", "Brad Thor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Vampire Lestat?", "answers": ["Jean Toomer", "Anne Rice", "Seamus Heaney", "Julia Kristeva"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Oblivion: Stories?", "answers": ["Anne Holm", "David Foster Wallace", "Beverly Lyon Clark", "Lloyd Jones"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Wiz?", "answers": ["William F. Brown", "Christopher Collier", "Mickey Rapkin", "W. W. Jacobs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Zeitoun?", "answers": ["Charles Spurgeon", "James Plunkett", "Horace Silver", "Dave Eggers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cape Cod?", "answers": ["Mao Zedong", "Beatrix Potter", "Niccol\u00f2 Machiavelli", "William Martin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Beautyful Ones Are Not Yet Born?", "answers": ["Ayi Kwei Armah", "James Plunkett", "Theodore Taylor", "Amish Tripathi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A White Heron?", "answers": ["Sarah Orne Jewett", "A. J. Cronin", "Ruth Westheimer", "Elizabeth Wurtzel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Giant?", "answers": ["Munro Leaf", "Edna Ferber", "Rex Pickett", "Adeline Yen Mah"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Historical Jesus: A Comprehensive Guide?", "answers": ["Henry Wadsworth Longfellow", "Gerd Theissen", "Theodore Dreiser", "Karel \u010capek"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Drama?", "answers": ["Raina Telgemeier", "H. E. Bates", "Lee Hall", "Eckhart Tolle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cat's Cradle?", "answers": ["Mario Batali", "Bruce Sterling", "Kurt Vonnegut", "Richard Paul Evans"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Citizen Kane: The Complete Screenplay?", "answers": ["Cathy Lamb", "Florence Nightingale", "Adam Parfrey", "Herman J. Mankiewicz"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pete the Cat: I Love My White Shoes?", "answers": ["Katherine Paterson", "Eric Litwin", "Jack Kerouac", "Ovid"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ugly Duckling?", "answers": ["Desiderius Erasmus", "Christopher Paolini", "Hans Christian Andersen", "Ethel Turner"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book God of War?", "answers": ["Louisa May Alcott", "Robert E. Vardeman", "Martin Dugard", "William Henry Hudson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Mayor of Casterbridge: The Life and Death of a Man of Character?", "answers": ["Oliver Goldsmith", "Nathaniel Hawthorne", "Thomas Hardy", "Fran\u00e7ois Rabelais"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Remember This Titan: The Bill Yoast Story - Lessons Learned from a Celebrated Coach's Journey?", "answers": ["Carl Linnaeus", "O. Henry", "H. Richard Hornberger", "Steve Sullivan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Remember This Titan: The Bill Yoast Story - Lessons Learned from a Celebrated Coach's Journey?", "answers": ["Robert Bolt", "Nick Stafford", "Bill Yoast", "Colleen McCullough"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Time Traveler's Wife?", "answers": ["W. Bruce Cameron", "Audrey Niffenegger", "Bankim Chandra Chattopadhyay", "Erle Stanley Gardner"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Blind Side: Evolution of a Game?", "answers": ["Michael Lewis", "Frank Abagnale", "David Henry Hwang", "R. J. Palacio"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sarah\u2019s Key?", "answers": ["R. D. Blackmore", "Aravind Adiga", "Alice Schroeder", "Tatiana De Rosnay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Game of Thrones?", "answers": ["George R. R. Martin", "Arthur Golden", "Christa Faust", "Gary Paulsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Analects?", "answers": ["Paulo Herique", "Kathleen Grissom", "Confucius", "Heinrich B\u00f6ll"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Interview with the Vampire?", "answers": ["Thomas Paine", "Anne Rice", "Bernard Lewis", "R. D. Wingfield"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book First Date the Musical?", "answers": ["David Patterson", "Marsha Norman", "Austin Winsberg", "Rosa Parks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wear Sunscreen?", "answers": ["Sophie Kinsella", "Lauren Kate", "Mary Schmich", "Edwin Meese"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Choke?", "answers": ["Chuck Palahniuk", "Sarah Dessen", "John Heilemann", "Gary Ezzo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Americanization of the World: Or the Trend of the Twentieth Century (1902)?", "answers": ["William Thomas Stead", "Jeffrey Zaslow", "Beatrice Sparks", "Willy Russell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Maniac Magee?", "answers": ["Jerry Spinelli", "Robert Falls", "Daphne du Maurier", "Roland Barthes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stepping Out?", "answers": ["Pope Benedict XVI", "Richard Harris", "Mark Z. Danielewski", "Gore Vidal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Fog?", "answers": ["Dale Wasserman", "Adam Johnson", "James Herbert", "Louisa May Alcott"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Atlantis: The Antediluvian World?", "answers": ["Priscilla Cummings", "Philip Caputo", "K. A. Applegate", "Ignatius L. Donnelly"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Flat Stanley?", "answers": ["Jeff Brown", "Johann Wolfgang von Goethe", "Friedrich Engels", "Sue Grafton"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gulag Archipelago?", "answers": ["Washington", "Katharine Holabird", "Sharon Creech", "Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Centennial?", "answers": ["Anne Fine", "Jon Scieszka", "Jamie Simons", "James A. Michener"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?", "answers": ["Noam Chomsky", "Dana Wilkerson", "Lynda Adamson", "J. K. Rowling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Crispin: The Cross of Lead?", "answers": ["Anne Rivers Siddons", "Leslie Bricusse", "Paramahansa Yogananda", "Edward Irving Wortis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Iron Giant?", "answers": ["Lawrence Kasha", "Ted Hughes", "Anne Fine", "Alain LeRoy Locke"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A psalm of life?", "answers": ["Julia Donaldson", "Sampson Davis", "Anna Quindlen", "Henry Wadsworth Longfellow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Princess Diaries?", "answers": ["Terrance Dicks", "Cornelius Ryan", "James C. Collins", "Meg Cabot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Tale of Love and Darkness?", "answers": ["Slavomir Rawicz", "Amos Oz", "Mariama B\u00e2", "William Easterly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book George's Marvellous Medicine?", "answers": ["Caitlin Moran", "Nevil Shute", "Roald Dahl", "Margret Rey"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Journey's End?", "answers": ["William Luther Pierce", "Bharati Krishna Tirthaji", "R. C. Sherriff", "Lynn Flewelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Principles of Scientific Management?", "answers": ["Greg Farshtey", "Philipp Meyer", "Kate Chopin", "Frederick Winslow Taylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Medea?", "answers": ["Jules Verne", "Euripides", "Fu Xi", "Margaret Atwood"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The secret story of Sonia Rodriguez?", "answers": ["Patricia Cornwell", "Muhammad al-Bukhari", "Lee Hall", "Alan Lawrence Sitomer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ecclesiastical History of the English Nation?", "answers": ["Madeleine L'Engle", "Eugene O'Neill", "Francesca Fremantle", "Bede"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Selfish Gene?", "answers": ["Richard Dawkins", "Eleanor Hibbert", "Tim O'Brien", "Kate Cary"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Babylon Mystery Religion?", "answers": ["William Easterly", "William Saroyan", "James Lapine", "Ralph Woodrow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Roots: The Saga of an American Family?", "answers": ["Stephen Vincent Ben\u00e9t", "Alex Haley", "Herman Koch", "A. N. Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Robin Hood - The Original Classic Edition?", "answers": ["Walter Scott", "Robert Kimmel Smith", "Nicholas Monsarrat", "Paul Creswick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Truman?", "answers": ["Jorge Luis Borges", "David McCullough", "Lala Lajpat Rai", "Gerd Theissen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book They're a Weird Mob?", "answers": ["Carl Hiaasen", "Murasaki Shikibu", "John O'Grady", "Todd Burpo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ethan Frome?", "answers": ["Thomas Hobbes", "Philip Carlo", "Edith Wharton", "Frederick Winslow Taylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Death in the Family?", "answers": ["James Agee", "Ira Wood", "Brian Yorkey", "Sarah Orne Jewett"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chita: a memory of Last Island?", "answers": ["David Wood", "Lafcadio Hearn", "Charles Webb", "David Soman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book On the Road?", "answers": ["Harry Thompson", "Dennis Wainstock", "Jack Kerouac", "Edward Gibbon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lone Survivor: The Eyewitness Account of Operation Redwing and the Lost Heroes of SEAL Team 10?", "answers": ["Sherry Argov", "James A. Michener", "Marcus Luttrell", "Kimon Valaskakis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lone Survivor: The Eyewitness Account of Operation Redwing and the Lost Heroes of SEAL Team 10?", "answers": ["Patrick Robinson", "Nicola Kraus", "Joe Klein", "William Gibson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Killing Kennedy?", "answers": ["Martin Dugard", "Charles Darwin", "Aaron Sorkin", "Ravinder Singh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Killing Kennedy?", "answers": ["Bill O'Reilly", "Richard Carlson", "Johann Christoph Friedrich von Schiller", "William Shakespeare"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blue Ocean Strategy: How to Create Uncontested Market Space and Make Competition Irrelevant?", "answers": ["Timothy Ferriss", "Amely Greeven", "W. Chan Kim", "Richard Nelson Bolles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blue Ocean Strategy: How to Create Uncontested Market Space and Make Competition Irrelevant?", "answers": ["Eric Idle", "Ren\u00e9e Mauborgne", "Rashid-al-Din Hamadani", "Glen Hirshberg"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book No Easy Day?", "answers": ["John D. Voelker", "William Gibson", "Matt Bissonnette", "Shepherd Mead"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book No Easy Day?", "answers": ["William Luther Pierce", "Kevin Maurer", "Michael Ondaatje", "William Faulkner"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tess of the d'Urbervilles?", "answers": ["James A. Michener", "John the Evangelist", "Thomas Hardy", "Alan Dean Foster"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Game Change?", "answers": ["Mark Halperin", "Fran\u00e7oise Sagan", "Gyan C. Jain", "Samuel Shem"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Game Change?", "answers": ["Munshi Premchand", "John Heilemann", "Bret Easton Ellis", "Sir John Retcliffe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Half Broke Horses?", "answers": ["Jeannette Walls", "Patricia Reilly Giff", "Alice Hoffman", "Samuel P. Huntington"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The True Story of the Three Little Pigs?", "answers": ["Ishmael Beah", "Matt Baglio", "Jon Scieszka", "Erich von D\u00e4niken"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The True Story of the Three Little Pigs?", "answers": ["Lane Smith", "Bram Stoker", "Matt Stone", "Susanna Kearsley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Day I Swapped My Dad for Two Goldfish?", "answers": ["Christopher Paolini", "Ted Sorensen", "Donna Tartt", "Neil Gaiman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Contemporary American Short Stories?", "answers": ["Kim Barnouin", "Michael Serra", "Lee Hall", "Douglas Angus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Storm Front?", "answers": ["Wilhelm Grimm", "Jim Jacobs", "Wendy Fonarow", "Richard Castle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gospel According to Mark?", "answers": ["Philippa Gregory", "John Locke", "Jorge Luis Borges", "Marge Piercy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Break with Charity?", "answers": ["J. G. Ballard", "Sofi Oksanen", "E. Annie Proulx", "Ann Rinaldi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pompeii?", "answers": ["Robert Harris", "Willie Nelson", "Eric Blehm", "Kevin Trudeau"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Autobiography of Malcolm X?", "answers": ["British Library", "John-Michael Tebelak", "Janet Evanovich", "Malcolm X"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Autobiography of Malcolm X?", "answers": ["Kate Cary", "John Fowles", "Alex Haley", "Fania Oz-Salzberger"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sound of Thunder?", "answers": ["Wilbur A. Smith", "Joseph Campbell", "Marion Kemp", "Aristophanes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The three billy goats Gruff?", "answers": ["Janet Stevens", "Harvey Diamond", "Joceline Sanschagrin", "James C. Collins"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hairy Maclary from Donaldson's Dairy?", "answers": ["Angela Johnson", "Lynley Dodd", "Bessie Head", "Clifford Odets"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rules?", "answers": ["Beverly D'Onofrio", "Cynthia Lord", "Baldassare Castiglione", "Nan Knighton"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Imitation of Life?", "answers": ["Edwin Meese", "Maggie Stiefvater", "Marsha Norman", "Fannie Hurst"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Put on a Happy Face?", "answers": ["Bill Dedman", "Harriet Beecher Stowe", "Frederick M. Avolio", "Charles Strouse"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Yearling?", "answers": ["Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings", "Gunnar Myrdal", "Cacilda Jeth\u00e1", "James Kirkwood Jr."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The gingerbread man?", "answers": ["Barry Moser", "Eric Kimmel", "Compton Mackenzie", "Dmitry Glukhovsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Bridge Too Far?", "answers": ["Dorothy Fields", "Christopher Paul Curtis", "Cornelius Ryan", "Anne Holm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The New Captain Underpants Collection?", "answers": ["Dav Pilkey", "Merian C. Cooper", "James Herbert", "Margaret Mitchell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How the West Was Won?", "answers": ["Alice Walker", "Neil Cross", "Nicholas Dante", "Louis L'Amour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Prozac Nation?", "answers": ["Anne Mazer", "John Donne", "Elizabeth Wurtzel", "Peter Spier"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The White Queen?", "answers": ["Christopher Paolini", "Samantha Shannon", "Philippa Gregory", "Herodotus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Killer Angels: A Novel of the Civil War?", "answers": ["Tobias Smollett", "Pat Conroy", "Helaine Fendelman", "Michael Shaara"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Harold and the Purple Crayon?", "answers": ["H. P. Lovecraft", "Crockett Johnson", "W. Somerset Maugham", "Louis Fischer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book American Boy?", "answers": ["Robert Thornton Morrison", "Larry Watson", "Joel Shatzky", "Bjarne Stroustrup"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Call of Cthulhu?", "answers": ["Don Winslow", "Arthur C. Clarke", "H. P. Lovecraft", "Cornelia Funke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Red and the Black?", "answers": ["Lois Duncan", "Reinhold Niebuhr", "Rosalind Wiseman", "Stendhal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Faust?", "answers": ["Andy McNab", "Victoria Holmes", "Johann Wolfgang von Goethe", "Jamie McGuire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book To Kill a Mockingbird?", "answers": ["Alyson Noel", "Harper Lee", "Aravind Adiga", "John Bradshaw"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Made of Steel?", "answers": ["John O'Hara", "K\u00e1roly Pap", "Terrance Dicks", "Gabriel Garc\u00eda M\u00e1rquez"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beautiful Bastard?", "answers": ["William D. Cohan", "Tobias Wolff", "Christina Hobbs", "Daniel Handler"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beautiful Bastard?", "answers": ["Harriet Beecher Stowe", "Alice Schroeder", "Lauren Billings", "W. Chan Kim"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court?", "answers": ["Steven Kellogg", "Daniel Quinn", "Mark Twain", "Samuel Taylor Coleridge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Inheritance?", "answers": ["Rustichello da Pisa", "Christopher Paolini", "Richmal Crompton", "Bill Bryson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Few Good Men?", "answers": ["Pervez Musharraf", "Wilbur A. Smith", "Aaron Sorkin", "T. S. Eliot"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Manufacturing Consent: The Political Economy of the Mass Media?", "answers": ["Paulo Coelho", "Nicholas Evans", "Theodore Taylor", "Noam Chomsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Manufacturing Consent: The Political Economy of the Mass Media?", "answers": ["William Martin", "Edward S. Herman", "Edgar Rice Burroughs", "Evelyn Waugh"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book For Whom the Bell Tolls?", "answers": ["J. Alison James", "Bill Gates", "David Remnick", "Ernest Hemingway"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Marathon Man?", "answers": ["Nick Hornby", "John Banville", "William Goldman", "Philip Carlo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Primal Fear?", "answers": ["Simon Armitage", "E.T.A. Hoffmann", "William Diehl", "Halima Bashir"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ishmael?", "answers": ["Daniel Quinn", "Boles\u0142aw Prus", "Amos Oz", "Mike Weiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Too Had a Love Story?", "answers": ["Sylvia Nasar", "Ravinder Singh", "Drew Karpyshyn", "Patrick Rothfuss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Best Russian Short Stories?", "answers": ["Amanda Lindhout", "William Diehl", "Thomas Seltzer", "William Inge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hunger Games?", "answers": ["Euclid", "James Clavell", "James Rado", "Suzanne Collins"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Singularity Is Near?", "answers": ["Diana Wynne Jones", "Ray Kurzweil", "Milton A. Rothman", "D. H. Lawrence"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rights of Man?", "answers": ["Erskine Caldwell", "Thomas Paine", "Sharon Creech", "Kevin J. Anderson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mishnah?", "answers": ["Paul Galdone", "Harlan Ellison", "Judah the Prince", "Truman Capote"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Strumpet City?", "answers": ["Susan Sontag", "James Plunkett", "George Abbott", "Michael Hollinger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Brokeback Mountain?", "answers": ["Rhonda Byrne", "Dalton Trumbo", "E. Annie Proulx", "Amish Tripathi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wizard's First Rule?", "answers": ["Terry Bisson", "Catherine Hapka", "Terry Goodkind", "Linda Woolverton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Silence of the Lambs?", "answers": ["Thomas Harris", "Carson McCullers", "John Peck", "Tim LaHaye"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Clockwork Orange?", "answers": ["Fran\u00e7ois Rabelais", "Eben Alexander", "Betty Mahmoody", "Anthony Burgess"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Shield of Achilles?", "answers": ["Pope Paul VI", "W. H. Auden", "Natalie Standiford", "Lorianne Siomades"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gotcha!?", "answers": ["Bertrand Russell", "Veronica Roth", "Fern Michaels", "Sophocles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Choose Your Own Adventure?", "answers": ["Maurine Dallas Watkins", "James Madison", "Fred Graver", "Stephen Fishman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Water for Elephants?", "answers": ["Peter Barnes", "Sara Gruen", "Bernard Pomerance", "Shelagh Delaney"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tao Te Ching?", "answers": ["John Knowles", "Laozi", "Hal Moore", "Howard E. Wasdin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Patriots Novels Series?", "answers": ["Oscar Wilde", "James Wesley Rawles", "Andrew Clements", "Khalil Gibran"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chicken Little el Cielo Se Esta Cayendo?", "answers": ["Margaret Fuller", "Steven Kellogg", "Dodie Smith", "Tobias Smollett"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Untouchable?", "answers": ["Kami Garcia", "John Banville", "Carolyn Reeder", "Mary Wollstonecraft"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cold Comfort Farm?", "answers": ["Michael Mayer", "William Ernest Henley", "Stella Gibbons", "Cathy Lamb"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tolk\u0101ppiyam?", "answers": ["Tholkappiar", "Shirley Jones", "Colette", "Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Our Town?", "answers": ["L. P. Hartley", "Thornton Wilder", "Sebastian Faulks", "David Goldblatt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Encyclop\u00e9die?", "answers": ["Timothy Ferriss", "Jean le Rond d'Alembert", "Poppy Z. Brite", "Tahir Shah"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Encyclop\u00e9die?", "answers": ["John Berendt", "Eduard Jose", "Thomas C Foster", "Denis Diderot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Christmas Carol?", "answers": ["Matthew Quick", "Erskine Caldwell", "Charles Dickens", "Gregory David Roberts"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A short account of the destruction of the Indies?", "answers": ["Bartolom\u00e9 de Las Casas", "Jack London", "Thomas Carlyle", "Alice Raymon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Azarel?", "answers": ["Albert Facey", "Michael Flatley", "K\u00e1roly Pap", "Jody Rosen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lake House?", "answers": ["Erich Segal", "Nikos Kazantzakis", "George Stanley", "James Patterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The ant and the grasshopper?", "answers": ["Louis Fischer", "Philip K. Dick", "Bari Weissman", "David Benioff"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Guardians of Ga'Hoole: The Journey?", "answers": ["Thomas Malory", "Gore Vidal", "Mary Schmich", "Kathryn Lasky"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The patriot?", "answers": ["Plato", "Stephen Molstad", "Kathryn Erskine", "Jawanza Kunjufu"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Snowman?", "answers": ["Henry Beveridge", "James L. Swanson", "Dan Brown", "Raymond Briggs"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Thin Man?", "answers": ["Dashiell Hammett", "Joe Masteroff", "Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie", "Christopher Brookmyre"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Empire of Dirt?", "answers": ["Wendy Fonarow", "Carson McCullers", "Joel Shatzky", "Roger Sherman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time?", "answers": ["Mitch Albom", "Ken Follett", "Mark Haddon", "Carol Higgins Clark"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Goodnight Moon?", "answers": ["Margaret Wise Brown", "Roald Dahl", "A. C. H. Smith", "Doris Roettger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lonesome Dove?", "answers": ["Joshua Sobol", "Larry McMurtry", "Betty Comden", "David Patterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beau Geste?", "answers": ["L. Frank Baum", "Toni Morrison", "P. C. Wren", "Christopher Brookmyre"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Daniel Deronda?", "answers": ["Gayle Forman", "Dianne Watkins Stuart", "Marshall Barer", "George Eliot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Theogony?", "answers": ["Hesiod", "Don DeLillo", "Ingrid Law", "Jacob Grimm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Franny and Zooey?", "answers": ["Alice Munro", "Manu (Lawgiver)", "J. D. Salinger", "Jos\u00e9 Saramago"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tirukku\u1e5ba\u1e37?", "answers": ["Pierre Choderlos de Laclos", "Patrick Ness", "Rick Warren", "Thiruvalluvar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bridges of Madison County?", "answers": ["Robert James Waller", "Dorothy B. Hughes", "Angela Brown", "Georges Perec"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Coldest Winter Ever?", "answers": ["Eva Ibbotson", "Sister Souljah", "Douglass Wallop", "J. D. Salinger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Day After Tomorrow?", "answers": ["Henry David Thoreau", "Anna Quindlen", "Karma-glin\u0307-pa", "Allan Folsom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Scar Tissue?", "answers": ["Anthony Kiedis", "Diana Gabaldon", "Truman Capote", "Jim Gaffigan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Scar Tissue?", "answers": ["George Vecsey", "Thomas Seltzer", "Larry Sloman", "Mike Leigh"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Things They Carried?", "answers": ["Helen DeWitt", "Tim O'Brien", "Pearl Poet", "Clement Clarke Moore"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Catch-22?", "answers": ["Tony Morden", "Richard Nelson", "Joseph Heller", "Herman J. Mankiewicz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Somewhere in Time?", "answers": ["Rudolph Besier", "Franklin Lacey", "Richard Matheson", "Sol Yurick"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Janice Holt Giles?", "answers": ["Dianne Watkins Stuart", "Will Eisner", "Greil Marcus", "Ron Powers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jack the Giant-Killer?", "answers": ["Bob Thiele", "Marjorie W. Sharmat", "Charles de Lint", "Kate Cary"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Laws of Physics?", "answers": ["Tim O'Brien", "Michelle Knudsen", "Richard Nelson Bolles", "Milton A. Rothman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Notebook & the Wedding?", "answers": ["Malorie Blackman", "Nicholas Sparks", "Laurie Lee", "Pliny the Elder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lord of the Dance?", "answers": ["Martin Seymour-Smith", "Samuel Taylor Coleridge", "Michael Flatley", "William Novak"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Shropshire Lad?", "answers": ["Charles Nordhoff", "Helen Bannerman", "A. E. Housman", "Ida Tarbell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Along Came a Spider?", "answers": ["Alfred Noyes", "Darren Shan", "James Patterson", "Ori Brafman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rocket Boys?", "answers": ["Joe Masteroff", "Donna Tartt", "Alexis de Tocqueville", "Homer Hickam"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book World War Z?", "answers": ["Tom Rob Smith", "Max Brooks", "George Ade", "Jodi Picoult"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The House of God?", "answers": ["Anthony Berkeley Cox", "Samuel Shem", "John Galsworthy", "Robert Edwin Lee"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Judas pig?", "answers": ["Peter Shaffer", "Joseph Robinette", "Horace Silver", "Eddi Fiegel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Clash of Kings?", "answers": ["Harriet Parker", "Darin Strauss", "W.E.B. Du Bois", "George R. R. Martin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Post Office?", "answers": ["E. B. White", "Charles Bukowski", "Fred Graver", "Joe R. Lansdale"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jarhead: A Marine's Chronicle of the Gulf War and Other Battles?", "answers": ["Margaret Floy Washburn", "Anthony Swofford", "Christopher Smart", "Sherman Alexie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gone Girl?", "answers": ["Gillian Flynn", "Willy Russell", "William Bradford", "Stephen Crane"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Princess of Mars?", "answers": ["Thomas Wolfe", "James Alexander Thom", "Michael J. Losier", "Edgar Rice Burroughs"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Life: A User's Manual?", "answers": ["George Eliot", "Michael Shaara", "Pseudonymous Bosch", "Georges Perec"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Storm Front?", "answers": ["William Inge", "Jim Butcher", "Jacqueline Susann", "Leslie Bricusse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Alchemist?", "answers": ["Daniel Goleman", "Paulo Coelho", "Geraint Anderson", "Greg Cox"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Diary of a Wimpy Kid?", "answers": ["Krishna Dharma", "Jeff Kinney", "Danny Wallace", "John L. Hennessy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Into the Wild?", "answers": ["Jon Krakauer", "Darin Strauss", "Kingsley Amis", "Auguste Maquet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Moneyball?", "answers": ["Margaret Edson", "Danae Yankoski", "Nick Hornby", "Michael Lewis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A stroll in the air?", "answers": ["James Plunkett", "Herbert Fields", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco", "James McBride"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Room On The Broom?", "answers": ["Thucydides", "William Styron", "Julia Donaldson", "Fareed Zakaria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Room On The Broom?", "answers": ["Dennis Ritchie", "Axel Scheffler", "Jim Bouton", "Ren\u00e9e Mauborgne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep??", "answers": ["Reza Aslan", "Yasmina Khadra", "Philip K. Dick", "K. A. Applegate"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Big Fish?", "answers": ["Fritjof Capra", "Richard Matheson", "John August", "Samuel Shem"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Thumbelina?", "answers": ["Carlos Ruiz Zaf\u00f3n", "Hans Christian Andersen", "Kingsley Amis", "W. Wilkins"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Miss Viola Swamp?", "answers": ["David Treuer", "Confucius", "James Marshall", "Zelda Fitzgerald"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Miss Viola Swamp?", "answers": ["Margaret Peterson Haddix", "Hugh Johnson", "Todd Strasser", "Harry Allard"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book She Stoops to Conquer?", "answers": ["Solomon Noethup", "Oliver Goldsmith", "Daniel Keyes", "Laura Colker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Year Down Yonder?", "answers": ["Arthur Ransome", "Basil Liddell Hart", "Bob Thiele", "Richard Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Like a rolling stone?", "answers": ["Isabel Allende", "Greil Marcus", "Ben Mezrich", "Sheila Lane"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book What Maisie Knew?", "answers": ["Henry James", "Deborah Smith", "Rick Elice", "Harry Paul"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Robert Ruark's Africa?", "answers": ["Carl Van Vechten", "Stephen Crane", "Robert Ruark", "John Banville"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Robert Ruark's Africa?", "answers": ["Sarah Gilbert", "Michael McIntosh", "Gore Vidal", "Raymond Queneau"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lowland?", "answers": ["Jean Anouilh", "Jhumpa Lahiri", "John Dickinson", "Margery Williams"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wheat Belly?", "answers": ["Barbara A. Shapiro", "The Chew", "William Davis", "Matthew Holm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Free Man of Color?", "answers": ["The Chew", "Barbara Hambly", "Arnold Rampersad", "Jawanza Kunjufu"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to steal a dog?", "answers": ["Robert Southey", "Barbara O'Connor", "Arthur C. Clarke", "Michelle Gadpaille"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Practical Magic?", "answers": ["Ralph Woodrow", "Mary Wollstonecraft", "Arthur Kopit", "Alice Hoffman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Foundations of International Politics?", "answers": ["Jerome Lawrence", "Diana Wynne Jones", "V. C. Andrews", "Harold Hance Sprout"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Harriet's daughter?", "answers": ["M. NourbeSe Philip", "Anna Quindlen", "Devaki Nandan Khatri", "Irving Stone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Graduate?", "answers": ["Kim Carpenter", "Amrita Pritam", "Eric Litwin", "Charles Webb"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Around the World in Eighty Days?", "answers": ["Jules Verne", "Phyllis Reynolds Naylor", "Stephen C. Lundin", "Douglas Angus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Notebook?", "answers": ["Nicholas Sparks", "Jessie Redmon Fauset", "George Howe Colt", "Jacqueline Davies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Love in the Time of Cholera?", "answers": ["Gabriel Garc\u00eda M\u00e1rquez", "Pope Benedict XVI", "Harold Kushner", "Mary Robinette Kowal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Vanished!?", "answers": ["Edmund White", "Danielle Steel", "Eudora Welty", "Guy de Maupassant"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Absolute Power?", "answers": ["Eleanor Estes", "Michael Camille", "David Baldacci", "Terrence McNally"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Absolute Power?", "answers": ["Ray Russell", "Allen C. Guelzo", "Wallace Thurman", "Shehzad Husain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chamber Music?", "answers": ["Arthur Kopit", "Guy Bolton", "Ethel Waters", "Mike Resnick"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cat Sense: How the New Feline Science Can Make You a Better Friend to Your Pet ?", "answers": ["E. M. Forster", "John Bradshaw", "Clive Cussler", "Emma Donoghue"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rules of the Red Rubber Ball?", "answers": ["Kevin Carroll", "Jeff Whitty", "Lionel Bart", "Richard Blackaby"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Language of Flowers?", "answers": ["Helene Hanff", "Helene Hanff", "Vanessa Diffenbaugh", "Brendan Behan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ramayana?", "answers": ["George Abbott", "Valmiki", "Dennis Lehane", "Naoki Higashida"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Separate Peace?", "answers": ["S. A. Bodeen", "L. Frank Baum", "William Boyd", "John Knowles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Norton Anthology of Literature by Women?", "answers": ["Matthew the Apostle", "John Locke", "Joanne Harris", "Sandra Gilbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cranford?", "answers": ["Jane O'Connor", "Elizabeth Gaskell", "Pauline R\u00e9age", "Matthew Gregory Lewis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Skinwalkers?", "answers": ["William Hoffer", "Tony Hillerman", "Jon Ronson", "Michael Falconer Anderson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book James and the Giant Peach?", "answers": ["William Powell", "Jim Butcher", "Marilyn Diamond", "Roald Dahl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Notes on a Scandal?", "answers": ["Zo\u00eb Heller", "Rory Freedman", "Philippa Gregory", "Jason Mott"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sophie's Choice?", "answers": ["David Lodge", "Anthony Powell", "William Styron", "William Ernest Henley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Alice Ramsey's Grand Adventure?", "answers": ["Marianne Williamson", "Joanna C. Galdone", "Don Brown", "Henry David Thoreau"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Letters from a Farmer in Pennsylvania to the Inhabitants of the British Colonies (1903)?", "answers": ["John Dickinson", "Foster W. Cline", "Walt Whitman", "Michael J. Losier"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The crisis?", "answers": ["John Clare", "William Boyd", "Jean Marzollo", "Thomas Paine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tale of Peter Rabbit?", "answers": ["Beatrix Potter", "Robert Barnard", "Barbara Park", "Ian McEwan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Boxcar Children?", "answers": ["Raj\u0101\u02bc \u02bbAbd All\u0101h \u1e62\u0101ni\u02bb", "Thomas \u00e0 Kempis", "Gertrude Chandler Warner", "Boles\u0142aw Prus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ghost Writer?", "answers": ["Jon Scieszka", "Sylvain Reynard", "Philip Roth", "Gavin Maxwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sun Also Rises?", "answers": ["Ernest Hemingway", "Tahir Shah", "Conrad Ferdinand Meyer", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Green Mile?", "answers": ["Marla Heller", "Ptolemy", "Stephen King", "Laurie Lee"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Contest?", "answers": ["Matthew Reilly", "Brian Kernighan", "Robert R. McCammon", "Harry Allard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ecclesiastes?", "answers": ["Michael Jackson", "Solomon", "Thomas Harris", "Patrick J. O'Brian"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Labyrinth?", "answers": ["Max Allan Collins", "A. C. H. Smith", "E. L. James", "Alice Raymon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Spanish Gypsy?", "answers": ["George Eliot", "Tim O'Brien", "Jeff Whitty", "The Chew"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ignited Minds?", "answers": ["Sarah Orne Jewett", "Chaim Potok", "A. P. J. Abdul Kalam", "Bob Fosse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Airport?", "answers": ["Harry Thompson", "James Baldwin", "Nicola Kraus", "Arthur Hailey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Most Dangerous Game?", "answers": ["David McCullough", "Jeannie Gunn", "Larry Watson", "Richard Connell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Scarlet Pimpernel?", "answers": ["Richard Matheson", "Ethel Waters", "Dale Carnegie", "Baroness Emma Orczy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A River Runs Through It?", "answers": ["Ronald David Laing", "Norman Maclean", "Michelle Knudsen", "Shelagh Delaney"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fancy Nancy?", "answers": ["Sattar Memon", "Paul Howard", "Jane O'Connor", "Horace Silver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Winds of War?", "answers": ["Douglas Angus", "Eugene O'Neill", "Robert Edwin Lee", "Herman Wouk"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Source?", "answers": ["John Dos Passos", "A. A. Milne", "James A. Michener", "Mitch Albom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Vagina Monologues?", "answers": ["Madeleine L'Engle", "Jon Scieszka", "Eve Ensler", "Richard Adams"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Twisted?", "answers": ["Homer Hickam", "Alan Moore", "Laurie Halse Anderson", "Sarah Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Never Let Me Go?", "answers": ["Michelle Alexander", "Meg Cabot", "Walter Dean Myers", "Kazuo Ishiguro"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Life?", "answers": ["Bill Clinton", "Catherine Hapka", "Alfred North Whitehead", "Michael Morpurgo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Empire of the Sun?", "answers": ["Ian McEwan", "J. G. Ballard", "Al-Sharif al-Radi", "Howard Lindsay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Under Two Flags?", "answers": ["Philip Carlo", "Khushwant Singh", "Ouida", "Stephen Kendrick"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rape of Nanking: The Forgotten Holocaust of World War II?", "answers": ["Iris Chang", "Helen Schucman", "Bankim Chandra Chattopadhyay", "James McBride"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ender's Game?", "answers": ["Dennis Wainstock", "Orson Scott Card", "Dorothy Wall", "Mary Roach"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fried Green Tomatoes?", "answers": ["Fannie Hurst", "Edward Willett", "Wallace Wattles", "Fannie Flagg"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Last Samurai?", "answers": ["Joe Klein", "Dorothy Wall", "Don Brown", "Helen DeWitt"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Book of Ruth?", "answers": ["Jane Hamilton", "Douglas Carter Beane", "Max Allan Collins", "Robert Goolrick"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Savvy?", "answers": ["Ignatius L. Donnelly", "Thomas More", "James Lincoln Collier", "Ingrid Law"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A World Lit Only by Fire?", "answers": ["Brendan Behan", "Betsy Maestro", "William Manchester", "Sampson Davis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Maru: Roman?", "answers": ["Dennis Kelly", "Bessie Head", "Marco Polo", "Michael Connelly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Johnny Got His Gun?", "answers": ["Betsy Maestro", "Harvey Fierstein", "Dalton Trumbo", "Cecily von Ziegesar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In a Grove?", "answers": ["Susan Beth Pfeffer", "Betty Friedan", "Karen Hesse", "Ryunosuke Akutagawa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Alien?", "answers": ["Tyler Perry", "Kate Mosse", "Alan Dean Foster", "Al Gore"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Master and Commander?", "answers": ["Patrick O'Brian", "Jason Gehlert", "Jonathan Harr", "Michel Faber"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Master and Commander?", "answers": ["Michael Chabon", "Laozi", "Patrick J. O'Brian", "James Baldwin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Will Be Here?", "answers": ["V.S. Naipaul", "Adriana Trigiani", "Steven Curtis Chapman", "Annie Jacobsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Disney Princess Tangled?", "answers": ["Harlan Coben", "Mary Balogh", "Rupert Hart-Davis", "Curtis Sittenfeld"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book No full stops in India?", "answers": ["Milton A. Rothman", "Mark Tully", "Anton Chekhov", "Anthony Berkeley Cox"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pilot's Wife?", "answers": ["Anita Shreve", "Jonathan Safran Foer", "Sebastian Junger", "Ernestine Gilbreth Carey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Divine Comedy?", "answers": ["Dante Alighieri", "Mary Wesley", "Ralph Woodrow", "Alice Sebold"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Passage to India?", "answers": ["Guy Bolton", "Nancy Farmer", "Erich von D\u00e4niken", "E. M. Forster"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rumble Fish?", "answers": ["Poppy Z. Brite", "Louise Fitzhugh", "Stephen Vincent Ben\u00e9t", "S. E. Hinton"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Promise?", "answers": ["Carson McCullers", "Chaim Potok", "Seth Grahame-Smith", "Mahatma Gandhi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Visions of Cody?", "answers": ["James Marshall", "Robert Graves", "Albert Facey", "Jack Kerouac"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Once upon a time in America?", "answers": ["Tatiana De Rosnay", "Erle Stanley Gardner", "Ruth Westheimer", "Adrian Martin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Big Rock Candy Mountain?", "answers": ["P. C. Wren", "Wallace Stegner", "Kevin Carroll", "Charles Frazier"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Big Rock Candy Mountain?", "answers": ["H. A. Rey", "Kimon Valaskakis", "Charles Dickens", "Justin Halpern"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Iron Man?", "answers": ["Bob Woodward", "Nina Simone", "Robert Sobel", "Ted Hughes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Brighton Rock?", "answers": ["Graham Greene", "Philip Wylie", "R. K. Narayan", "Victor Hugo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Liar's Poker: Rising through the Wreckage on Wall Street?", "answers": ["Michael Lewis", "Clive Cussler", "Carl Linnaeus", "Germaine Greer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Drive: The Surprising Truth About What Motivates Us?", "answers": ["Alan Dean Foster", "Lynn Vincent", "Daniel H. Pink", "Henryk Sienkiewicz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hero with a Thousand Faces?", "answers": ["Donald Margulies", "Joseph Campbell", "Irene Mecchi", "Emma Donoghue"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gil Blas?", "answers": ["Jay Asher", "Mary Roach", "Michelle Gadpaille", "Alain-Ren\u00e9 Lesage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Crimson Petal and the White?", "answers": ["Michel Faber", "Howard Ashman", "Richard Nelson Bolles", "Nelson Algren"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone?", "answers": ["Jon Lee Anderson", "Billy Graham", "J. K. Rowling", "W. Somerset Maugham"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Federalist No. 10?", "answers": ["Tracey Garvis-Graves", "Lois Banner", "James Madison", "E. Annie Proulx"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book India Wins Freedom?", "answers": ["James Plunkett", "Barry Moser", "Ron Hall", "Abul Kalam Azad"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Noah's Ark?", "answers": ["Rohinton Mistry", "Anton LaVey", "Kirk Mitchell", "Peter Spier"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book WHEN YOU WISH UPON A STAR (BOOK ONLY)?", "answers": ["Washington", "Gavin Maxwell", "Toni Morrison", "Henri Charri\u00e8re"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jami' al-tawarikh?", "answers": ["Craig Hansen Werner", "Jonathan Swift", "Rashid-al-Din Hamadani", "Lincoln Steffens"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Legally Blonde: The Musical?", "answers": ["Haruki Murakami", "Heather Hach", "James Boswell", "Baldassare Castiglione"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Glass Bead Game?", "answers": ["Hermann Hesse", "Stendhal", "Sebastian Junger", "Rick Riordan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The future of India?", "answers": ["David Henry Hwang", "Federico Garc\u00eda Lorca", "Ann Voskamp", "Bimal Jalan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The 3 Mistakes of My Life?", "answers": ["Franklin Lacey", "Ryunosuke Akutagawa", "Chetan Bhagat", "Jeremy Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A View from the Bridge?", "answers": ["Arthur Miller", "Banjo Paterson", "Sinclair Lewis", "Jim Jacobs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Brother Sam Is Dead?", "answers": ["James Lincoln Collier", "Eric Wilson", "Jeannette Walls", "Pearl Poet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Brother Sam Is Dead?", "answers": ["Jon Lee Anderson", "Christopher Collier", "Michael Hollinger", "Neil Simon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Letters to a young poet?", "answers": ["Rainer Maria Rilke", "Jamie Simons", "Tess Mallos", "Shelagh Delaney"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shades of Milk and Honey?", "answers": ["Libba Bray", "Baldassare Castiglione", "Jessie Redmon Fauset", "Mary Robinette Kowal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Five People You Meet in Heaven?", "answers": ["Aeschylus", "M. NourbeSe Philip", "John O'Hara", "Mitch Albom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Zero Hour?", "answers": ["Basil Copper", "Joseph Finder", "Steven Curtis Chapman", "Milton William Cooper"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Other Europe?", "answers": ["Sheila Quigley", "Craig Brown", "Jacques Rupnik", "Ivan Turgenev"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tale of Mr. Jeremy Fisher?", "answers": ["Anne Rivers Siddons", "Karl Alexander", "Louisa May Alcott", "Beatrix Potter"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Summer Place?", "answers": ["George Harrison", "Sloan Wilson", "Victoria Holmes", "Tracy Letts"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Periodic Table?", "answers": ["Robert Holden", "Robert Boyle", "Jason Mott", "Primo Levi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Maritime fiction?", "answers": ["Kevin Maurer", "John Peck", "Gaston Leroux", "Harriet Martineau"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rosa Parks?", "answers": ["Kurt Vonnegut", "Deborah Smith", "Rosa Parks", "Elizabeth Wurtzel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pact?", "answers": ["Amrita Pritam", "John Reynolds Gardiner", "Thomas Hardy", "Lisa Frazier Page"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pact?", "answers": ["Esphyr Slobodkina", "Rameck Hunt", "Kristin Cashore", "Gail Boushey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pact?", "answers": ["Sampson Davis", "Harlan Ellison", "Tom Wolfe", "Michael McIntosh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Quiet: The Power of Introverts in a World That Can't Stop Talking?", "answers": ["Susan Cain", "Wil Haygood", "Aleister Crowley", "Quiara Alegr\u00eda Hudes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Proof of Heaven: A Neurosurgeon's Near-Death Experience and Journey into the Afterlife?", "answers": ["Chris Ryan", "Jeannette Walls", "Eben Alexander", "Yasmina Khadra"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wonder Boys?", "answers": ["Darren Shan", "Arthur Conan Doyle", "Loretta Lynn", "Michael Chabon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Horrid Henry?", "answers": ["Roger Allers", "Crockett Johnson", "Francesca Simon", "Eudora Welty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Annabel Lee?", "answers": ["William D. Cohan", "Patricia Cornwell", "Edgar Allan Poe", "Clive Cussler"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Theory of Evolution?", "answers": ["Libba Bray", "Maurice Sendak", "Thomas \u00e0 Kempis", "John Maynard Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book King Lear?", "answers": ["William Shakespeare", "Carol Higgins Clark", "Crockett Johnson", "Frederick M. Avolio"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Amadeus?", "answers": ["Wilson Rawls", "Mark Twain", "Rudolph Besier", "Peter Shaffer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chariot of the Gods?", "answers": ["Ira Levin", "Sheila Lane", "Erich von D\u00e4niken", "Arthur Conan Doyle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Five Point Someone?", "answers": ["Jerome Lawrence", "David Remnick", "Betty Mahmoody", "Chetan Bhagat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Eye of the Needle?", "answers": ["Vladimir Vladimirovich Nabokov", "Eben Alexander", "Ken Follett", "William S. Gray"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Secret Garden?", "answers": ["Jerry Spinelli", "Joseph Stein", "Jacques Rupnik", "Frances Hodgson Burnett"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Treasure of the Sierra Madre?", "answers": ["Robert James Waller", "Allen C. Guelzo", "Rashid-al-Din Hamadani", "B. Traven"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The itsy bitsy spider?", "answers": ["Christopher Isherwood", "Julie Taymor", "Lorianne Siomades", "Robert Greene"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Nightingale pledge?", "answers": ["Dadabhai Naoroji", "Florence Nightingale", "David Brauner", "Larry Collins"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Angels & Demons?", "answers": ["Mel Brooks", "Dan Brown", "Mary Lewis Wang", "Anne Rice"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Looking for Alaska?", "answers": ["John Green", "Daniel James Brown", "Belle de Jour", "Luigi Pirandello"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jesus Calling?", "answers": ["Seamus Heaney", "James C. Collins", "Stieg Larsson", "Sarah Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Speedpost?", "answers": ["Shobhaa De", "Drew Karpyshyn", "Henry Beveridge", "Jos\u00e9 Rizal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Daddy-Long-Legs?", "answers": ["Grumpy Cat", "Rufus Jones", "Jean Webster", "Glen Berger"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Thomas the Tank Engine: The Complete Collection?", "answers": ["Reverend W. Awdry", "Barbara Hambly", "Jayne Ann Krentz", "Charles Dudley Warner"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Voice of Israel?", "answers": ["Rick Riordan", "Marissa Meyer", "Barbara Park", "Abba Eban"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Sound of Thunder?", "answers": ["Ray Bradbury", "Susan Beth Pfeffer", "Elmore Leonard", "William P. Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Goal: A Process of Ongoing Improvement?", "answers": ["Eliyahu M. Goldratt", "Michael Brandman", "Daniel Handler", "Christopher Hampton"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Odyssey?", "answers": ["Joan Bauer", "Homer", "Rachel Renee Russell", "Abe Burrows"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Starship Troopers?", "answers": ["Kenneth Oppel", "Hillary Rodham Clinton", "Madeleine L'Engle", "Robert A. Heinlein"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book If You're Happy and You Know It!?", "answers": ["Jan Ormerod", "Jeff Probst", "Micky Dolenz", "Andrew Carnegie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Return of the Native?", "answers": ["Howard Pyle", "Kim Carpenter", "Thomas Hardy", "Brian Kernighan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Return to Love?", "answers": ["Ernest Thayer", "Malcolm Lowry", "Marianne Williamson", "Colleen McCullough"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Little Boy Lost?", "answers": ["Marghanita Laski", "Robert A. Heinlein", "Jim Butcher", "Henri Charri\u00e8re"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Agatha Christie bibliography?", "answers": ["Solomon", "Bartolom\u00e9 de Las Casas", "Jos\u00e9 Rizal", "Agatha Christie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sandman?", "answers": ["Pierre Choderlos de Laclos", "E.T.A. Hoffmann", "Heather Hach", "Wendy Fonarow"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stranger in a Strange Land?", "answers": ["Wil Haygood", "Robert A. Heinlein", "Haylie Pomroy", "Berry Gordy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The missing 'gator of Gumbo Limbo?", "answers": ["Thomas C Foster", "Jean Craighead George", "Frank Herbert", "Washington Irving"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Al Capone Does My Shirts?", "answers": ["Gennifer Choldenko", "Edward Irving Wortis", "Jos\u00e9 Rizal", "Michael Jackson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Revenge of the Wannabes?", "answers": ["Lisi Harrison", "Lurlene McDaniel", "Sun Tzu", "Betty Friedan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Walk in the Clouds?", "answers": ["Mike Resnick", "Diane Trister. Dodge", "Ray Russell", "Deborah Chiel"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Native American Fiction?", "answers": ["Harold Robbins", "Petrarch", "David Treuer", "John Bunyan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Naked?", "answers": ["Stieg Larsson", "Donna Diamond", "David Sedaris", "Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Go the Fuck to Sleep?", "answers": ["George Gipe", "Adam Mansbach", "Eleanor Hibbert", "Sigmund Freud"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Brideshead Revisited?", "answers": ["Anton Chekhov", "Evelyn Waugh", "George Abbott", "Shrikant G. Talageri"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beastly?", "answers": ["Shelagh Delaney", "Alex Flinn", "Michael Hollinger", "Lucy Maud Montgomery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book When Bad Things Happen to Good People?", "answers": ["Ben Okri", "George Abbott", "Harold Kushner", "Charles Reade"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book House of Darkness House of Light: The True Story Volume One?", "answers": ["Leslie Bricusse", "Lawrence Kasha", "Andrea Perron", "Amador Taguinod Daguio"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lawrence of Arabia: The Authorised Biography of T.E. Lawrence?", "answers": ["Andrew S. Tanenbaum", "Edward Lear", "Jeremy Wilson", "Larry McMurtry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Love Can Build a Bridge?", "answers": ["Naomi Judd", "Krishna Dharma", "Jean Claverie", "John Ajvide Lindqvist"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Filth?", "answers": ["Gregory Maguire", "Eugene O'Neill", "Confucius", "Irvine Welsh"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hawaii?", "answers": ["Ouida", "Michael Cunningham", "Mark Kurlansky", "James A. Michener"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Inkheart?", "answers": ["Cornelia Funke", "Sue Grafton", "Daniel Silva", "Rob Grant"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Doll's House?", "answers": ["Whitney Stewart", "Jane Green", "Barbara Taylor Bradford", "Henrik Ibsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Second Nun's Tale?", "answers": ["Robert Reich", "Jerzy Kosi\u0144ski", "George Ella Lyon", "Geoffrey Chaucer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Boy and His Dog?", "answers": ["Harlan Ellison", "Cheryl Wall", "Eric Van Lustbader", "Crockett Johnson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Something Wicked This Way Comes?", "answers": ["Ray Bradbury", "Michael Ende", "Paul Galdone", "Jay Thompson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Amelia Bedelia?", "answers": ["Peggy Parish", "Diana Hacker", "Thomas Carlyle", "Jagmohan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Crazy?", "answers": ["Boris Pasternak", "Greg Cox", "Dick Roughsey", "Pete Earley"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Les Mis\u00e9rables?", "answers": ["Roland Barthes", "Banjo Paterson", "Sheila Lane", "Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Les Mis\u00e9rables?", "answers": ["Louis de Berni\u00e8res", "Justin Halpern", "Jamie McGuire", "Alain Boublil"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Antigone?", "answers": ["Conrad Ferdinand Meyer", "Michael Cunningham", "Sergey Lukyanenko", "Sophocles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Decameron?", "answers": ["Jonathan Larson", "Giovanni Boccaccio", "Mary Carter", "Doreen Cronin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Storybook Treasury of Dick and Jane and Friends?", "answers": ["A. C. H. Smith", "William Henry Hudson", "Lois Duncan", "William S. Gray"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Six Characters in Search of an Author?", "answers": ["Mario Puzo", "Lynda Adamson", "William Makepeace Thackeray", "Luigi Pirandello"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Odessa File?", "answers": ["Ralph Ellison", "Tim Rice", "Rabindranath Tagore", "Frederick Forsyth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Big Stone Gap: Big Cherry Holler ; Milk Glass Moon?", "answers": ["David Lindsay-Abaire", "Adriana Trigiani", "Alfred Uhry", "Roark Bradford"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Life As We Knew It?", "answers": ["John Guare", "Susan Beth Pfeffer", "Clive Cussler", "Basil Copper"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Moloka'i?", "answers": ["Alan Brennert", "John Locke", "Jenny Downham", "L. P. Hartley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Little Prince?", "answers": ["Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry", "James Dickey", "Ted Sorensen", "Jordan Belfort"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Meditations on the Tarot?", "answers": ["Lafcadio Hearn", "Murasaki Shikibu", "Anonymous", "Anthony Berkeley Cox"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Billy Budd?", "answers": ["Herman Melville", "Elizabeth George Speare", "Beatrix Potter", "E. M. Forster"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nineteen Eighty-Four?", "answers": ["Kate DiCamillo", "Rick Warren", "Robert Newton Peck", "George Orwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Monkey's Paw?", "answers": ["W. W. Jacobs", "Rupert Hart-Davis", "Iris Johansen", "John Donne"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cheaper by the Dozen?", "answers": ["Al-Sharif al-Radi", "Abul Kalam Azad", "Ernestine Gilbreth Carey", "Patrick O'Brian"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Federalist Papers?", "answers": ["Deja King", "John Jay", "Bill Dedman", "Alvin Schwartz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Federalist Papers?", "answers": ["Countee Cullen", "James Madison", "Fannie Flagg", "Tom Angleberger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Federalist Papers?", "answers": ["Pervez Musharraf", "Alexander Hamilton", "Samuel Shem", "Whitney Stewart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Know What You Did Last Summer?", "answers": ["Valmiki", "Lois Duncan", "H. E. Bates", "Margaret Peterson Haddix"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Giraffes can't dance?", "answers": ["Giles Andreae", "Max Brooks", "Alice Munro", "Steve Eng"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dead Souls?", "answers": ["Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings", "William Shakespeare", "Nikolai Gogol", "A. J. Quinnell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Scanner Darkly?", "answers": ["Philip K. Dick", "William Styron", "Joy Adamson", "Thomas \u00e0 Kempis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Breakfast at Tiffany's?", "answers": ["Jonathan Safran Foer", "Truman Capote", "Pearl S. Buck", "Diana Hacker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Borstal Boy?", "answers": ["Richard Bach", "Mark Haddon", "Brendan Behan", "Walter Dean Myers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book As I Lay Dying?", "answers": ["William Faulkner", "Lurlene McDaniel", "Stephen Molstad", "Louise Fitzhugh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fingersmith?", "answers": ["V\u0101tsy\u0101yana", "Stephen Mallatratt", "Sarah Waters", "Greil Marcus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Joy of Sex?", "answers": ["Edgar Allan Poe", "Lane Smith", "Alex Comfort", "Narmad\u0101pras\u0101da Up\u0101dhy\u0101ya"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book What Color is Your Parachute??", "answers": ["Devaki Nandan Khatri", "Piers Paul Read", "Sophocles", "Richard Nelson Bolles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Catch Me if You Can?", "answers": ["W. Bruce Cameron", "Basil Copper", "Stan Redding", "Bimal Jalan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Catch Me if You Can?", "answers": ["Jean Toomer", "Frank Abagnale", "Flannery O'Connor", "Rabindranath Tagore"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lajja?", "answers": ["George Samuel Clason", "George Vecsey", "Marianne Williamson", "Taslima Nasrin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Paperboy?", "answers": ["Pete Dexter", "Judah the Prince", "Julia Kristeva", "Guy Bolton"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Red Pony?", "answers": ["Robert Bloch", "John Steinbeck", "Tyler Perry", "Tom Perrotta"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Simple Plan?", "answers": ["Kim Carpenter", "Thomas Hardy", "Scott Smith", "Lisa Genova"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Seven Summers: The Story of an Indian Childhood?", "answers": ["Charles T. Horngren", "Lane Becker", "Mulk Raj Anand", "Aldous Huxley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The discovery of India?", "answers": ["Kim Carpenter", "Jawaharlal Nehru", "Prosper M\u00e9rim\u00e9e", "Ron Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stranger than Fiction: True Stories?", "answers": ["Richard Herrnstein", "Howard E. Wasdin", "John Gunther", "Chuck Palahniuk"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kensuke's Kingdom?", "answers": ["Ernest Cline", "Michael Morpurgo", "A. C. H. Smith", "Katherine Paterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Story of an Hour?", "answers": ["Billie Letts", "Kate Chopin", "Mark Ribowsky", "William Landay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In the Line of Fire: A Memoir?", "answers": ["Pervez Musharraf", "Tim Tharp", "Gabrielle-Suzanne Barbot de Villeneuve", "George Abbott"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Thomas the Tank Engine?", "answers": ["Reverend W. Awdry", "Ingrid Law", "Julie Smith", "Julian Fellowes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Winter's Bone?", "answers": ["Loretta Lynn", "Elizabeth Barrett Browning", "Daniel Woodrell", "Stephen Crane"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil?", "answers": ["Stephen J. Dubner", "Lois Duncan", "Daniel Wallace", "John Berendt"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark?", "answers": ["Julie Taymor", "Judah the Prince", "Jo Swerling", "Miguel de Cervantes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark?", "answers": ["Curt Gentry", "Matt Baglio", "Glen Berger", "Mark Twain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark?", "answers": ["Euripides", "Kenneth Grahame", "Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa", "Markus Zusak"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Uncle Tom's Cabin?", "answers": ["Harriet Beecher Stowe", "E. Annie Proulx", "Cassandra Golds", "Ori Brafman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Before I Go to Sleep?", "answers": ["Peter S. Beagle", "S. J. Watson", "Koushun Takami", "Mario Batali"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Boy at War?", "answers": ["Sheryl WuDunn", "Anne Rice", "John Galsworthy", "Harry Mazer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ball Four?", "answers": ["Flora Rheta Schreiber", "Jim Bouton", "Glen Rounds", "Katherine Anne Porter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Robin Hood and His Adventures?", "answers": ["Paul Fleischman", "Thomas Carlyle", "Paul Creswick", "Mark Driscoll"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Short Account of the Destruction of the Indies?", "answers": ["Bartolom\u00e9 de Las Casas", "William Martin", "Michael Falconer Anderson", "William Dean Howells"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gone?", "answers": ["Michael Grant", "Phyllis Reynolds Naylor", "Jojo Moyes", "Barbara Taylor Bradford"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pillars of the Earth?", "answers": ["Ken Follett", "Dorothy B. Hughes", "Petrarch", "Arna Bontemps"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Flags of Our Fathers?", "answers": ["Jan Ormerod", "Rosalind Wiseman", "James Bradley", "Gillian Flynn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Flags of Our Fathers?", "answers": ["Russel Crouse", "Sean Hannity", "Ron Powers", "Anita Loos"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rising Sun?", "answers": ["Robert Munsch", "Jagmohan", "Robert Frost", "Michael Crichton"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bluebeard?", "answers": ["Melanie Hauser", "Langston Hughes", "Mary Chase", "Jean Claverie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bluebeard?", "answers": ["Charles Perrault", "Jean-Paul Sartre", "Alice Hoffman", "Marcus Luttrell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chocolat?", "answers": ["Carolyn Reeder", "Joanne Harris", "Arthur Ransome", "Erich Maria Remarque"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peter Pan?", "answers": ["J. M. Barrie", "Barack Obama", "Stephen Chbosky", "Ira Wood"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Foucault's Pendulum?", "answers": ["Umberto Eco", "Dick Roughsey", "Carlo Collodi", "Alice Walker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Love You Forever?", "answers": ["Heidi Murkoff", "W. W. Jacobs", "Dianne Watkins Stuart", "Robert Munsch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hannibal?", "answers": ["Nirad C. Chaudhuri", "Thomas Harris", "Caralyn Buehner", "Alastair Fowler"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Misanthrope?", "answers": ["Moli\u00e8re", "Jules Verne", "Howard Pyle", "Mark Driscoll"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Reason I Jump: The Inner Voice of a Thirteen-Year-Old Boy with Autism?", "answers": ["Paul Fleischman", "Katherine Paterson", "Naoki Higashida", "Richard Matheson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lost Boys?", "answers": ["Christopher Hampton", "J. J. Virgin", "Orson Scott Card", "Ayaan Hirsi Ali"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Study in Scarlet?", "answers": ["Jack London", "Arthur Conan Doyle", "Michel Faber", "James Patterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Be Here Now?", "answers": ["Ram Dass", "Billie Joe Armstrong", "Muhammad al-Bukhari", "Edmond Halley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How Far We Slaves Have Come!?", "answers": ["Fidel Castro", "Li Cunxin", "Esther Hicks", "Devaki Nandan Khatri"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How Far We Slaves Have Come!?", "answers": ["Adam Parfrey", "Alvin Toffler", "Nelson Mandela", "James Bradley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Parenting With Love And Logic?", "answers": ["Pope Benedict XVI", "Robert Barnard", "C. S. Godshalk", "Foster W. Cline"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to Archer?", "answers": ["Clifford Odets", "Sterling Archer", "Ian McEwan", "Billie Joe Armstrong"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Silver Sword?", "answers": ["Eckhart Tolle", "Alfred Uhry", "Ian Serraillier", "Christopher Hampton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Illustrated Man?", "answers": ["Karen Hesse", "Ray Bradbury", "Henry David Thoreau", "Carol Sklenicka"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The boy who cried wolf?", "answers": ["Christy Brown", "B. G. Hennessy", "William Shakespeare", "Theresa Karas Yianilos"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A song for you?", "answers": ["Betty Comden", "Dylan Thomas", "Betsy Thornton", "Harold Kushner"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blindness?", "answers": ["Jos\u00e9 Saramago", "W. Somerset Maugham", "Carl Hiaasen", "Jacques Rupnik"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Spring Awakening?", "answers": ["Virginia Woolf", "Adolph Green", "Michael Shaara", "Steven Sater"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Discovery of India?", "answers": ["Jawaharlal Nehru", "Marjorie W. Sharmat", "George Samuel Clason", "Janet Stevens"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Heartbreaking Work of Staggering Genius?", "answers": ["Albert Facey", "Bill Clinton", "Adriana Trigiani", "Dave Eggers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Why True Love Waits: The Definitive Book on How to Help Your Kids Resist Sexual Pressure?", "answers": ["Barbara Hambly", "Bharati Krishna Tirthaji", "Josh McDowell", "Edgar Allan Poe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pursuit of Happyness?", "answers": ["Devaki Nandan Khatri", "Jerry Hicks", "Chris Gardner", "Guy de Maupassant"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Les Mis\u00e9rables?", "answers": ["Phyllis Reynolds Naylor", "Victor Hugo", "David Baldacci", "Amely Greeven"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Far from the Madding Crowd?", "answers": ["Don Brown", "Iris Murdoch", "Thomas Hardy", "Christopher Ryan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cats?", "answers": ["Theodor Mommsen", "Helaine Fendelman", "Joe McGinniss", "T. S. Eliot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Kennedy legacy?", "answers": ["Christopher McDougall", "Percy Bysshe Shelley", "Gail Boushey", "Ted Sorensen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book What Went Wrong?", "answers": ["Ryunosuke Akutagawa", "Marcia Brown", "Bernard Lewis", "Stephen W. Garber"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Them?", "answers": ["Ana\u00efs Nin", "Kim Barnouin", "Nirad C. Chaudhuri", "Joyce Carol Oates"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Chosen?", "answers": ["John Wyndham", "Sara Shepard", "Chaim Potok", "Christina Hobbs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The King and I?", "answers": ["Robert Reich", "Oscar Hammerstein II", "Cecil Murphey", "Pearl S. Buck"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wintergirls?", "answers": ["John Boswell", "Francis Lathom", "Laurie Halse Anderson", "William Nack"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Name of the Rose?", "answers": ["Umberto Eco", "Todd Burpo", "Susanna Kearsley", "Wally Lamb"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pippin?", "answers": ["Wallace Stegner", "Lew Wallace", "Laurie Lee", "Roger O. Hirson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Return to Eden?", "answers": ["Trent Lott", "Rosalind Miles", "Thor Muller", "James Patterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Complete Anne of Green Gables Boxed Set?", "answers": ["Margaret Fuller", "Lucy Maud Montgomery", "Daniel Handler", "Rick Elice"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Void?", "answers": ["Richard Dawkins", "Georges Perec", "Tony Morden", "Arthur Kopit"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Highwayman?", "answers": ["Alfred Noyes", "F. Scott Fitzgerald", "Alistair MacLean", "Frederick Forsyth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book City of God?", "answers": ["Sogyal Rinpoche", "Augustine of Hippo", "James M. Cain", "Ian Rankin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bravo Two Zero?", "answers": ["Andy McNab", "The Chew", "Herodotus", "Aristophanes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bus Stop?", "answers": ["Harry Allard", "William Inge", "W. Bruce Cameron", "Napoleon Hill"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Am Legend?", "answers": ["Harry Mazer", "Jerry B. Jenkins", "Beryl Markham", "Richard Matheson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Funny Thing Is...?", "answers": ["Carlos Ruiz Zaf\u00f3n", "Ellen DeGeneres", "Oscar Wilde", "Mary Robinette Kowal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Casey at the Bat?", "answers": ["Naoki Higashida", "Ernest Thayer", "Megan McDonald", "Alcoholics Anonymous"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shrek the Musical?", "answers": ["Francine Rivers", "Charles A. Murray", "David Lindsay-Abaire", "Robert Boyle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sharp Objects?", "answers": ["Erle Stanley Gardner", "Ronald David Laing", "Gillian Flynn", "Ann Patchett"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Long Walk to Freedom?", "answers": ["Nelson Mandela", "D. H. Lawrence", "Lorianne Siomades", "H. G. Wells"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The White Tiger: A Novel?", "answers": ["Allan Knee", "Ridley Pearson", "Aravind Adiga", "Alejandro Junger"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mystic River?", "answers": ["Wilbur A. Smith", "Alice Hoffman", "Heidi Murkoff", "Dennis Lehane"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Where's Wally??", "answers": ["Francesca Simon", "Elizabeth Strout", "James Clavell", "Martin Handford"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Andersonville?", "answers": ["Farhat Ishtiaq", "MacKinlay Kantor", "Berry Gordy", "Jacques Rupnik"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Metro 2033?", "answers": ["Dmitry Glukhovsky", "Aristotle", "Nancy Milford", "Matthew Bourne"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book 777 and Other Qabalistic Writings of Aleister Crowley?", "answers": ["Catherine Johnson", "B. Traven", "Aleister Crowley", "Richard Preston"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Let Freedom Ring: Winning the War of Liberty over Liberalism?", "answers": ["Eddi Fiegel", "Daniel Silva", "Meg Cabot", "Sean Hannity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Virginian?", "answers": ["Mike Weiss", "Harold Hance Sprout", "Irving Shulman", "Owen Wister"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sliver?", "answers": ["Michael Dobbs", "Ira Levin", "Suzanne Collins", "William Boyd"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Thirteen Reasons Why?", "answers": ["William Goldman", "Jerry Spinelli", "Narmad\u0101pras\u0101da Up\u0101dhy\u0101ya", "Jay Asher"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Americanah?", "answers": ["Aristophanes", "Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie", "Laura Hillenbrand", "Aryabhata"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The French Lieutenant's Woman?", "answers": ["John Fowles", "Erica Jong", "T. Coraghessan Boyle", "Janet Stevens"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Original Alice in Wonderland?", "answers": ["Lawrence Hill", "Julia Donaldson", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel", "Lewis Carroll"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sight Unseen?", "answers": ["Carson McCullers", "George Bernard Shaw", "Merriam-Webster", "Donald Margulies"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Captain Corelli's Mandolin?", "answers": ["Billie Letts", "Geoffrey Chaucer", "Thomas Kyd", "Louis de Berni\u00e8res"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Philosophi\u00e6 Naturalis Principia Mathematica?", "answers": ["Jeanne DuPrau", "Lloyd D. Newell", "J. G. Ballard", "Isaac Newton"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Great and Terrible Beauty?", "answers": ["Aeschylus", "Libba Bray", "Margaret Mitchell", "Nancy Milford"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Heart of Darkness?", "answers": ["Richard Paul Evans", "Craig Brown", "Dorothy B. Hughes", "Joseph Conrad"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hard Times?", "answers": ["Harriet Beecher Stowe", "Mark Ribowsky", "Bob Thiele", "Charles Dickens"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Severed Head: Capital Visions?", "answers": ["Sue Grafton", "Eileen Christelow", "Louisa May Alcott", "Julia Kristeva"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book North and South?", "answers": ["K. A. Applegate", "Roger Zelazny", "Elizabeth Gaskell", "Arthur Whitelaw"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to Read a Book?", "answers": ["Lynn Vincent", "Jay Asher", "Charles Van Doren", "Isabel Allende"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to Read a Book?", "answers": ["Edward Willett", "Pseudonymous Bosch", "Mortimer J. Adler", "Lew Wallace"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The History of the Peloponnesian War?", "answers": ["Raina Telgemeier", "Victor Hugo", "Stephen C. Lundin", "Thucydides"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Mousetrap?", "answers": ["Robert Edwin Lee", "David Auburn", "Agatha Christie", "Michael Symon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Daily Five?", "answers": ["Tom Jones", "Patricia Reilly Giff", "Joe R. Lansdale", "Gail Boushey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Razor's Edge?", "answers": ["Crockett Johnson", "W. Somerset Maugham", "Raymond Chandler", "Paulo Lins"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dragon Rider?", "answers": ["Cornelia Funke", "Gordon Elliott", "Stephen Mallatratt", "Sun Tzu"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Sister's Keeper?", "answers": ["James Fenimore Cooper", "Margret Rey", "Jodi Picoult", "Erskine Caldwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Eagle Has Landed?", "answers": ["Helen Prejean", "Jack Higgins", "John Grisham", "Mazarine Pingeot"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Waiting for Lefty?", "answers": ["Phoebe Atwood Taylor", "Joanne Greenberg", "Bret Harte", "Clifford Odets"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The bear?", "answers": ["Baldassare Castiglione", "William Faulkner", "Halima Bashir", "Ray Kurzweil"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sahara Romanzo?", "answers": ["Kristin Cashore", "Kenneth Tynan", "Clive Cussler", "Ted Sorensen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dear John?", "answers": ["James Kirkwood Jr.", "Beatrix Potter", "Nicholas Sparks", "Stephen Templin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Apology?", "answers": ["Natalie Standiford", "Plato", "Justin Halpern", "Sister Souljah"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Defending Jacob?", "answers": ["Jerry B. Jenkins", "William Landay", "Louisa May Alcott", "H. Richard Hornberger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Paul Revere's ride?", "answers": ["Jeffrey Zaslow", "Henry Wadsworth Longfellow", "Henry Bellamann", "Nathan Myhrvold"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rob Roy?", "answers": ["Sonya Hartnett", "Charles A. Murray", "Walter Scott", "Henryk Sienkiewicz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A place to call home?", "answers": ["Piers Anthony", "Deborah Smith", "David Nicholls", "Friedrich Engels"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Mystery of Heroism?", "answers": ["Mark Z. Danielewski", "Samuel P. Huntington", "Sigmund Freud", "Stephen Crane"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book India of my dreams?", "answers": ["Mahatma Gandhi", "Slavomir Rawicz", "James Weldon Johnson", "Mortimer J. Adler"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fit for Life: A New Beginning: The Ultimate Diet and Health Plan?", "answers": ["Martin Handford", "Harvey Diamond", "Joe Klein", "Christopher Hitchens"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Patriot Games?", "answers": ["Nicole Mones", "Ruth Stiles Gannett", "Tom Clancy", "Joe McGinniss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book One Day?", "answers": ["Mark Driscoll", "Albert Camus", "Alex Garland", "David Nicholls"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Opus?", "answers": ["James Agee", "Michael Hollinger", "Irving Stone", "Alistair MacLean"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Black Betty?", "answers": ["Christy Brown", "Walter Mosley", "Anne Fine", "Scott Turow"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The One Minute Manager?", "answers": ["Dave Pelzer", "Fred Kaplan", "Scott Turow", "Ken Blanchard"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lincoln Lawyer?", "answers": ["Michael Connelly", "Amanda Brown", "Nicola Kraus", "Bell Hooks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde?", "answers": ["Robert Louis Stevenson", "Johann Wolfgang von Goethe", "Nicolaus Copernicus", "Howard E. Wasdin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Streams in the Desert: Hope for Hurting Hearts?", "answers": ["L. B. Cowman", "P. D. Eastman", "Edward Willett", "Harold Kushner"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Death and Life of Charlie St. Cloud?", "answers": ["Timothy Ferriss", "David Oliver Relin", "Ben Sherwood", "Allen Ginsberg"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Naked Lunch?", "answers": ["P\u0101\u1e47ini", "William S. Burroughs", "Ouida", "Pittacus Lore"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peer Gynt?", "answers": ["Marsha Norman", "Jon Ronson", "Warren Lockhart", "David Henry Hwang"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kissed by an Angel Collector's Edition?", "answers": ["Quiara Alegr\u00eda Hudes", "Stendhal", "Pittacus Lore", "Mary Claire Helldorfer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Grey Wolf: The Escape of Adolf Hitler : the Case Presented?", "answers": ["Harlan Coben", "Howard Pyle", "Simon Dunstan", "Trent Lott"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Middlesex?", "answers": ["Rainer Maria Rilke", "David A. Adler", "Joe Klein", "Jeffrey Eugenides"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Secret?", "answers": ["Lloyd Jones", "Angela Johnson", "Rhonda Byrne", "John Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Orange Is the New Black: My Year in a Women's Prison?", "answers": ["Kinky Friedman", "Hesiod", "C. S. Godshalk", "Piper Kerman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Freedom from Fear?", "answers": ["Wayne Short", "Aung San Suu Kyi", "Muslim ibn al-Hajjaj", "Rebecca Skloot"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Carousel?", "answers": ["Oscar Hammerstein II", "Philip Carlo", "Khushwant Singh", "Bobby Lynn Maslen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Alice Adams?", "answers": ["Robert Frost", "Leonard Everett Fisher", "Richard Linklater", "Booth Tarkington"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wonder?", "answers": ["R. J. Palacio", "Mitch Albom", "Michael Dorris", "Charles W. Chesnutt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The selfish giant?", "answers": ["Murasaki Shikibu", "Oscar Wilde", "Marshall Barer", "Luigi Pirandello"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Arms and the Man?", "answers": ["George Bernard Shaw", "Wil Haygood", "M. Scott Peck", "Christina Crawford"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Grapes of Wrath?", "answers": ["Lynn Vincent", "Helaine Fendelman", "Billie Joe Armstrong", "John Steinbeck"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Long Walk?", "answers": ["Val McDermid", "Stephen Crane", "Elie Wiesel", "Slavomir Rawicz"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Airborn?", "answers": ["Jane O'Connor", "George Gipe", "David Wong", "Kenneth Oppel"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Malgudi days?", "answers": ["Charles Osborne", "Sara Gruen", "R. K. Narayan", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Saturday Night Fever?", "answers": ["Barthe DeClements", "Arthur Kopit", "Nan Knighton", "Robert Thornton Morrison"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Time Machine?", "answers": ["Michelle Alexander", "H. G. Wells", "Kathryn Stockett", "Mary Roach"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Deck the Halls?", "answers": ["Adam Johnson", "Beryl Gilroy", "Aleister Crowley", "Mary Higgins Clark"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Deck the Halls?", "answers": ["Simone Elkeles", "Jason Gehlert", "Marco Polo", "Carol Higgins Clark"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mao's Last Dancer?", "answers": ["Li Cunxin", "Harry Turtledove", "Axel Scheffler", "Robert Southey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Robert's Rules of Order?", "answers": ["Henry Martyn Robert", "Thor Heyerdahl", "Jim Bouton", "Sue Monk Kidd"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Operation Spy School?", "answers": ["George Stanley", "Thomas Kyd", "Sharon Draper", "Barack Obama"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Eldorado?", "answers": ["Shepherd Mead", "Edgar Allan Poe", "Mike Weiss", "Allen Ginsberg"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harbinger?", "answers": ["Jonathan Cahn", "Murasaki Shikibu", "Katharine Holabird", "Terry Goodkind"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Two Treatises of Government?", "answers": ["Dan Poynter", "Kami Garcia", "Robert A. Heinlein", "John Locke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The importance of being earnest?", "answers": ["George Langelaan", "Gunnar Myrdal", "Arthur Hailey", "Charles Osborne"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Historia Regum Britanniae?", "answers": ["Geoffrey of Monmouth", "Michael Serra", "Jack London", "Steven Curtis Chapman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Black Girl in Search of God?", "answers": ["Ernest Hemingway", "Kate DiCamillo", "George Bernard Shaw", "Dylan Thomas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Vow: The True Events That Inspired the Movie?", "answers": ["Wendy Fonarow", "L. Frank Baum", "Krickitt Carpenter", "Liz Tuccillo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Vow: The True Events That Inspired the Movie?", "answers": ["Henry Williamson", "Alexandre Dumas", "Dana Wilkerson", "Eva Ibbotson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Vow: The True Events That Inspired the Movie?", "answers": ["Charlotte Perkins Gilman", "Jorge Luis Borges", "Kim Carpenter", "Roald Dahl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Passage?", "answers": ["Justin Cronin", "Margret Rey", "Kathryn Erskine", "John-Michael Tebelak"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Life and Loves of a She-Devil?", "answers": ["Darin Strauss", "Richard Wright", "Fay Weldon", "Michael Mayer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Zorro?", "answers": ["Isabel Allende", "Doris Pilkington Garimara", "William Ernest Henley", "Trey Parker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book About a Boy?", "answers": ["A. S. Byatt", "Valmiki", "Bret Harte", "Nick Hornby"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shogun: A Novel of Japan?", "answers": ["Shepherd Mead", "James Clavell", "Mahatma Gandhi", "Susanna Kearsley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Screwtape Letters?", "answers": ["Angela Johnson", "C. S. Lewis", "Eleanor Hibbert", "Enda Walsh"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ant and the Dove?", "answers": ["David Icke", "Mary Lewis Wang", "Mary Norton", "Tahereh Mafi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Purge?", "answers": ["Sofi Oksanen", "Alan Lawrence Sitomer", "Kaui Hart Hemmings", "Aung San Suu Kyi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Awake and Sing!?", "answers": ["Evelyn Waugh", "Fred Ebb", "Jean Giraudoux", "Clifford Odets"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book America the beautiful?", "answers": ["Lynn Sherr", "James D. Houston", "Ben Carson", "Arthur C. Clarke"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Walk in the Woods?", "answers": ["Marshall Barer", "Marcus Luttrell", "Bill Bryson", "Tony Kushner"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Saint Joan?", "answers": ["George Bernard Shaw", "Erica Jong", "John Fowles", "Sister Souljah"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hostage?", "answers": ["Brendan Behan", "Flora Thompson", "Clifford Sawhney", "Richard Bach"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Raft?", "answers": ["Kate DiCamillo", "Billy Frolick", "Henry Blackaby", "Stephanie Stuve-Bodeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Last Lecture?", "answers": ["Clifton Taulbert", "William S. Gray", "Cacilda Jeth\u00e1", "Randy Pausch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Last Lecture?", "answers": ["Billie Joe Armstrong", "Zo\u00eb Heller", "Jeffrey Zaslow", "A. S. Byatt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blue Plate Special: An Autobiography of My Appetites?", "answers": ["Jonathan Harr", "Muhammad al-Bukhari", "Naomi Mitchison", "Kate Christensen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The midnight ride of Paul Revere?", "answers": ["Mridula Baljekar", "Mark Twain", "Krishna Dharma", "Henry Wadsworth Longfellow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A satisfied mind?", "answers": ["David Morrell", "Steve Eng", "Mark Tully", "Drew Karpyshyn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jonathan Livingston seagull: a story?", "answers": ["John Connolly", "Richard Bach", "Barbara O'Connor", "Jeff Whitty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Siddhartha?", "answers": ["Alyson Noel", "A. J. Quinnell", "Hermann Hesse", "Basil Copper"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kon-Tiki: Across the Pacific in a Raft?", "answers": ["Loretta Lynn", "James Baldwin", "Jos\u00e9 Saramago", "Thor Heyerdahl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book On the Island?", "answers": ["Christopher Ryan", "Arthur Golden", "George Stanley", "Tracey Garvis-Graves"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Through the Looking-Glass?", "answers": ["Matthew J. Costello", "India Knight", "Nicholas Sparks", "Lewis Carroll"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ice Man?", "answers": ["Matthew Bourne", "Philip Carlo", "Dave Thompson", "Margaret Stohl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chasing Lincoln's Killer?", "answers": ["Jacques Rupnik", "Robert Penn Warren", "Edmond Rostand", "James L. Swanson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Principles of Psychology?", "answers": ["William James", "Donna Tartt", "Thomas Keneally", "Veronica Roth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The princess and the frog?", "answers": ["Bill O'Reilly", "Deborah Chiel", "Gore Vidal", "Will Eisner"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Profiles in Courage?", "answers": ["Darren Shan", "Sigmund Freud", "Melina Marchetta", "John F. Kennedy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Never Promised You a Rose Garden?", "answers": ["Trey Parker", "John Dos Passos", "Joanne Greenberg", "Daniel Defoe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Scary Stories to Tell in the Dark?", "answers": ["Friedrich Nietzsche", "Alvin Schwartz", "Lynn Vincent", "Nayantara Sahgal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Arcadia?", "answers": ["Tom Stoppard", "Peter Stone", "Michael McIntosh", "K\u00e1roly Pap"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book John Henry?", "answers": ["Greg Behrendt", "Thomas Jefferson", "Julius Lester", "Thomas Kyd"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Children of Men?", "answers": ["Terry Bisson", "P. D. James", "Jan Ormerod", "Justin Halpern"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book If\u2014?", "answers": ["Joseph Heller", "Barry Reed", "Rudyard Kipling", "Philip K. Dick"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Many Lives Many Masters?", "answers": ["Brian Weiss", "Arnold Bennett", "James Randi", "Paul Torday"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Mandalorian Armor?", "answers": ["Michael Ledwidge", "A. E. Housman", "Umberto Eco", "K. W. Jeter"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Picture of Dorian Gray?", "answers": ["Oscar Wilde", "Anne Holm", "James Herriot", "Doris Pilkington Garimara"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Book of the Dead?", "answers": ["Lynda Adamson", "Elizabeth Strout", "Patricia Cornwell", "Terrence McNally"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rebel Without a Cause?", "answers": ["Caryl Churchill", "Robert Lindner", "Arundhati Roy", "Haruki Murakami"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In Arabian Nights?", "answers": ["Beverly Lewis", "Emmet Fox", "Tahir Shah", "Linda Woolverton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book White Noise?", "answers": ["Gregory David Roberts", "Don DeLillo", "Ian Fleming", "John Osborne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mullah Nasruddin?", "answers": ["Clifford Sawhney", "John Ajvide Lindqvist", "George Howe Colt", "Sarah Chauncey Woolsey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anna Karenina?", "answers": ["Leo Tolstoy", "Terry Bisson", "Tim Rice", "Jon Ronson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sometimes a Great Notion?", "answers": ["Ken Kesey", "Thor Heyerdahl", "Mark Helprin", "Harold Kushner"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Horton Hears a Who!?", "answers": ["Marcia Brown", "Daniel Defoe", "John Keir Cross", "Dr. Seuss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Angels in America: A Gay Fantasia on National Themes?", "answers": ["Terry Bisson", "William R. Forstchen", "Tony Kushner", "Nicholas Dante"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Paleo Diet Revised?", "answers": ["Loren Cordain", "Alain-Ren\u00e9 Lesage", "Karen Blixen", "Chris Gardner"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kaleidoscope?", "answers": ["Chris Ryan", "Tom Perrotta", "Danielle Steel", "Mikhail Lermontov"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lucky?", "answers": ["Alice Sebold", "Jim Gaffigan", "Gustave Flaubert", "Richard Gravil"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Oresteia?", "answers": ["Kenneth E. Boulding", "Arthur Laurents", "Aeschylus", "Samuel Noah Kramer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Book of Mormon?", "answers": ["Stephen Kendrick", "Alice Raymon", "Matt Stone", "Miguel de Cervantes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Book of Mormon?", "answers": ["Robert Lopez", "Steven D. Levitt", "Drew Karpyshyn", "Anne Fine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Book of Mormon?", "answers": ["Trey Parker", "Euclid", "Rumiko Takahashi", "W. Chan Kim"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nausea?", "answers": ["Sue Monk Kidd", "Jean-Paul Sartre", "Simon Armitage", "Penelope Williamson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Suitable Boy?", "answers": ["Philipp Meyer", "Vikram Seth", "Danielle Steel", "Gregory David Roberts"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bitch?", "answers": ["Stacy Schiff", "David Almond", "Deja King", "Michael Rosen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Survival In Auschwitz?", "answers": ["Rainer Maria Rilke", "Yasmina Khadra", "Primo Levi", "Caralyn Buehner"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tramp art?", "answers": ["Paul Vixie", "Helaine Fendelman", "Haylie Pomroy", "Gunnar Myrdal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fahrenheit 451?", "answers": ["Roddy Doyle", "Rich Cohen", "Ray Bradbury", "Richard Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gora: (Gora)?", "answers": ["Sara Shepard", "M. Scott Peck", "Martin Dugard", "Rabindranath Tagore"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Of Human Bondage?", "answers": ["W. Somerset Maugham", "Christa Faust", "Sarah Gilbert", "Louis L'Amour"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dog Sees God: Confessions of a Teenage Blockhead?", "answers": ["Amrita Pritam", "Caralyn Buehner", "James A. Michener", "Bert V. Royal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Covenant?", "answers": ["Malorie Blackman", "Theodore Taylor", "Yasmina Khadra", "James A. Michener"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Covenant?", "answers": ["Michael Falconer Anderson", "William Inge", "Neil Gaiman", "Aldous Huxley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Twinkle Twinkle Little Star?", "answers": ["Iris Murdoch", "Mike Weiss", "Jane Taylor", "Richard Peck"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gold-Bug?", "answers": ["Edgar Allan Poe", "Dodie Smith", "Dare Wright", "James Bradley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The American historical romance?", "answers": ["Nick Stafford", "George Dekker", "Bryce Courtenay", "Sarah Dessen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Slap?", "answers": ["Eben Alexander", "Hilary Mantel", "Doug Naylor", "Christos Tsiolkas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book When Worlds Collide?", "answers": ["P. D. Eastman", "Martin Amis", "Philip Wylie", "Philip Caputo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book When Worlds Collide?", "answers": ["Lawrence Hill", "Andrew Carnegie", "Edwin Balmer", "Kevin J. Anderson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Raven?", "answers": ["Dan Poynter", "Shrikant G. Talageri", "Edgar Allan Poe", "Bob Dylan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Horse Whisperer?", "answers": ["Nicholas Evans", "Ford Madox Ford", "James Thurber", "Howard E. Wasdin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Can-Can?", "answers": ["Halima Bashir", "John Hersey", "Martin Dugard", "Abe Burrows"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Graceling?", "answers": ["Wilson Rawls", "Dinabandhu Mitra", "James Hilton", "Kristin Cashore"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?: A Play?", "answers": ["Edward Albee", "Bob Woodward", "Robert Kimmel Smith", "Shobhaa De"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cost Accounting - Career Path?", "answers": ["Raj\u0101\u02bc \u02bbAbd All\u0101h \u1e62\u0101ni\u02bb", "Charles T. Horngren", "Guru Nanak Dev", "Sonya Hartnett"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Black and Blue?", "answers": ["Anna Quindlen", "Stephen Molstad", "Lynda La Plante", "Henry James"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nothing's Fair in Fifth Grade?", "answers": ["Barthe DeClements", "Scott Turow", "Delos W. Lovelace", "L. Ron Hubbard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Three Cups of Deceit?", "answers": ["Shrikant G. Talageri", "Robert Wooster", "Jon Krakauer", "Sir John Retcliffe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Prometheus Bound?", "answers": ["Eduard Jose", "James Alexander Thom", "A. C. H. Smith", "Aeschylus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Among the Hidden?", "answers": ["Marshall Barer", "Megan McDonald", "Margaret Peterson Haddix", "Michael Mayer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cold Mountain?", "answers": ["C. S. Godshalk", "Charles Frazier", "Sarah Ban Breathnach", "Cecily von Ziegesar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kings Row?", "answers": ["No\u00ebl Coward", "William Dean Howells", "Anne Rivers Siddons", "Henry Bellamann"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Madame Doubtfire?", "answers": ["Anne Fine", "Norman Vincent Peale", "Frank McCourt", "Mary Kay Andrews"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Treasure Island?", "answers": ["Henry David Thoreau", "David Brauner", "Robert Louis Stevenson", "Flora Rheta Schreiber"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Matilda the Musical?", "answers": ["Jean Marzollo", "Iris Murdoch", "Giles Andreae", "Dennis Kelly"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Twits?", "answers": ["Roald Dahl", "Beatrix Potter", "Christos Tsiolkas", "A. S. A. Harrison"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Peter and the Starcatcher?", "answers": ["Robert A. Heinlein", "Rick Elice", "Gillian Flynn", "Eric Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The House of Blue Leaves?", "answers": ["John Guare", "Frank Graziano", "Jean Craighead George", "Jean Claverie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dirty Wars: The World Is a Battlefield?", "answers": ["Margret Rey", "Jeremy Scahill", "Owen Wister", "Adriana Trigiani"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Twelve Years a Slave?", "answers": ["Martin Fridson", "Solomon Noethup", "Robert Ludlum", "Robert Graves"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Agenda 21?", "answers": ["David Auburn", "Glenn Beck", "Joyce Lankester Brisley", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Agenda 21?", "answers": ["Thomas L. Friedman", "Harriet Parker", "Richard Adams", "Joseph Kesselring"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tuck Everlasting?", "answers": ["Ethel Waters", "Natalie Babbitt", "Ben Sherwood", "Aristophanes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cirque du Freak?", "answers": ["Raj\u0101\u02bc \u02bbAbd All\u0101h \u1e62\u0101ni\u02bb", "Darren Shan", "Joshua Sobol", "Thomas Meehan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Greek Myths?", "answers": ["Angela Brown", "John Boyne", "Robert Graves", "Samuel Beckett"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Song of Solomon?", "answers": ["H. Richard Hornberger", "Solomon", "Dave Barry", "Ruta Sepetys"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book War Horse?", "answers": ["Jane Hamilton", "Louis Sachar", "Li Cunxin", "Nick Stafford"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gilded Age: A Tale of Today?", "answers": ["Tony Kushner", "Thornton Wilder", "Charles Dudley Warner", "Munro Leaf"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gilded Age: A Tale of Today?", "answers": ["Wilson Rawls", "Robert Edwin Lee", "Margaret Elphinstone", "Mark Twain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book London?", "answers": ["Edward Rutherfurd", "Deborah Ellis", "Elizabeth Wurtzel", "James A. Michener"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My So-Called Life?", "answers": ["Catherine Clark", "Natalie Babbitt", "David Soman", "Allen Ginsberg"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gold Coast?", "answers": ["Nelson DeMille", "Tom Rath", "Marghanita Laski", "W. R. Bolen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Where the Sidewalk Ends?", "answers": ["Arna Bontemps", "Cassandra Clare", "Charles Spurgeon", "Shel Silverstein"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bingo?", "answers": ["Ian Serraillier", "Edward Bond", "Edgar Rice Burroughs", "Jodi Picoult"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bride Stripped Bare?", "answers": ["Joanna C. Galdone", "Laurie Lee", "Karen Blixen", "Nikki Gemmell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Merry Adventures of Robin Hood?", "answers": ["Li Cunxin", "Howard Pyle", "Deborah Ellis", "Horace Silver"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Dance with Dragons?", "answers": ["Alan Jay Lerner", "Fidel Castro", "Abraham Verghese", "George R. R. Martin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Science Fiction: The 100 Best Novels?", "answers": ["Christopher Brookmyre", "David Pringle", "Lauren Kate", "Richard Bach"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Dash Diet Weight Loss Solution?", "answers": ["Margaret Atwood", "Marla Heller", "Alain-Ren\u00e9 Lesage", "Amish Tripathi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How Green Was My Valley?", "answers": ["Gore Vidal", "Caryl Churchill", "Neil Simon", "Richard Llewellyn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Color Purple?", "answers": ["Thomas More", "Gunnar Myrdal", "Edith Wharton", "Marsha Norman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book SEAL Team Six: Memoirs of an Elite Navy SEAL Sniper?", "answers": ["Anthony Kiedis", "Nikki Gemmell", "Kami Garcia", "Howard E. Wasdin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book SEAL Team Six: Memoirs of an Elite Navy SEAL Sniper?", "answers": ["Deborah Smith", "Stephen Templin", "Yann Martel", "Candace Bushnell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Beach House?", "answers": ["Mary Alice Monroe", "Andrew S. Tanenbaum", "Reverend W. Awdry", "Reginald Rose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Heaven Is for Real?", "answers": ["Shashi Tharoor", "Todd Burpo", "Marco Polo", "Mohsin Hamid"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Heaven Is for Real?", "answers": ["Banjo Paterson", "Lynn Vincent", "Stan Redding", "Robert Holden"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Puss in Boots?", "answers": ["Douglas Adams", "Kate Chopin", "Philip Pullman", "Henry David Thoreau"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Gruffalo's Child?", "answers": ["Richard Hakluyt", "Austin Winsberg", "Julia Donaldson", "Robert Harris"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book On the Beach?", "answers": ["Sherman Alexie", "Bob Fosse", "Rajendra Prasad", "Nevil Shute"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Unhappy India?", "answers": ["Michael Symon", "Isabel Allende", "Lala Lajpat Rai", "Aristophanes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Really Short History of Nearly Everything?", "answers": ["Ray Bradbury", "Bill Bryson", "Richard Condon", "Liz Lark"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Flashman?", "answers": ["George MacDonald Fraser", "Richard Parker", "Ayaan Hirsi Ali", "Flora Rheta Schreiber"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Judgment?", "answers": ["Katherine Anne Porter", "Franz Kafka", "Debbie Macomber", "Bartolom\u00e9 de Las Casas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dreams from My Father?", "answers": ["W. Chan Kim", "Ken Kesey", "Jeffrey Eugenides", "Barack Obama"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Journey?", "answers": ["John Galsworthy", "Berry Gordy", "Tony Blair", "George Vecsey"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Monster?", "answers": ["Walter Dean Myers", "Pat Conroy", "Rodman Philbrick", "Charles Darwin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pal Joey?", "answers": ["Anita Diamant", "Arthur Kopit", "John O'Hara", "Charles Portis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Last Unicorn?", "answers": ["Stephen Covey", "Diana Gabaldon", "Peter S. Beagle", "Meredith Willson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A More Perfect Union: The Story of Our Constitution?", "answers": ["James Plunkett", "Betsy Maestro", "Elmore Leonard", "Stephen W. Garber"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Show Boat?", "answers": ["Oscar Hammerstein II", "Seth Grahame-Smith", "Tatiana De Rosnay", "Lisa Frazier Page"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Atlas Shrugged?", "answers": ["James Fenimore Cooper", "Mary Norton", "Uri Shulevitz", "Ayn Rand"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Giver?", "answers": ["Lois Lowry", "Mark Halperin", "Benjamin Franklin", "John Berendt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book So Long a Letter?", "answers": ["Joseph Finder", "Mario Vargas Llosa", "Belva Plain", "Mariama B\u00e2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Disney's Lady and the Tramp?", "answers": ["Rainer Maria Rilke", "Jamie Simons", "Arthur Balfour", "Henry Beveridge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jews and words?", "answers": ["Adriana Trigiani", "Amos Oz", "R. K. Narayan", "John R. Erickson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jews and words?", "answers": ["W. H. Auden", "R. D. Blackmore", "Fania Oz-Salzberger", "Chetan Bhagat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Grease?", "answers": ["John Hersey", "Jim Jacobs", "Pauline R\u00e9age", "A. J. Cronin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Grease?", "answers": ["Kathleen Winsor", "Warren Casey", "Reza Aslan", "Bibhutibhushan Bandopadhyay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Billy Elliot the Musical?", "answers": ["Lee Hall", "Peter Benchley", "Joseph Campbell", "Bill Dedman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Room of One's Own?", "answers": ["Virginia Woolf", "E. Annie Proulx", "Cornelius Ryan", "Mary Balogh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Living Sober?", "answers": ["Todd Burpo", "Alcoholics Anonymous", "Mary Shelley", "Michael Hollinger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book This Boy's Life: A Memoir?", "answers": ["Margaret Fuller", "Pearl Poet", "Tobias Wolff", "Gunnar Myrdal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Name of this Book is Secret?", "answers": ["Jacob Grimm", "Judah the Prince", "Michael Flatley", "Pseudonymous Bosch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Poetics?", "answers": ["Alex Garland", "Bede", "Meg Cabot", "Aristotle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Heat Wave?", "answers": ["Richard Castle", "Christina Crawford", "Valmiki", "Faith Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Kitchen House?", "answers": ["Garth Stein", "Daniel Wallace", "Kathleen Grissom", "Franz Kafka"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Oliver!?", "answers": ["George Vecsey", "Harvey Fierstein", "Rosa Parks", "Lionel Bart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sarah Kane?", "answers": ["Anne Fine", "Sarah Kane", "Julian Fellowes", "Janet Riehecky"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book God Is Not Great: How Religion Poisons Everything?", "answers": ["Jenny Downham", "Christopher Hitchens", "Jerry Hicks", "Kevin Maurer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Paul Revere's ride?", "answers": ["Euripides", "David Hackett Fischer", "Eudora Welty", "Laurie Halse Anderson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Little Red Riding Hood?", "answers": ["Heather Hach", "Charles Perrault", "Eleanor Estes", "Mridula Baljekar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Geography?", "answers": ["David Rabe", "Greg Behrendt", "Shirley Conran", "Ptolemy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Running Man?", "answers": ["Patricia Reilly Giff", "Stephen King", "Dan Poynter", "Barbara O'Connor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Civil Action?", "answers": ["William R. Forstchen", "Cecily von Ziegesar", "Roger O. Hirson", "Jonathan Harr"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Revolution 2020?", "answers": ["B. G. Hennessy", "Friedrich Nietzsche", "James Patterson", "Chetan Bhagat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Principles of Management?", "answers": ["Tony Morden", "Harlan Coben", "Glen Rounds", "Axel Scheffler"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Demian?", "answers": ["Gerome Ragni", "Louis Sachar", "Hermann Hesse", "Ana\u00efs Nin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bluebeard?", "answers": ["Kurt Vonnegut", "Phoebe Atwood Taylor", "Jonathan Larson", "Fidel Castro"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book There's a Boy in the Girls' Bathroom?", "answers": ["Louis Sachar", "C. Everard Palmer", "Nicole Mones", "Truman Capote"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gossip Girl?", "answers": ["Jon Lee Anderson", "Jess Walter", "Loren Cordain", "Cecily von Ziegesar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Feminine Mystique?", "answers": ["Sloan Wilson", "Hasan Azizul Huq", "Betty Friedan", "Frank Wedekind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Outliers: The Story of Success?", "answers": ["Philip Wylie", "Malcolm Gladwell", "Bill Yoast", "Jean Giraudoux"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Progress of the Soul?", "answers": ["Jane Green", "Ntozake Shange", "John Donne", "Joanna Cole"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Spark Notes A Tale of Two Cities?", "answers": ["Wendy Fonarow", "Joseph Robinette", "Charles Dickens", "Chris Crutcher"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Plum Island?", "answers": ["Michael Chabon", "Nelson DeMille", "Edwin Balmer", "E. M. Forster"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Der Erlk\u00f6nig?", "answers": ["Rajendra Prasad", "Thomas Hardy", "Johann Wolfgang von Goethe", "Ayaan Hirsi Ali"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Story of O?", "answers": ["Richard Blackaby", "Rohinton Mistry", "Andrew Carnegie", "Pauline R\u00e9age"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Diary of a Young Girl?", "answers": ["Katherine Paterson", "Megan McDonald", "Christopher Smart", "Anne Frank"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Journey to the Center of the Earth?", "answers": ["Kim Barnouin", "Jules Verne", "Harry Allard", "Maya Angelou"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Big Fish: A Novel of Mythic Proportions?", "answers": ["Daniel Wallace", "Alan Moore", "Owen Wister", "James Lapine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Brothers Karamazov?", "answers": ["A. E. W. Mason", "Jean Webster", "Lee Hall", "Fyodor Dostoyevsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Town Like Alice?", "answers": ["Thomas L. Friedman", "Lawrence Kimbrough", "E. L. Doctorow", "Nevil Shute"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Finnegans Wake?", "answers": ["James Joyce", "Jean Giraudoux", "Ian McEwan", "Hesiod"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Black Water?", "answers": ["Thomas Keneally", "Tracy Letts", "Eleanor Estes", "Joyce Carol Oates"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Yellow Raft in Blue Water?", "answers": ["Richard Harris", "Shelagh Delaney", "Nikolai Gogol", "Michael Dorris"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Course in Miracles?", "answers": ["Mark Haddon", "Lisa Genova", "Helen Schucman", "Eric S. Nylund"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Orphan Master's Son?", "answers": ["Jacques Rupnik", "John Galsworthy", "Christopher Collier", "Adam Johnson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ugly Duckling?", "answers": ["Iris Johansen", "Jeffrey Eugenides", "Herman Wouk", "Lydia Flem"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book 90 Minutes in Heaven?", "answers": ["Fern Michaels", "Don Piper", "Seamus Heaney", "Ernest J. Gaines"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book 90 Minutes in Heaven?", "answers": ["Paulo Coelho", "Cecil Murphey", "Thomas Bell", "Matthew Gregory Lewis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stuart Little?", "answers": ["E. B. White", "Michael Brandman", "Luigi Pirandello", "Nan Knighton"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book 2001: A Space Odyssey?", "answers": ["John Milton", "Arthur C. Clarke", "Matt Lang", "David Lindsay-Abaire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Push?", "answers": ["Barthe DeClements", "Sapphire", "James Lapine", "Richard Nelson Bolles"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The turning point?", "answers": ["Aristotle", "Christina Baker Kline", "Norman Vincent Peale", "Fritjof Capra"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Summerland?", "answers": ["Elin Hilderbrand", "Luigi Pirandello", "Carl Bernstein", "Louisa May Alcott"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Scarlet Letter?", "answers": ["George Gipe", "Henry Miller", "Bob Woodward", "Nathaniel Hawthorne"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shiver?", "answers": ["Amy Tan", "Maggie Stiefvater", "Daniel Goleman", "Marisha Pessl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book This Is Craig Brown?", "answers": ["Thomas Pynchon", "Craig Brown", "William Shakespeare", "Ian Rankin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book All Quiet on the Western Front?", "answers": ["Walter Lord", "Erich Maria Remarque", "R. C. Sherriff", "Bobby Lynn Maslen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Let It Snow?", "answers": ["Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa", "John Green", "Ben Carson", "Charles Webb"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Let It Snow?", "answers": ["Lauren Myracle", "Julie Taymor", "Patrick Rothfuss", "James Wesley Rawles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Waiting for Godot?", "answers": ["Samuel Beckett", "Sarah Orne Jewett", "Paige Turner", "Mike Leigh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Tree Grows in Brooklyn?", "answers": ["Mary Roach", "Trent Lott", "Betty Smith", "Kate Christensen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Divergent?", "answers": ["Marguerite Henry", "Veronica Roth", "A. N. Wilson", "Alice Walker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rapunzel?", "answers": ["Diana Hacker", "Charles Dudley Warner", "Tom Rob Smith", "Paul O. Zelinsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rime of the Ancient Mariner?", "answers": ["Eleanor H. Porter", "John Bunyan", "Samuel Taylor Coleridge", "James Randi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Duchess of Malfi?", "answers": ["Lane Smith", "Jagmohan", "Matthew Holm", "John Webster"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Thus Spoke Zarathustra?", "answers": ["Maurine Dallas Watkins", "Friedrich Nietzsche", "Walter Francis White", "Harry Thompson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beauty and the Beast?", "answers": ["Matthew J. Costello", "Jonathan Harr", "George Dekker", "Gabrielle-Suzanne Barbot de Villeneuve"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Johnny Tremain?", "answers": ["Ayi Kwei Armah", "Piers Paul Read", "Daniel Woodrell", "Esther Forbes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book It Walks By Night?", "answers": ["John Dickson Carr", "Julie Smith", "Baroness Emma Orczy", "Barbara Hambly"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book And Then There Were None?", "answers": ["A. S. Byatt", "Agatha Christie", "John Wyndham", "Greil Marcus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book U.S. Air Force: A Complete History?", "answers": ["John Dickson Carr", "Leonard Everett Fisher", "Dik A. Daso", "Paul Laurence Dunbar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The FastDiet?", "answers": ["John Gardner", "William Hoffer", "Alex Haley", "Mimi Spencer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The FastDiet?", "answers": ["Michael J. Mosley", "Washington", "Justin Halpern", "John Galsworthy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Leaves of Grass?", "answers": ["Walt Whitman", "Margaret Elphinstone", "S. A. Bodeen", "Milton A. Rothman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Polar Express?", "answers": ["Aeschylus", "John Howard Griffin", "Chris Van Allsburg", "Brian Yorkey"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ella Enchanted?", "answers": ["John Berendt", "Gail Carson Levine", "Philip Roth", "Libba Bray"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Orion?", "answers": ["Anthony Berkeley Cox", "Tony Blair", "Richard Henry Horne", "Alfred North Whitehead"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ulysses?", "answers": ["Alex Flinn", "James Joyce", "Elie Wiesel", "Cass Sunstein"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Joy of Cooking?", "answers": ["Joseph Campbell", "Ralph Ellison", "Irma S. Rombauer", "William Diehl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Judy Moody and the Not Bummer Summer?", "answers": ["Megan McDonald", "Harvey Diamond", "Nicolaus Copernicus", "Bob Thiele"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Island?", "answers": ["Gavin Maxwell", "Cathy Lamb", "William Cullen Bryant", "Victoria Hislop"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Red Sparrow?", "answers": ["Jason Matthews", "August Wilson", "R. C. Sherriff", "Margaret Stohl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Fox and the Grapes?", "answers": ["Anne Mazer", "Aesop", "Josh McDowell", "Wilhelm Grimm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Short History of Nearly Everything?", "answers": ["Danny Wallace", "Bill Bryson", "Arthur C. Clarke", "Tucker Max"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Birdsong?", "answers": ["Sebastian Faulks", "Charles Darwin", "Eva Ibbotson", "John Clare"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Norwegian Wood?", "answers": ["Stephanie Stuve-Bodeen", "Lincoln Child", "Haruki Murakami", "Conrad Ferdinand Meyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Half of a Yellow Sun?", "answers": ["Victor Hugo", "Mahatma Gandhi", "Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie", "Moli\u00e8re"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Man on Fire?", "answers": ["A. J. Quinnell", "Franklin Lacey", "John Adams", "Gyan C. Jain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to succeed in business without really trying?", "answers": ["Shepherd Mead", "Shel Silverstein", "Prosper M\u00e9rim\u00e9e", "Chris Tebbetts"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Kingdom Keepers: Disney After Dark?", "answers": ["Ridley Pearson", "William Gibson", "Eben Alexander", "Charles Portis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Robinson Crusoe?", "answers": ["Thomas Rockwell", "Edmond Halley", "Montesquieu", "Daniel Defoe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Historian?", "answers": ["Elizabeth Kostova", "Natalie Standiford", "Pope Benedict XVI", "Peter Stone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Can Love Happen Twice??", "answers": ["Ovid", "Ravinder Singh", "Ellen DeGeneres", "Reza Aslan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Crucial Conversations?", "answers": ["W. R. Bolen", "Bret Witter", "Steven Kellogg", "Kerry Patterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cannery Row?", "answers": ["David Patterson", "John Steinbeck", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco", "Donna Tartt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Post-American World?", "answers": ["Fareed Zakaria", "Howard Ashman", "Tahir Shah", "Jamie McGuire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Travels of Marco Polo?", "answers": ["Marco Polo", "Whitney Stewart", "Peter Shaffer", "Deirdre David"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Travels of Marco Polo?", "answers": ["Kenneth E. Boulding", "Jason Gehlert", "Noel Streatfeild", "Rustichello da Pisa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bringing Down the House: The Inside Story of Six MIT Students Who Took Vegas for Millions?", "answers": ["Rick Riordan", "Zo\u00eb Heller", "Ben Mezrich", "Michael Stewart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Road?", "answers": ["Tracey Garvis-Graves", "Ivan Turgenev", "Cormac McCarthy", "Thomas Bell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Robe?", "answers": ["Sylvain Reynard", "Ruth Westheimer", "Larry Collins", "Lloyd C. Douglas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Experiencing God: God's Invitation to Young Adults?", "answers": ["Beryl Markham", "Rainer Maria Rilke", "Flora Thompson", "Richard Blackaby"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Experiencing God: God's Invitation to Young Adults?", "answers": ["Grumpy Cat", "Joyce Carol Oates", "Henry Blackaby", "Harold Bell Wright"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gora.?", "answers": ["T. H. White", "T. H. White", "Patricia Highsmith", "Rabindranath Tagore"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Greek Cook Book?", "answers": ["Curt Gentry", "Tess Mallos", "Jamie Ford", "Eric Litwin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bad Monkey?", "answers": ["A. J. Cronin", "Chuck Palahniuk", "James D. Houston", "Carl Hiaasen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Misty of Chincoteague?", "answers": ["Esther Forbes", "Steven Sater", "George Gipe", "Marguerite Henry"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Aftershock: The Next Economy and America's Future?", "answers": ["Ren\u00e9e Mauborgne", "Edward Lear", "Robert Reich", "Ray Bradbury"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Half a Life?", "answers": ["Darin Strauss", "John Galsworthy", "Tony Blair", "James Ellroy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Streets of Laredo?", "answers": ["Aleister Crowley", "Betsy Thornton", "Larry McMurtry", "William Goldman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stopping by Woods on a Snowy Evening?", "answers": ["Christopher McDougall", "Robert Frost", "Pierre Boulle", "William Henry Hudson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The descendants?", "answers": ["Geraint Anderson", "Kaui Hart Hemmings", "Mimi Spencer", "Dorothy Wall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Battle Royale?", "answers": ["Dale Wasserman", "Koushun Takami", "Frederick Winslow Taylor", "Dianne Watkins Stuart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock?", "answers": ["T. S. Eliot", "Lionel Bart", "William F. Nolan", "Gertrude Chandler Warner"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The White Man's Burden: Why the West's Efforts to Aid the Rest Have Done So Much Ill and So Little Good?", "answers": ["William Easterly", "Annie Jacobsen", "Susan Spencer-Wendel", "Jeffery Deaver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Time After Time?", "answers": ["Patrick Ness", "Karl Alexander", "Chris Van Allsburg", "Elizabeth Cody Kimmel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Principles of Management?", "answers": ["Harriet Ann Jacobs", "Solomon", "Steven McShane", "Martin Amis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Kingdom of God Is Within You?", "answers": ["Stella Gibbons", "David Foster Wallace", "Leo Tolstoy", "Rob Grant"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sir Gawain and the Green Knight?", "answers": ["Thomas Mann", "Howard E. Wasdin", "Pearl Poet", "Don Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Goldilocks and the Three Bears?", "answers": ["Kenneth Grahame", "Caralyn Buehner", "Elizabeth Kostova", "David A. Adler"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Praise of Folly?", "answers": ["Desiderius Erasmus", "Matthew Holm", "Colum McCann", "Mickey Rapkin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Euclid's Elements?", "answers": ["R. C. Sherriff", "Euclid", "George Gipe", "Bessie Head"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Liliom?", "answers": ["Willie Gilbert", "Mitch Albom", "Ferenc Moln\u00e1r", "David Brauner"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Conjuring?", "answers": ["Matt Lang", "John Edward Williams", "James Randi", "Carla Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wounds of Love : The Mystical Marriage of Saint Rose of Lima: The Mystical Marriage of Saint Rose of Lima?", "answers": ["B. Traven", "R.M. French", "Philip K. Dick", "Frank Graziano"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Wimpy Kid: Do-it-yourself Book?", "answers": ["Jeff Kinney", "Bill W.", "John Dickson Carr", "Martin Cruz Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Invisible Man?", "answers": ["Eric Suben", "Terrence McNally", "H. G. Wells", "Barry Reed"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hamlet?", "answers": ["Sarah Waters", "Mary Claire Helldorfer", "William Faulkner", "Brendan Behan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sofia the First?", "answers": ["Cameron Crowe", "Steven Gould", "Catherine Hapka", "Grumpy Cat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book An Ideal Husband?", "answers": ["Charles Nordhoff", "John Irving", "The Chew", "Oscar Wilde"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book BUtterfield 8: Roman?", "answers": ["Rohinton Mistry", "Harriet Parker", "Taslima Nasrin", "John O'Hara"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Maze Runner?", "answers": ["Stephen Crane", "Ferenc Moln\u00e1r", "James Dashner", "Mark O'Donnell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Dog's Purpose?", "answers": ["Kenneth Tynan", "Kevin Mitnick", "Jessie Redmon Fauset", "W. Bruce Cameron"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Very Good Year: The Journey of a California Wine from Vine to Table?", "answers": ["Julius Lester", "Thomas Rockwell", "Mike Weiss", "Alfred Uhry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Wealth of Nations?", "answers": ["Thomas Meehan", "Lane Becker", "Adam Smith", "W. Wilkins"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Iliad?", "answers": ["Homer", "Stephenie Meyer", "Angela Johnson", "Melvin Belli"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Skinwalker?", "answers": ["Barack Obama", "John Reynolds Gardiner", "Faith Hunter", "Donald R. Bear"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mamma Mia!?", "answers": ["Christopher Priest", "Catherine Johnson", "Ransom Riggs", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Walk to Remember?", "answers": ["Lucretius", "Eugene H. Peterson", "Don Lynch", "Nicholas Sparks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Woman in Black?", "answers": ["Benjamin Disraeli", "Susan Hill", "Katrina Kittle", "Eve Bunting"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Woman in Black?", "answers": ["Karl Marx", "Gregory David Roberts", "Julie Brady", "Stephen Mallatratt"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Who Was Walt Disney??", "answers": ["Matt Stone", "Art Spiegelman", "Whitney Stewart", "Mary Roach"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Know Why the Caged Bird Sings?", "answers": ["Maya Angelou", "Jason Matthews", "James Marshall", "Jerome Lawrence"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Fountainhead?", "answers": ["Scott Smith", "John Coleman Burroughs", "Elmore Leonard", "Ayn Rand"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Annie Get Your Gun?", "answers": ["Eric Van Lustbader", "William Golding", "Robert E. Vardeman", "Herbert Fields"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Annie Get Your Gun?", "answers": ["William Langland", "Brian Yorkey", "Dorothy Fields", "Dennis Kelly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pride and Prejudice and Zombies?", "answers": ["Barack Obama", "Allen Ginsberg", "Seth Grahame-Smith", "Mahatma Gandhi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blue Blood?", "answers": ["Robert Lindner", "Jack Weinstock", "Mel Brooks", "Edward Conlon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The War of the Worlds?", "answers": ["H. G. Wells", "Valmiki", "Christopher Priest", "Donna Tartt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Strangers on a Train?", "answers": ["Christopher Isherwood", "James A. Michener", "Carol Higgins Clark", "Patricia Highsmith"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Funny Girl?", "answers": ["Isobel Lennart", "Angela Johnson", "Abba Eban", "Scott Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Silver Linings Playbook?", "answers": ["Milton A. Rothman", "Samuel Noah Kramer", "Carlo Collodi", "Matthew Quick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Olivia Manning: A Woman at War?", "answers": ["Deirdre David", "Mary Claire Helldorfer", "Paige Turner", "Sharon Creech"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Applause?", "answers": ["Desiderius Erasmus", "Fred Graver", "Adolph Green", "Ethan Hawke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Applause?", "answers": ["Lynda La Plante", "Jack Weinstock", "Betty Comden", "The Chew"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to Eat Fried Worms?", "answers": ["Michael Connelly", "Tennessee Williams", "Shrikant G. Talageri", "Thomas Rockwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Prophecy?", "answers": ["Chris Kuzneski", "Willa Cather", "Seamus Heaney", "John Adams"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Aztec?", "answers": ["Gary Jennings", "Horace Walpole", "Jack Hibberd", "Sara Shepard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Midsummer Night's Dream?", "answers": ["William Shakespeare", "Rabindranath Tagore", "Fritjof Capra", "Richard Blackaby"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bells?", "answers": ["Edgar Allan Poe", "Roger Zelazny", "Irving Stone", "Vanessa Diffenbaugh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book If You Give a Moose a Muffin?", "answers": ["Laura Numeroff", "Christopher Paolini", "John Dos Passos", "Piers Anthony"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Amy Vanderbilt complete book of etiquette?", "answers": ["Cynthia Lord", "Robert Reich", "Jody Rosen", "Amy Vanderbilt"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jurassic Park?", "answers": ["Michael Crichton", "Zo\u00eb Heller", "Harold Robbins", "Lynn Vincent"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The power of positive thinking?", "answers": ["Steve Sheinkin", "Norman Vincent Peale", "Curtis Sittenfeld", "Edgar Allan Poe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Carpetbaggers?", "answers": ["Jean Claverie", "Alice Sebold", "Harold Robbins", "Alice Walker"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anything Goes?", "answers": ["Guy Bolton", "Carol Gilligan", "Brian Yorkey", "Herman J. Mankiewicz"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anything Goes?", "answers": ["P. G. Wodehouse", "Jack Higgins", "James Randi", "Amos Oz"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anything Goes?", "answers": ["Liz Tuccillo", "Carolyn Reeder", "Rex Pickett", "Howard Lindsay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anything Goes?", "answers": ["Russel Crouse", "Mary Lewis Wang", "Dave Gibbons", "Henry David Thoreau"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Night Circus?", "answers": ["Jeannette Walls", "Erin Morgenstern", "Lauren Myracle", "Amish Tripathi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Nanny Diaries?", "answers": ["Plato", "Emma McLaughlin", "Polly Adler", "Desmond Morris"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Nanny Diaries?", "answers": ["Richard Condon", "John Dickinson", "Nicola Kraus", "Megan McDonald"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Power of Now?", "answers": ["Eckhart Tolle", "Joseph Gibaldi", "Joanne Greenberg", "Mark Z. Danielewski"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Alive: The Story of the Andes Survivors?", "answers": ["Piers Paul Read", "Walt Whitman", "David Rabe", "Kate Chopin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Winter's Tales?", "answers": ["Albert E Cliffe", "Susanna Kearsley", "Karen Blixen", "Charles Perrault"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Quidditch Through the Ages?", "answers": ["Hugh Johnson", "Marsha Norman", "Stephen W. Garber", "J. K. Rowling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Deliverance?", "answers": ["John Archambault", "Robert Harris", "Jim Butcher", "James Dickey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Nazarene?", "answers": ["Mohsin Hamid", "Samuel Beckett", "S. A. Bodeen", "Sholem Asch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dad Is Fat?", "answers": ["Harvey Fierstein", "P. D. Eastman", "Patricia Reilly Giff", "Jim Gaffigan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hotel?", "answers": ["Arthur Hailey", "William Cullen Bryant", "Barthe DeClements", "Jerzy Kosi\u0144ski"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Carrie?", "answers": ["Terry Bisson", "Fareed Zakaria", "Ana\u00efs Nin", "Stephen King"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hugh Johnson's Pocket Wine?", "answers": ["Bill Dedman", "Hugh Johnson", "Martin Fridson", "Harriet Beecher Stowe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tuzuk-I-Jahangiri or Memoirs of Jahangir?", "answers": ["Henry Beveridge", "Stieg Larsson", "Robert Wooster", "Walter Lord"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Show Boat?", "answers": ["Edna Ferber", "Edward Young", "Rudolph Besier", "Pierre Boulle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Society in America?", "answers": ["Robert Burns", "Geraint Anderson", "Harriet Martineau", "Ernest Hemingway"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Complicated Kindness?", "answers": ["Jamie McGuire", "Miriam Toews", "David Baldacci", "Jodi Picoult"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book M*A*S*H: A Novel About Three Army Doctors?", "answers": ["H. Richard Hornberger", "Lydia Flem", "Susan J Tolchin", "Lincoln Peirce"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book M*A*S*H: A Novel About Three Army Doctors?", "answers": ["Eric Carle", "W. C. Heinz", "Tom Perrotta", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Common Sense?", "answers": ["Christopher Hampton", "Pierre Choderlos de Laclos", "Thomas Paine", "Samuel Shem"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Scarlett?", "answers": ["John R. Erickson", "Alexandra Ripley", "Doreen Cronin", "Michelle Gadpaille"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Major Barbara?", "answers": ["Joshua Sobol", "George Bernard Shaw", "James M. Cain", "Wendy Fonarow"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Library of Helene Hanff Limited Edition Signed?", "answers": ["Michel Faber", "Chinua Achebe", "John O'Hara", "Helene Hanff"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beauty and the Beast?", "answers": ["Martin Dugard", "Linda Woolverton", "Margaret Mitchell", "Aeschylus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Presumed Innocent?", "answers": ["Jonathan Larson", "Scott Turow", "Alan Moore", "Judah the Prince"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Junie B. Jones's First Boxed Set Ever!?", "answers": ["Barbara Park", "Darin Strauss", "Nicholas Monsarrat", "Debbie Macomber"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Zoo?", "answers": ["Alain-Ren\u00e9 Lesage", "James Patterson", "Peter Barnes", "Ayi Kwei Armah"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Zoo?", "answers": ["Christopher McDougall", "Jacques Rupnik", "Michael Ledwidge", "William Easterly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book United States Declaration of Independence?", "answers": ["Winnie Holzman", "Robert R. Livingston", "Greg Behrendt", "Zora Neale Hurston"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book United States Declaration of Independence?", "answers": ["Benjamin Franklin", "Fu Xi", "Nicole Mones", "Frank Herbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book United States Declaration of Independence?", "answers": ["John Adams", "Lloyd C. Douglas", "Frank Herbert", "Frederic Loewe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book United States Declaration of Independence?", "answers": ["Miguel \u00c1ngel Ruiz", "Jacob Grimm", "Lisa Genova", "Thomas Jefferson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book United States Declaration of Independence?", "answers": ["Owen Wister", "Sidney Lanier", "Roger Sherman", "Lynn Vincent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Portnoy's Complaint?", "answers": ["Richard Paul Evans", "Monica Dickens", "Philip Roth", "Sherry Argov"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Giraffes Cant Dance - Do Not Release Without Authorisation?", "answers": ["Max Allan Collins", "Reinhold Niebuhr", "Giles Andreae", "Johann David Wyss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nudge?", "answers": ["William Hoffer", "Mikhail Lermontov", "Cass Sunstein", "Aleister Crowley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nudge?", "answers": ["Aldo Leopold", "Thornton Wilder", "Richard Thaler", "Emma Donoghue"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Area 51: An Uncensored History of America's Top Secret Military Base?", "answers": ["Willie Nelson", "Annie Jacobsen", "Judy Blume", "Kathryn Lasky"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Into the Woods?", "answers": ["James Lapine", "Alain-Ren\u00e9 Lesage", "Seth Grahame-Smith", "Maurice Sendak"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Black Hawk Down?", "answers": ["Mimi Spencer", "Mark Bowden", "Mark Haddon", "Benjamin Franklin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Argo: How the CIA and Hollywood Pulled Off the Most Audacious Rescue in History?", "answers": ["Peter Rinearson", "Chris Crutcher", "Doug Naylor", "Tony Mendez"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Argo: How the CIA and Hollywood Pulled Off the Most Audacious Rescue in History?", "answers": ["Robert Newton Peck", "Aldous Huxley", "Randy Pausch", "Matt Baglio"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rose Garden?", "answers": ["Samuel P. Huntington", "James Alexander Thom", "Susanna Kearsley", "James Dickey"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book City Mouse and Country Mouse?", "answers": ["Margaret Mitchell", "Paige Turner", "Mao Zedong", "Lawrence Kimbrough"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Momo?", "answers": ["Iain Banks", "Joseph Gibaldi", "Frank Wedekind", "Michael Ende"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mary Poppins?", "answers": ["Julian Fellowes", "Patricia McCormick", "Chris Crutcher", "Emmet Fox"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book One pair of hands?", "answers": ["Marshall Brickman", "Edwin Balmer", "T. S. Eliot", "Monica Dickens"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Emperor's New Clothes?", "answers": ["Dylan Thomas", "Sylvia Plath", "Hans Christian Andersen", "Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Great Lawsuit. Man versus Men. Woman versus Women?", "answers": ["Rachel Renee Russell", "Robert Newton Peck", "Katie Davis", "Margaret Fuller"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Battlefield Earth?", "answers": ["L. Ron Hubbard", "Jim Butcher", "Edmond Rostand", "Friedrich Engels"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Death Be Not Proud?", "answers": ["John Gunther", "Eleanor Coerr", "Stan Redding", "Ishmael Beah"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Monk Who Sold His Ferrari?", "answers": ["Henry Williamson", "Scott O'Dell", "S. J. Watson", "Robin Sharma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book One Fine Day in the Middle of the Night?", "answers": ["Christopher Brookmyre", "Thomas Jefferson", "Jean Craighead George", "Milton William Cooper"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Much Ado About Nothing?", "answers": ["David Patterson", "Wally Lamb", "William Shakespeare", "Tim O'Brien"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book 1776?", "answers": ["Walt Whitman", "Justin Cronin", "David McCullough", "Stephen Molstad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Memoirs of a Geisha?", "answers": ["Richard Blackaby", "Arthur Golden", "Dana Wilkerson", "Pope Benedict XVI"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The beach house?", "answers": ["Perseus Books Group", "Thomas Seltzer", "Jane Green", "John Fowles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lysistrata?", "answers": ["Sister Souljah", "Aristophanes", "Charles Spurgeon", "Thomas \u00e0 Kempis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Zealot: The Life and Times of Jesus of Nazareth?", "answers": ["Betsy Thornton", "Reza Aslan", "P. C. Wren", "Robert R. McCammon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Ash\u1e6d\u0101dhy\u0101y\u012b?", "answers": ["P\u0101\u1e47ini", "Jamie McGuire", "Erik Larson", "Laozi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dune?", "answers": ["Irene Mecchi", "Terry Goodkind", "Sarah Dessen", "Frank Herbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Girls of Riyadh?", "answers": ["Kamala Markandaya", "Mary Claire Helldorfer", "Raj\u0101\u02bc \u02bbAbd All\u0101h \u1e62\u0101ni\u02bb", "A. S. A. Harrison"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book It's a man's world?", "answers": ["Michael Lewis", "Adam Parfrey", "Linda Sue Park", "Edgar Allan Poe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A God in Ruins?", "answers": ["Lucy Maud Montgomery", "Cynthia Kadohata", "J. C. Holt", "Leon Uris"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Godfather?", "answers": ["Thomas L. Friedman", "Jacqueline Wilson", "Jon Lee Anderson", "Mario Puzo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Kiss Before Dying?", "answers": ["Clement Clarke Moore", "John the Evangelist", "Ira Levin", "John Clare"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Italian Mysteries?", "answers": ["Clive Barker", "William F. Nolan", "R. C. Sherriff", "Francis Lathom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Psycho?", "answers": ["Thiruvalluvar", "Thomas Seltzer", "Robert Bloch", "William S. Burroughs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Country Girl?", "answers": ["Margaret Floy Washburn", "Clifford Odets", "Robert Greene", "Agatha Christie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Children of a Lesser God?", "answers": ["Robert Graves", "Mark Medoff", "Drew Karpyshyn", "Grace Metalious"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Snoopy! The Musical?", "answers": ["Jean Craighead George", "Anthony Burgess", "Michael Grace", "Whitney Stewart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Snoopy! The Musical?", "answers": ["John the Evangelist", "Margaret Edson", "P. C. Wren", "Warren Lockhart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Snoopy! The Musical?", "answers": ["Sarah Orne Jewett", "Arthur Whitelaw", "Trevanian", "George Eliot"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book One Pair of Hands: The Happy Prisoner ; Mariana ; Kate and Emma ; One Pair of Feet?", "answers": ["Grumpy Cat", "Monica Dickens", "A. E. Housman", "Al Gore"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mandingo?", "answers": ["Kyle Onstott", "Tom Rath", "Carl Van Vechten", "Marjorie Garber"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book HAMLET: TEXT IN ENGLISCH?", "answers": ["Trey Parker", "Julia Kristeva", "William Shakespeare", "Shobhaa De"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pardoner's Tale?", "answers": ["J. Meade Falkner", "Geoffrey Chaucer", "Rob Grant", "Elizabeth Jolley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gandhi and Stalin?", "answers": ["Axel Scheffler", "Nikki Gemmell", "Ben Sherwood", "Louis Fischer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Mother Tongue: English and How It Got That Way?", "answers": ["Bill Bryson", "Rick Riordan", "William Styron", "Anton Chekhov"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Contemporary American Fiction?", "answers": ["David Brauner", "Michael Stewart", "Alan Moore", "Aleksey Nikolayevich Tolstoy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Indian in the Cupboard?", "answers": ["Eric Berne", "Billie Letts", "Isaac Newton", "Lynne Reid Banks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Algebra of Infinite Justice?", "answers": ["Else Holmelund Minarik", "Arundhati Roy", "Neil Simon", "A. S. Byatt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Leviathan?", "answers": ["Khushwant Singh", "Stan Redding", "Reginald Rose", "Thomas Hobbes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shrek !?", "answers": ["Judith Krantz", "William Steig", "Michael Ledwidge", "Barbara A. Shapiro"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Crow Road?", "answers": ["Patricia McCormick", "Iain Banks", "Alan Davies", "Michael Chabon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Orphan Train?", "answers": ["Dayananda Saraswati", "Christina Baker Kline", "Lincoln Steffens", "Hans Christian Andersen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Killing Lincoln?", "answers": ["Confucius", "Christy Brown", "Martin Dugard", "Art Spiegelman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Killing Lincoln?", "answers": ["Bill O'Reilly", "Taslima Nasrin", "Robert Sobel", "Munro Leaf"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book TITANIC AN ILLUSTRATED HISTORY?", "answers": ["Michelle Magorian", "Augusten Burroughs", "J. K. Rowling", "Don Lynch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ironman?", "answers": ["Rudolph Besier", "Eddi Fiegel", "Chris Crutcher", "William Saroyan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Wonderful Wizard of Oz?", "answers": ["L. Frank Baum", "David Hackett Fischer", "Steven Curtis Chapman", "James Clavell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf??", "answers": ["Steven Gould", "Dan Poynter", "Edward Albee", "B. G. Hennessy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Book of Negroes?", "answers": ["Lawrence Hill", "Jacqueline Wilson", "Mary Lewis Wang", "Robin Jones Gunn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Everyday Use?", "answers": ["Julia Donaldson", "Alice Walker", "James Clavell", "Christopher Hampton"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Superfudge?", "answers": ["Dorothy Wall", "Franz Kafka", "Rashid-al-Din Hamadani", "Judy Blume"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cut?", "answers": ["William R. Forstchen", "Scott Turow", "Jacques Rupnik", "Patricia McCormick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Maximum Ride: The Angel Experiment?", "answers": ["Clifton Taulbert", "Nikolai Gogol", "James Patterson", "Allen Ginsberg"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Forsyte Saga?", "answers": ["Christopher Hitchens", "George R. R. Martin", "David Nicholls", "John Galsworthy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Love Does: Discover a Secretly Incredible Life in an Ordinary World?", "answers": ["Barry Reed", "Mark Haddon", "Michelle Gadpaille", "Bob Goff"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Five Love Languages?", "answers": ["Jonathan Larson", "Gary D. Chapman", "Christopher Paul Curtis", "Stephen Crane"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Scarlet Ibis?", "answers": ["Frank Lauria", "James Hurst", "Cassandra Golds", "Jos\u00e9 Saramago"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book With Reagan?", "answers": ["Sheryl WuDunn", "Edwin Meese", "Erskine Caldwell", "William Ernest Henley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Big Sleep?", "answers": ["Raymond Chandler", "Doreen Cronin", "Tony Mendez", "Wallace Thurman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Between Shades of Gray?", "answers": ["Arthur Kopit", "Ruta Sepetys", "Kingsley Amis", "Rich Cohen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Where the Red Fern Grows?", "answers": ["Mary Roach", "James Clavell", "Ford Madox Ford", "Wilson Rawls"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pitch perfect?", "answers": ["Mickey Rapkin", "Guinness World Records", "Jacob Grimm", "Rich Cohen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Double Indemnity?", "answers": ["Frederick Winslow Taylor", "James M. Cain", "Drew Karpyshyn", "James Agee"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Host?", "answers": ["Lloyd Jones", "Horace Silver", "Ovid", "Stephenie Meyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Zombie?", "answers": ["Peter Rinearson", "Joyce Carol Oates", "Hasan Azizul Huq", "Judith Krantz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Eleven?", "answers": ["James Baldwin", "Patricia Reilly Giff", "William Thomas Stead", "Sol Yurick"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Son of a Witch?", "answers": ["Gregory Maguire", "Percy Bysshe Shelley", "Ally Condie", "Malcolm Gladwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dream Children?", "answers": ["Michael Ende", "Baroness Emma Orczy", "Don Brown", "A. N. Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nectar in a Sieve?", "answers": ["Joseph Heller", "Kamala Markandaya", "Richard Paul Evans", "Charlotte Perkins Gilman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Vedic Mathematics?", "answers": ["Patrick Barlow", "Bharati Krishna Tirthaji", "Anton LaVey", "Henry Williamson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tipping Point: How Little Things Can Make a Big Difference?", "answers": ["Jamie Ford", "Oliver Goldsmith", "Lorraine Hansberry", "Malcolm Gladwell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Singin' in the Rain?", "answers": ["William S. Gray", "Sun Tzu", "Andy McNab", "Adolph Green"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Singin' in the Rain?", "answers": ["Betty Comden", "Mourning Dove", "Jacqueline Davies", "Aaron Sorkin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Matilda?", "answers": ["James Thurber", "Roald Dahl", "John Wyndham", "Fareed Zakaria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dog Sees God: Confessions of a Teenage Blockhead?", "answers": ["Mary Balogh", "Aleister Crowley", "Douglass Wallop", "Bert V. Royal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Election?", "answers": ["Tom Perrotta", "Malcolm X", "Arthur Hailey", "Matthew Quick"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Poisonwood Bible?", "answers": ["Billy Frolick", "Barbara Kingsolver", "Irene Mecchi", "Richard Blackaby"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Canterbury Tales?", "answers": ["Geoffrey Chaucer", "Colin Wilson", "Wu Cheng'en", "Flannery O'Connor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Thinking historically?", "answers": ["Fyodor Dostoyevsky", "Thomas C. Holt", "Carol Sklenicka", "Carlos Ruiz Zaf\u00f3n"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Seven Brides for Seven Brothers?", "answers": ["Joe McGinniss", "David Landay", "Manu (Lawgiver)", "Stella Gibbons"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Seven Brides for Seven Brothers?", "answers": ["Marguerite Henry", "George Gipe", "Lawrence Kasha", "David McCullough"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Shahnameh?", "answers": ["R. D. Blackmore", "P\u0101\u1e47ini", "Bessie Head", "Ferdowsi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book It Was a Very Good Year: Extraordinary Moments in Stock Market History?", "answers": ["S. J. Watson", "Clive Cussler", "Judith Krantz", "Martin Fridson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Old MacDonald Had a Farm?", "answers": ["Jane Cabrera", "Randy Pausch", "John Webster", "Robert Harling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Education of Little Tree?", "answers": ["Robert R. Livingston", "Asa Earl Carter", "Cecily von Ziegesar", "Alfred Uhry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Madame Bovary?", "answers": ["Gustave Flaubert", "Stella Gibbons", "Harry Allard", "Enda Walsh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Federalist No. 51?", "answers": ["James Madison", "Quentin Tarantino", "Charles Lederer", "Amos Oz"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Fantasticks?", "answers": ["Harvey Schmidt", "Lydia Flem", "Niccol\u00f2 Machiavelli", "Gustave Flaubert"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Fantasticks?", "answers": ["Michael Frayn", "Carlos Ruiz Zaf\u00f3n", "Tom Jones", "Edmund Cooper"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book How to Be a Woman?", "answers": ["Montesquieu", "Ann Voskamp", "Caitlin Moran", "Wallace Wattles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sisterland?", "answers": ["Curtis Sittenfeld", "Richard O'Brien", "Sofi Oksanen", "Noam Chomsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sonnet 43?", "answers": ["Ruth Westheimer", "William Shakespeare", "Charles Dudley Warner", "John Archambault"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Nickel and Dimed?", "answers": ["Barbara Ehrenreich", "Trent Lott", "Penny Dann", "Steve Sheinkin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Queen Bees and Wannabes?", "answers": ["Rosalind Wiseman", "Warren Lockhart", "James Herriot", "Karma-glin\u0307-pa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Harvey?", "answers": ["Chinua Achebe", "Mary Chase", "Thomas Paine", "Alex Haley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Single Man?", "answers": ["Christopher Isherwood", "Laurence Sterne", "Adam Johnson", "Bram Stoker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Howards End?", "answers": ["Rupert Hart-Davis", "E. M. Forster", "Henry David Thoreau", "Cornelia Funke"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children?", "answers": ["Ellen G. White", "Giovanni Boccaccio", "Ransom Riggs", "Edna Ferber"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Milly-Molly-Mandy Stories?", "answers": ["Aristotle", "John Jay", "Ernest Thayer", "Joyce Lankester Brisley"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Old Man and the Sea?", "answers": ["Oscar Hammerstein II", "Ernest Hemingway", "Chaim Potok", "Nathan Myhrvold"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Anne of Green Gables?", "answers": ["Lucy Maud Montgomery", "Sattar Memon", "Jacqueline Susann", "Bret Witter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sex at Dawn?", "answers": ["Mark Kurlansky", "Christopher Ryan", "Tom Rob Smith", "Gary Ezzo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sex at Dawn?", "answers": ["Dare Wright", "Cacilda Jeth\u00e1", "Laura Hillenbrand", "Aleksandr Pushkin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beautiful Boy: A Father's Journey Through His Son's Addiction?", "answers": ["David Sheff", "Gordon Korman", "Charles Van Doren", "Elizabeth Barrett Browning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Cruel Sea?", "answers": ["Helaine Fendelman", "Eric S. Nylund", "Nicholas Monsarrat", "Steven Curtis Chapman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The God of Small Things?", "answers": ["Ben Carson", "Robert R. Livingston", "Arundhati Roy", "Charles A. Murray"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Red Dragon?", "answers": ["Thomas Harris", "Giovanni Boccaccio", "Marta Hillers", "Elias Chacour"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Agunpakhi?", "answers": ["Herman Melville", "Hasan Azizul Huq", "Rudolph Besier", "W. Wilkins"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The One and Only Ivan?", "answers": ["Suzanne Collins", "K. A. Applegate", "Ali", "Colleen McCullough"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fearless: The Undaunted Courage and Ultimate Sacrifice of Navy SEAL Team SIX Operator Adam Brown?", "answers": ["John Grisham", "Eric Blehm", "Mark Helprin", "John Dempsey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cutting for Stone?", "answers": ["Abraham Verghese", "Chris Ryan", "Bharati Krishna Tirthaji", "Herb Gardner"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Spartacus?", "answers": ["Louis de Berni\u00e8res", "Howard Fast", "Catherine Johnson", "Sloan Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Contemporary British fiction?", "answers": ["V. C. Andrews", "Rumiko Takahashi", "Nick Bentley", "Jack Higgins"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Century of Dishonor?", "answers": ["Helen Hunt Jackson", "Craig Thomas", "Shepherd Mead", "George Dekker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Golden Gate?", "answers": ["Adam Smith", "Thiruvalluvar", "Philip Carlo", "Vikram Seth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Know I've Been Changed?", "answers": ["Jean Anouilh", "Michael Wigglesworth", "Philipp Meyer", "Tyler Perry"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Running with Scissors?", "answers": ["William Blake", "Augusten Burroughs", "Beverly D'Onofrio", "Elizabeth Jolley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Winnie-the-Pooh?", "answers": ["British Library", "A. A. Milne", "Jeff Probst", "Colum McCann"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Human Comedy?", "answers": ["Tahereh Mafi", "William Saroyan", "Trent Lott", "John Jay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gulliver's Travels?", "answers": ["Andrew Clements", "Laura Hillenbrand", "Jonathan Swift", "Ron Powers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gulliver's Travels?", "answers": ["Arthur C. Clarke", "Richard Gravil", "Richard Llewellyn", "Augustine of Hippo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Moveable Feast?", "answers": ["L. Ron Hubbard", "B. Traven", "Hilary Mantel", "Ernest Hemingway"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Baby It's You!?", "answers": ["Elizabeth Barrett Browning", "Colin Escott", "Michael Morpurgo", "Eug\u00e8ne Ionesco"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Baby It's You!?", "answers": ["Floyd Mutrux", "M. NourbeSe Philip", "Walter Francis White", "Lafcadio Hearn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Yellow Wallpaper?", "answers": ["Charlotte Perkins Gilman", "Munro Leaf", "Nelson George", "Kenneth Grahame"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book His eye is on the sparrow?", "answers": ["Margaret Wise Brown", "Alice Sebold", "Douglas Angus", "Ethel Waters"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Saving Private Ryan?", "answers": ["Meg Cabot", "Max Allan Collins", "Edward Gibbon", "William Diehl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cracker!?", "answers": ["\u00c9mile Zola", "Floyd Mutrux", "Arthur Kopit", "Cynthia Kadohata"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hatchet?", "answers": ["Gary Paulsen", "Billy Frolick", "Natalie Babbitt", "Joceline Sanschagrin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book TransAtlantic?", "answers": ["William Manchester", "John Maynard Smith", "Richard Nelson Bolles", "Colum McCann"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Johnny Appleseed Big Book?", "answers": ["Ann Patchett", "Steven Kellogg", "Napoleon Hill", "Ralph Woodrow"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The End?", "answers": ["Lisi Harrison", "William Easterly", "Christina Hobbs", "Daniel Handler"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pride and Prejudice?", "answers": ["W. Bruce Cameron", "Martin Fridson", "Joseph Finder", "Jane Austen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chicago?", "answers": ["Mary Balogh", "Herbert Fields", "Maurine Dallas Watkins", "Julian Fellowes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Games People Play?", "answers": ["Kate DiCamillo", "Max Brooks", "Billie Letts", "Eric Berne"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bunnicula: A Rabbit-Tale of Mystery?", "answers": ["Herman Wouk", "James Howe", "Bertolt Brecht", "Jean Craighead George"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Beowulf?", "answers": ["Winnie Holzman", "Tahereh Mafi", "Seamus Heaney", "Richard Wright"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Book of Revelation?", "answers": ["Deborah Ellis", "William F. Nolan", "John of Patmos", "David Lindsay-Abaire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Selfish Giant?", "answers": ["Eoin Colfer", "Judith Krantz", "Oscar Wilde", "Valmiki"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kiddie Lit?", "answers": ["Beverly Lyon Clark", "Richard Yates", "Ori Brafman", "John O'Grady"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In the Heights?", "answers": ["Sogyal Rinpoche", "J. Alison James", "Watty Piper", "Quiara Alegr\u00eda Hudes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bury My Heart at Wounded Knee?", "answers": ["Dee Brown", "Phillip Berman", "James Randi", "Lloyd C. Douglas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lift every voice and sing?", "answers": ["John Bunyan", "Elin Hilderbrand", "James Weldon Johnson", "Lincoln Child"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ranma 1/2?", "answers": ["Paulo Coelho", "Dave Eggers", "Rumiko Takahashi", "Rebecca Skloot"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Uglies?", "answers": ["Miriam Toews", "Scott Westerfeld", "Conrad Ferdinand Meyer", "Nathaniel Hawthorne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Strike Back?", "answers": ["Aristophanes", "Julie Taymor", "Chris Ryan", "William Ernest Henley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Bad Beginning?", "answers": ["Wil Haygood", "Daniel Handler", "Henry Martyn Robert", "Charlotte Perkins Gilman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Monster High?", "answers": ["Alice Munro", "F. Scott Fitzgerald", "Whitley Strieber", "Lisi Harrison"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Stepford Wives?", "answers": ["Ira Levin", "Joyce Carol Oates", "Patricia McCormick", "Frank Wedekind"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Quotations from Chairman Mao Tse-tung?", "answers": ["Mao Zedong", "Iris Murdoch", "Jacqueline Susann", "Jessie Redmon Fauset"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rural Muse?", "answers": ["Helen Prejean", "John Clare", "Dik A. Daso", "James Norman Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stig of the Dump?", "answers": ["Jonathan Harr", "Clive King", "Lauren Myracle", "Arnold Bennett"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hills Like White Elephants?", "answers": ["Cameron Crowe", "Eleanor Estes", "Ernest Hemingway", "Iris Murdoch"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Thousand Splendid Suns?", "answers": ["Spencer Johnson", "David Almond", "Sofi Oksanen", "Khaled Hosseini"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book All Creatures Great and Small?", "answers": ["Susan J Tolchin", "Jeff Brown", "Jean Webster", "James Herriot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Princess Bride?", "answers": ["William Langland", "Jennifer Weiner", "Colleen McCullough", "William Goldman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Little Boy Lost?", "answers": ["William Henry Hudson", "Reginald Rose", "Milan Kundera", "Carlos Ruiz Zaf\u00f3n"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Let the Right One In?", "answers": ["John Ajvide Lindqvist", "Anita Shreve", "Stendhal", "Jacqueline Davies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Basil Copper: A Life in Books?", "answers": ["Basil Copper", "Percy Bysshe Shelley", "Kate Chopin", "James Fenimore Cooper"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Savages?", "answers": ["Rick Riordan", "Ivan Turgenev", "Michael Camille", "Don Winslow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bouche cousue?", "answers": ["Chinua Achebe", "Mazarine Pingeot", "Richard Nelson", "Sebastian Junger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stable Peace?", "answers": ["Charlotte Perkins Gilman", "Kenneth E. Boulding", "Kenneth Tynan", "James L. Swanson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mockingbird?", "answers": ["Eric Carle", "Harlan Ellison", "Bill Bryson", "Kathryn Erskine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Quo Vadis?", "answers": ["Michael Grace", "Billie Joe Armstrong", "Roger Sherman", "Henryk Sienkiewicz"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Prime of Miss Jean Brodie?", "answers": ["Muriel Spark", "Tahereh Mafi", "Philip Carlo", "Miriam Toews"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Benjamin Button?", "answers": ["Danny Wallace", "Gabrielle-Suzanne Barbot de Villeneuve", "James Howard Kunstler", "F. Scott Fitzgerald"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Hollow Man?", "answers": ["John Dickson Carr", "Watty Piper", "Thor Heyerdahl", "Curt Gentry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Women of the Harlem renaissance?", "answers": ["Debbie Macomber", "Eve Adamson", "Foster W. Cline", "Cheryl Wall"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Glass Menagerie?", "answers": ["Craig Brown", "Loren Cordain", "Laurence Sterne", "Tennessee Williams"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pretty Little Liars?", "answers": ["Rachel Harris", "Walt Whitman", "Sara Shepard", "Tony Hillerman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A House in the Sky: A Memoir?", "answers": ["Jo Swerling", "Amanda Lindhout", "Mitch Albom", "Harry Turtledove"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A House in the Sky: A Memoir?", "answers": ["Wallace Thurman", "Alexandre Dumas", "Sylvain Reynard", "Sara Corbett"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Tempest?", "answers": ["William Shakespeare", "Isabel Allende", "Gabriel Garc\u00eda M\u00e1rquez", "Erik Larson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Woman of Substance?", "answers": ["Barbara Taylor Bradford", "Deborah Ellis", "Milton William Cooper", "Jerome Lawrence"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Howl and Other Poems?", "answers": ["O. Henry", "Sholem Asch", "Allen Ginsberg", "Jennifer Worth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Prince?", "answers": ["Walt Whitman", "Niccol\u00f2 Machiavelli", "Jerry Pinkney", "Joyce Lankester Brisley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The emperor's new clothes?", "answers": ["Iris Murdoch", "John Webster", "David Soman", "Marcus Sedgwick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Girl Named Disaster?", "answers": ["Nancy Farmer", "Malcolm Gladwell", "V\u0101tsy\u0101yana", "E. Annie Proulx"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Man Without a Country?", "answers": ["Kurt Vonnegut", "Sarah Chauncey Woolsey", "Michael Ende", "Sean Hannity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sumerians?", "answers": ["Walt Whitman", "Ayi Kwei Armah", "Robert Boyle", "Samuel Noah Kramer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Canterville Ghost?", "answers": ["Robert Frost", "Ted Hughes", "Astrid Lindgren", "Oscar Wilde"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Walk in the Woods: Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail?", "answers": ["Mark Haddon", "Jawaharlal Nehru", "Bill Bryson", "Abba Eban"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Walk in the Woods: Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail?", "answers": ["E. L. Doctorow", "Bartolom\u00e9 de Las Casas", "Beverly Lyon Clark", "Philip Kerr"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Cherry Orchard?", "answers": ["Luther Davis", "Cacilda Jeth\u00e1", "Anton Chekhov", "Janet Riehecky"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lorax?", "answers": ["Joseph Gibaldi", "Nathan Myhrvold", "Dr. Seuss", "Dale Wasserman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Devil and Tom Walker?", "answers": ["Washington Irving", "Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry", "Elaine Pagels", "John Hersey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Criminal Investigation?", "answers": ["Russel Crouse", "William S. Burroughs", "James N. Gilbert", "Sattar Memon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Timeline?", "answers": ["Wallace Thurman", "W. Chan Kim", "Kevin Henkes", "Michael Crichton"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Witches of Eastwick?", "answers": ["Emma Clayton", "Robert Reich", "John Dempsey", "Wilbur A. Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Side of the Mountain?", "answers": ["Carla Hall", "Arthur Ashe", "Jean Craighead George", "Lawrence Kasha"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Charlotte Gray?", "answers": ["Anton Chekhov", "Sebastian Faulks", "Ben Mezrich", "Katie Davis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Who Do You Think You Are?: Finding Your True Identity in Christ?", "answers": ["Benjamin Franklin", "Nick Bentley", "Kaui Hart Hemmings", "Mark Driscoll"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sonnets from the Portuguese?", "answers": ["James Bradley", "Elizabeth Barrett Browning", "Rashid-al-Din Hamadani", "Jojo Moyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ragtime?", "answers": ["E. L. Doctorow", "Farhat Ishtiaq", "Mike Piazza", "David Nicholls"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Civil War bookshelf?", "answers": ["Daniel Keyes", "Robert Wooster", "B. G. Hennessy", "Diane Trister. Dodge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blink: The Power of Thinking Without Thinking?", "answers": ["Jeanne DuPrau", "Tony Kushner", "Malcolm Gladwell", "Richmal Crompton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Neuromancer?", "answers": ["James Weldon Johnson", "William Gibson", "John Keats", "Albert Facey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Happy Prince and Other Tales?", "answers": ["Prosper M\u00e9rim\u00e9e", "Marissa Meyer", "Oscar Wilde", "Christopher Isherwood"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dot and the Dog?", "answers": ["Homer", "Mary Claire Helldorfer", "Ren\u00e9e Mauborgne", "John R Maslen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dot and the Dog?", "answers": ["Eoin Colfer", "Michelle Magorian", "Roger O. Hirson", "Bobby Lynn Maslen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Visit from St. Nicholas?", "answers": ["Clement Clarke Moore", "Karma-glin\u0307-pa", "Richard Nelson Bolles", "William Thomas Stead"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Satanic Verses?", "answers": ["Kinky Friedman", "Eudora Welty", "Salman Rushdie", "Irma S. Rombauer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Little Mermaid?", "answers": ["Tony Blair", "Belle de Jour", "Laura Colker", "Hans Christian Andersen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Journey to the West?", "answers": ["Wu Cheng'en", "Edith Wharton", "Banjo Paterson", "Nelson Mandela"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Clair-de-Lune?", "answers": ["James Randi", "Cassandra Golds", "Dik A. Daso", "Jack London"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fearless Fosdick?", "answers": ["Elie Wiesel", "Al Capp", "Chris Van Allsburg", "Charles Van Doren"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Out of the Dust?", "answers": ["Daniel Brown", "Marco Polo", "Karen Hesse", "Thomas Hobbes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Sandman Vol. 1?", "answers": ["Gene Stone", "Lois Banner", "Neil Gaiman", "W. H. Auden"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book On Golden Pond?", "answers": ["Giovanni Boccaccio", "Ernest Thompson", "Ntozake Shange", "Katherine Paterson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lord Jim?", "answers": ["T. S. Eliot", "Joseph Conrad", "Elizabeth Wurtzel", "William R. Forstchen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The God Delusion?", "answers": ["Richard Dawkins", "James Boswell", "John Jakes", "Malcolm Lowry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Natural?", "answers": ["Amos Oz", "Bernard Malamud", "Christina Hobbs", "Carol Higgins Clark"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book One Thousand Gifts?", "answers": ["William Gibson", "Ann Voskamp", "Marjorie W. Sharmat", "Robert James Waller"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Brief History of Time?", "answers": ["Edward Gibbon", "Ida Tarbell", "Jean-Dominique Bauby", "Stephen Hawking"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Long Way Gone: Memoirs of a Boy Soldier?", "answers": ["Ishmael Beah", "Andy McNab", "Thomas Paine", "Christopher Hitchens"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tears of the Desert?", "answers": ["Frances Hodgson Burnett", "Jacqueline Susann", "Tony Morden", "Halima Bashir"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book American Buffalo?", "answers": ["John Galsworthy", "Bimal Jalan", "David Mamet", "Billy Graham"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Being There?", "answers": ["Gary D. Chapman", "Milan Kundera", "Jerzy Kosi\u0144ski", "Lynn Vincent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Fair Lady?", "answers": ["Alan Jay Lerner", "Bret Harte", "Anonymous", "Anne Fine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Am Number Four?", "answers": ["L. Ron Hubbard", "Daniel James Brown", "Joseph Stein", "Pittacus Lore"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Diving-Bell and the Butterfly?", "answers": ["Robert Harling", "Haylie Pomroy", "George Harrison", "Jean-Dominique Bauby"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stiff: The Curious Lives of Human Cadavers?", "answers": ["Alvin Toffler", "Arthur Whitelaw", "Mary Roach", "Esther Forbes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Good Behavior?", "answers": ["Rory Freedman", "David Mitchell", "Stephen W. Garber", "Langston Hughes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Women in Love?", "answers": ["James Herriot", "Matthew Bourne", "D. H. Lawrence", "H. Richard Hornberger"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Exodus?", "answers": ["Aristophanes", "Mary Claire Helldorfer", "Leon Uris", "Frank Graziano"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Prestige?", "answers": ["Christopher Priest", "Karen Traviss", "Enda Walsh", "Lucy Irvine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Shepherd of the Hills?", "answers": ["Margaret Stohl", "David Brauner", "Harold Bell Wright", "Jan Ormerod"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Cuckoo's Calling?", "answers": ["Steven Gould", "Khushwant Singh", "Dave Barry", "J. K. Rowling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The tortoise and the hare?", "answers": ["David Treuer", "Rufus Jones", "Caitlin Moran", "Janet Stevens"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book North and South?", "answers": ["John Jakes", "Norton Juster", "Jan Ormerod", "William Styron"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Aesop's Fables?", "answers": ["Anne Rice", "Geraint Anderson", "Umberto Eco", "Aesop"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Deadwood?", "answers": ["David Benioff", "Pete Dexter", "Naomi Mitchison", "Michael Morpurgo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rita Hayworth and Shawshank Redemption?", "answers": ["Eve Ensler", "Shirley Conran", "Stephen King", "Cynthia Lord"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ninjago: The Challenge of Samukai?", "answers": ["Greg Farshtey", "Alan Moore", "Jean Giraudoux", "Marcus Luttrell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ninjago: The Challenge of Samukai?", "answers": ["Paulo Herique", "Malcolm Pasley", "Tony Hillerman", "James Plunkett"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wings of Fire?", "answers": ["John Steinbeck", "A. P. J. Abdul Kalam", "O. T Nelson", "Devaki Nandan Khatri"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Invisible Man?", "answers": ["Gene Stone", "Ralph Ellison", "Betty Friedan", "Laura Numeroff"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Dog of Flanders?", "answers": ["Daniel Defoe", "Brendan Behan", "Ouida", "Jim Jacobs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Big House: A Century in the Life of an American Summer Home?", "answers": ["Bill Dedman", "George Howe Colt", "William Boyd", "Anita Shreve"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Day's Wait?", "answers": ["Peter Barnes", "Ernest Hemingway", "Howard Ashman", "Arna Bontemps"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wild Horse Mesa?", "answers": ["Jacqueline Susann", "Mary Robinette Kowal", "Will Eisner", "Zane Grey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A House for Mr Biswas?", "answers": ["Euripides", "Albert Facey", "V.S. Naipaul", "Elizabeth George Speare"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Secret Ingredients?", "answers": ["David Remnick", "Scott Smith", "Michael Brandman", "Lynley Dodd"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Utopia?", "answers": ["Dalton Trumbo", "W. W. Jacobs", "Walter Scott", "Thomas More"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Witches of Eastwick?", "answers": ["John Updike", "Malcolm X", "Gail Carson Levine", "Charles A. Murray"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sleeping Beauty?", "answers": ["Emma Donoghue", "Franz Kafka", "Brian Weiss", "Charles Perrault"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Farewell to Arms?", "answers": ["Ernest Hemingway", "William Steig", "John Locke", "Paramahansa Yogananda"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kubla Khan?", "answers": ["Denise Mina", "David Lodge", "Samuel Taylor Coleridge", "William Bradford"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Giving Tree?", "answers": ["Shel Silverstein", "Aryabhata", "Homer Hickam", "Jeannie Gunn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Cay?", "answers": ["Bill Dedman", "Thomas Carlyle", "Theodore Taylor", "Guy Bolton"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rapture?", "answers": ["Bimal Jalan", "Jim Bouton", "Shobhaa De", "Tim LaHaye"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rapture?", "answers": ["Isobel Lennart", "Ray Kurzweil", "Edwin Balmer", "Jerry B. Jenkins"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Cider House Rules?", "answers": ["Ben Sherwood", "Ashley Gardner", "Alexander Hamilton", "John Irving"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Forks Over Knives?", "answers": ["Ayaan Hirsi Ali", "T. Colin Campbell", "Leon Uris", "Rohinton Mistry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Forks Over Knives?", "answers": ["Gavin Maxwell", "George Ella Lyon", "Caldwell Esselstyn", "Phillip Berman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Forks Over Knives?", "answers": ["Oliver Goldsmith", "Gene Stone", "Christopher Paul Curtis", "Sarah Dessen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Golden Boy?", "answers": ["Clifford Odets", "Eric Wilson", "Carson McCullers", "Jeannette Walls"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Golden Boy?", "answers": ["William Gibson", "Maya Angelou", "Daniel Quinn", "David Mitchell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book An Inspector Calls?", "answers": ["Oscar Wilde", "David Margolick", "Donna Tartt", "John Boynton Priestley"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Clean?", "answers": ["Alejandro Junger", "Jay Asher", "Robert Thornton Morrison", "Mike Leigh"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Clean?", "answers": ["Thomas Hobbes", "Amely Greeven", "Ted Sorensen", "John Boyne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Dinner?", "answers": ["Benjamin Franklin", "The Betches", "Thor Heyerdahl", "Herman Koch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Good Man Is Hard to Find?", "answers": ["Karen Traviss", "Alice Raymon", "Flannery O'Connor", "Charlotte Bront\u00eb"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tell Me A Story Mama?", "answers": ["Lafcadio Hearn", "Jean-Paul Sartre", "Harvey Diamond", "Angela Johnson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Inferno?", "answers": ["Adam Parfrey", "Dan Brown", "Andrew Clements", "Donald Margulies"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dracula?", "answers": ["Dayananda Saraswati", "Alexander Hamilton", "Bram Stoker", "Jean M. Auel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kalimantaan?", "answers": ["Ernest Hemingway", "Luke the Evangelist", "Diana Gabaldon", "C. S. Godshalk"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Zorba the Greek?", "answers": ["Jean le Rond d'Alembert", "Piers Anthony", "Sharon Draper", "Nikos Kazantzakis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Madhushala?", "answers": ["Jennifer Worth", "Bartolom\u00e9 de Las Casas", "Harivanshrai Bachchan", "W. R. Bolen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Rainmaker?", "answers": ["Cornelius Ryan", "John Grisham", "Thor Heyerdahl", "Gillian Flynn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Pocahontas?", "answers": ["Harry Thompson", "Bjarne Stroustrup", "Joseph Bruchac", "Pauline R\u00e9age"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Minority Report?", "answers": ["Mary Lewis Wang", "The Betches", "John Gardner", "Philip K. Dick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Electra?", "answers": ["J. A. Jance", "Bill Dedman", "Euripides", "Jeremy Wilson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Think and Grow Rich?", "answers": ["Ruth Stiles Gannett", "Napoleon Hill", "Anthony Powell", "Martin Handford"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them?", "answers": ["Lynda Adamson", "Jorge Luis Borges", "David Oliver Relin", "J. K. Rowling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Twilight?", "answers": ["Victor Hugo", "Sri Aurobindo", "George Harrison", "Stephenie Meyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book King Kong: A Picture Book?", "answers": ["Merian C. Cooper", "Josh McDowell", "Dik A. Daso", "Bertolt Brecht"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book King Kong: A Picture Book?", "answers": ["Auguste Maquet", "Brian Weiss", "Edgar Wallace", "Greg Cox"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ben-Hur: A Tale of the Christ?", "answers": ["Dalton Trumbo", "Stephen Chbosky", "Lew Wallace", "John Boynton Priestley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Chariots of the Gods??", "answers": ["Erich von D\u00e4niken", "Thomas Jefferson", "Harry Allard", "John Bunyan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Redeeming Love?", "answers": ["Sue Monk Kidd", "R.M. French", "Kate Christensen", "Francine Rivers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dred: A Tale of the Great Dismal Swamp?", "answers": ["Ori Brafman", "Sandra Cisneros", "Jeffrey Zaslow", "Harriet Beecher Stowe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Uglies series?", "answers": ["Ryunosuke Akutagawa", "Scott Westerfeld", "Adam Mansbach", "H. E. Bates"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wicked: The Life and Times of the Wicked Witch of the West?", "answers": ["Gail Carson Levine", "Mike Weiss", "Rob Grant", "Gregory Maguire"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Possession: A Romance?", "answers": ["A. S. Byatt", "Steven Curtis Chapman", "Wallace Thurman", "Henry Blackaby"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Metamorphoses?", "answers": ["Malorie Blackman", "Watty Piper", "Esphyr Slobodkina", "Ovid"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Camelot?", "answers": ["Alan Jay Lerner", "Robert R. Livingston", "James M. Cain", "Ann Voskamp"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Invictus?", "answers": ["William Ernest Henley", "Stephen Covey", "Jack Schaefer", "Michael Serra"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Computer networks?", "answers": ["Gaston Leroux", "Willie Gilbert", "Andrew S. Tanenbaum", "M. L. Stedman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book V for Vendetta?", "answers": ["Alan Moore", "William Nack", "Melvin Belli", "Alvin Toffler"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Son?", "answers": ["Fannie Hurst", "L. P. Hartley", "Philipp Meyer", "Edward Rutherfurd"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Once and Future King?", "answers": ["T. H. White", "Roddy Doyle", "William Gibson", "Fred Graver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Agony and the Ecstasy?", "answers": ["Irving Stone", "Allan Folsom", "George Eliot", "Emma McLaughlin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Jungle Book?", "answers": ["Ann M. Martin", "Rudyard Kipling", "Hermann Hesse", "Daniel Wallace"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Me Mine?", "answers": ["George Harrison", "Ayi Kwei Armah", "Aleksandr Pushkin", "Stephen King"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Lion & the Mouse?", "answers": ["Timothy Ferriss", "Jerry Pinkney", "Julia Kristeva", "Tom Clancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Borrowers?", "answers": ["Mary Norton", "Mohsin Hamid", "Sidney Lanier", "Joe McGinniss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Birds?", "answers": ["Michael Frayn", "David Morrell", "Aristophanes", "Umberto Eco"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Imitation of Christ?", "answers": ["Steven D. Levitt", "Thomas \u00e0 Kempis", "J. A. Jance", "Arthur Hailey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Imitation of Christ?", "answers": ["British Library", "James Herriot", "Harlan Coben", "Luke the Evangelist"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Arsenic and Old Lace?", "answers": ["A. A. Milne", "Joseph Kesselring", "Mark the Evangelist", "Roald Dahl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book My Place?", "answers": ["Robert Lopez", "Martin Fridson", "Bill Yoast", "Sally Morgan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Crash?", "answers": ["Helen DeWitt", "Harvey Diamond", "J. G. Ballard", "Ian Fleming"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Sentimental Journey Through France and Italy?", "answers": ["Laurence Sterne", "George Harrison", "Mary Robinette Kowal", "James Frey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Noughts & Crosses?", "answers": ["David Nicholls", "Joseph Gibaldi", "Peggy Parish", "Malorie Blackman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book L.A. Confidential?", "answers": ["James Ellroy", "Robert Ruark", "Allan Folsom", "Erich Maria Remarque"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Long Walk?", "answers": ["Paulo Lins", "Stephen King", "Jhumpa Lahiri", "John Boswell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas?", "answers": ["George Bernard Shaw", "Roark Bradford", "Samuel Noah Kramer", "Hunter S. Thompson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Wicked?", "answers": ["Winnie Holzman", "Terrance Dicks", "Clifton Taulbert", "Andrew Carnegie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book In a Free State?", "answers": ["V.S. Naipaul", "P. G. Wodehouse", "Sara Corbett", "Peter Benchley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hedda Gabler?", "answers": ["Samuel Taylor Coleridge", "Robert R. McCammon", "Sterling Archer", "Christopher Hampton"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hedda Gabler?", "answers": ["Henrik Ibsen", "Philip Carlo", "Joshua Sobol", "Matt Stone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Right Stuff?", "answers": ["Tom Wolfe", "Viktor Frankl", "Ingrid Law", "William James"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Minus One?", "answers": ["J. G. Ballard", "Christopher Hampton", "Michael Serra", "Koushun Takami"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The House on Mango Street?", "answers": ["Rex Pickett", "Irving Stone", "Sandra Cisneros", "James N. Gilbert"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Story of My Life?", "answers": ["Richard Dawkins", "Melvin Belli", "Beatrice Sparks", "Helen Keller"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Road Ahead?", "answers": ["Peter Rinearson", "Jacqueline Davies", "Friedrich Engels", "Eckhart Tolle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Road Ahead?", "answers": ["Stephen C. Lundin", "Bill Gates", "Esphyr Slobodkina", "Chris D'Arienzo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Road Ahead?", "answers": ["Nathan Myhrvold", "Frederick M. Avolio", "Steven Gould", "Michael Chabon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Good Year?", "answers": ["Peter Mayle", "Munro Leaf", "Barbara Hambly", "Mel Brooks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Parade's End?", "answers": ["Kenneth Tynan", "James L. Swanson", "Ford Madox Ford", "Guru Nanak Dev"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Kidnapped?", "answers": ["William Luther Pierce", "Robert Louis Stevenson", "Clement Clarke Moore", "Beryl Gilroy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Angelina Ballerina?", "answers": ["Primo Levi", "Colette", "Katharine Holabird", "Ernest Thompson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Pelican Brief?", "answers": ["P. G. Wodehouse", "John Grisham", "Jim Bouton", "Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book House of Leaves?", "answers": ["Clive Cussler", "Wil Haygood", "Mark Z. Danielewski", "Paul Vixie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Disney Fairies?", "answers": ["Madeleine L'Engle", "Michael Brandman", "James Fenimore Cooper", "Gail Carson Levine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Great Indian Novel?", "answers": ["John Boynton Priestley", "Shashi Tharoor", "Anita Shreve", "Adam Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Splendor in the grass?", "answers": ["Malcolm Pasley", "William Inge", "Mary Carter", "Samantha Shannon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book One for the Money?", "answers": ["Michael Dobbs", "Bjarne Stroustrup", "Janet Evanovich", "C. S. Godshalk"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mississippi Burning?", "answers": ["Willie Nelson", "Eugene O'Neill", "Bankim Chandra Chattopadhyay", "Kirk Mitchell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat?", "answers": ["A. E. Housman", "Corrie ten Boom", "John Peck", "Tim Rice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book America?", "answers": ["Cass Sunstein", "Milan Kundera", "Orson Scott Card", "Barack Obama"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The A Circuit?", "answers": ["Wu Cheng'en", "Elie Wiesel", "Catherine Hapka", "Alex Kendrick"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Call the Midwife?", "answers": ["William Boyd", "Jennifer Worth", "Mark Driscoll", "Fred Graver"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Flipped?", "answers": ["Julian Fellowes", "Kristin Cashore", "Wendelin Van Draanen", "John Adams"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Tarzan of the Apes?", "answers": ["Edgar Rice Burroughs", "Ron Hall", "Ian Fleming", "John Dickson Carr"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gabriel's Inferno?", "answers": ["Ben Mezrich", "Sylvain Reynard", "Lisa Genova", "Kathryn Stockett"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Importance of Being Earnest?", "answers": ["Melanie Hauser", "Marissa Meyer", "Oscar Wilde", "Glen Berger"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Total Frat Move?", "answers": ["W. R. Bolen", "Craig Brown", "Amos Oz", "Kazuo Ishiguro"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Stardust?", "answers": ["Lois Banner", "Neil Gaiman", "Craig Thomas", "Fania Oz-Salzberger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Little Engine That Could?", "answers": ["Enda Walsh", "Richard Nelson", "Alcoholics Anonymous", "Watty Piper"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Papillon?", "answers": ["Reinhold Niebuhr", "Piers Anthony", "David Patterson", "Henri Charri\u00e8re"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Mommie Dearest?", "answers": ["Bert Dodson", "Christina Crawford", "Rohinton Mistry", "Mark Z. Danielewski"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Claude McKay", "Anthony Swofford", "Craig Brown", "Glen Hirshberg"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Alfred North Whitehead", "Arna Bontemps", "Lee Hall", "Tahereh Mafi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Michael Serra", "Dalton Trumbo", "Countee Cullen", "Barbara Taylor Bradford"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Mark Haddon", "Paul Laurence Dunbar", "Johann Wolfgang von Goethe", "Anthony Powell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Frederic Loewe", "Laozi", "Langston Hughes", "Irving Stone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Carl Van Vechten", "Robert Goolrick", "Wendy Mass", "Jean M. Auel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["William Dean Howells", "Dennis Ritchie", "Jerry Bock", "Khaled Hosseini"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Thomas Hobbes", "Charles W. Chesnutt", "Ben Okri", "M. L. Stedman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Walter Francis White", "Thomas Hardy", "J. M. Barrie", "Robert Ruark"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Sofi Oksanen", "Fania Oz-Salzberger", "W.E.B. Du Bois", "Sara Pennypacker"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Guy Bolton", "Sterling Allen Brown", "Ben Okri", "Joe Masteroff"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Grumpy Cat", "Michelle Alexander", "Jean Toomer", "Che Guevara"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Helaine Fendelman", "James Weldon Johnson", "Caryl Churchill", "Laurie Lee"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Jessie Redmon Fauset", "Sandra Cisneros", "Sarah Gilbert", "Baroness Emma Orczy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Kathryn Stockett", "Booth Tarkington", "Alain LeRoy Locke", "Martin Handford"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Wallace Thurman", "Laura Numeroff", "Wallace Stegner", "Edmond Rostand"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Harlem Renaissance: A History and an Anthology?", "answers": ["Naomi Wolf", "A. J. Quinnell", "Richard Wright", "Marjorie Garber"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Children of a Lesser God?", "answers": ["Compton Mackenzie", "Mark Medoff", "Margery Williams", "Charles Nordhoff"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Up From Slavery?", "answers": ["Kerry Patterson", "Noam Chomsky", "Booker T. Washington", "Dmitry Glukhovsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Chronicles of Clovis?", "answers": ["Saki", "Lauren Kate", "Judy Blume", "Jacob Grimm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Price?", "answers": ["Ori Brafman", "Reverend W. Awdry", "Arthur Miller", "Tholkappiar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Fly?", "answers": ["Carlos Ruiz Zaf\u00f3n", "Karen Traviss", "George Langelaan", "Douglas Coupland"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A discourse on western planting?", "answers": ["Ernest Hemingway", "George Vecsey", "V.S. Naipaul", "Richard Hakluyt"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book South Pacific?", "answers": ["Oscar Hammerstein II", "Piers Anthony", "Christina Baker Kline", "W.E.B. Du Bois"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book South Pacific?", "answers": ["Alejandro Junger", "Dr. Seuss", "Lauren Kate", "Joshua Logan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Cleopatra: A Life?", "answers": ["Stacy Schiff", "William F. Brown", "Richard Hakluyt", "Michael Falconer Anderson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book She's Come Undone?", "answers": ["Jon Lee Anderson", "Lisa Genova", "Eric Carle", "Wally Lamb"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rikki-tikki-tavi?", "answers": ["Tahir Shah", "Jerry Pinkney", "Hans Christian Andersen", "Steven Sater"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Music Man?", "answers": ["Marion Kemp", "Meredith Willson", "Karen Traviss", "Irene Mecchi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Music Man?", "answers": ["Stephen Vincent Ben\u00e9t", "Darin Strauss", "Franklin Lacey", "Nicholas Dante"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Story of My Experiments with Truth?", "answers": ["Milton William Cooper", "Edward Bond", "Kathryn Lasky", "Mahatma Gandhi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Book of Proverbs?", "answers": ["Eugene O'Neill", "William R. Forstchen", "Roger O. Hirson", "Solomon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Middlemarch: A Study of Provincial Life?", "answers": ["Raina Telgemeier", "Compton Mackenzie", "Nikos Kazantzakis", "George Eliot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Camomile Lawn?", "answers": ["Mary Wesley", "Willie Gilbert", "Stacy Schiff", "Alexandre Dumas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The China Study?", "answers": ["Erich von D\u00e4niken", "Marcel Proust", "Henry Bellamann", "T. Colin Campbell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Gargantua and Pantagruel?", "answers": ["Ana\u00efs Nin", "L. Frank Baum", "Fran\u00e7ois Rabelais", "John R. Erickson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Evangeline?", "answers": ["Henry Wadsworth Longfellow", "Peggy Parish", "Don Lynch", "Fred Graver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Rules for Writers?", "answers": ["Alexander Hamilton", "Erich Maria Remarque", "Diana Hacker", "Joseph Campbell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Dancing Barefoot: The Patti Smith Story?", "answers": ["Eric Litwin", "Dave Thompson", "Eva Ibbotson", "Gabrielle-Suzanne Barbot de Villeneuve"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book 'Tis: A Memoir?", "answers": ["Philippa Gregory", "Libba Bray", "Frank McCourt", "Anne Frank"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Fortunate Life?", "answers": ["Albert Facey", "James Ellroy", "Donna Tartt", "Ford Madox Ford"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Black Boy?", "answers": ["Richard Wright", "Robert Lindner", "H. P. Lovecraft", "Bert V. Royal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Olive Kitteridge?", "answers": ["Richard Condon", "Elizabeth Strout", "Chinua Achebe", "Lincoln Child"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Macbeth?", "answers": ["William Shakespeare", "David Oliver Relin", "Jennifer Worth", "Bennett Cerf"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Sense and Sensibility?", "answers": ["Jane Austen", "Barbara O'Connor", "Emmet Fox", "E. B. White"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book We Were Soldiers Once ... and Young: Ia Drang - the Battle That Changed the War in Vietnam?", "answers": ["Richard Condon", "Hal Moore", "Aldo Leopold", "Diane Trister. Dodge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Railway Children?", "answers": ["David Icke", "E. Nesbit", "Joseph Robinette", "Francesca Fremantle"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Savages?", "answers": ["Shirley Conran", "Ernest J. Gaines", "Andrew Lloyd Webber", "Darin Strauss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Jackie Robinson: A Biography?", "answers": ["Jonathan Harr", "Arnold Rampersad", "Lynn Sherr", "Thomas Pynchon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Storyteller?", "answers": ["Bell Hooks", "Mario Vargas Llosa", "Joseph Finder", "Claude McKay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Man's Search for Meaning?", "answers": ["Robert Graves", "Viktor Frankl", "Alexandre Dumas", "Mark Helprin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Adventures of Captain Underpants?", "answers": ["Alex Flinn", "Michael Ondaatje", "Paul Torday", "Dav Pilkey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Old School?", "answers": ["Jacqueline Davies", "Frederick Forsyth", "Tobias Wolff", "Oscar Hammerstein II"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The American Crisis?", "answers": ["Thomas Paine", "Dorothy B. Hughes", "Albert Camus", "Lane Becker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The Other Hand?", "answers": ["C. Everard Palmer", "Ellen DeGeneres", "Chris Cleave", "Mary Higgins Clark"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Lucky Jim?", "answers": ["Kingsley Amis", "T. Colin Campbell", "Shashi Tharoor", "Nicholas Evans"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book One Direction: Forever Young?", "answers": ["Caralyn Buehner", "Martin Handford", "One Direction", "Dave Barry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Drew Bledsoe: Stand and Deliver?", "answers": ["Joshua Logan", "Mark Stewart", "Tim Tharp", "Jean Webster"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Ballet Shoes?", "answers": ["Noel Streatfeild", "Kate Christensen", "Edmond Halley", "Noam Chomsky"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Five Little Monkeys Jumping on the Bed (BK + CD)?", "answers": ["Richard Carlson", "Richmal Crompton", "James Boswell", "Eileen Christelow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Little Bear?", "answers": ["James Frey", "George Langelaan", "Else Holmelund Minarik", "Benjamin Spock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Blinky Bill?", "answers": ["Daniel Wallace", "Warren Lockhart", "Dorothy Wall", "Nicholas Evans"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Bastard Out of Carolina?", "answers": ["Dominique Lapierre", "Charles A. Murray", "Jane Taylor", "Dorothy Allison"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book A Painted House?", "answers": ["Sara Pennypacker", "George Ade", "Eileen Christelow", "John Grisham"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The English Girl?", "answers": ["Sarah Dessen", "T. H. White", "Daniel Silva", "Reginald Rose"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book The 39 Steps?", "answers": ["Patrick Barlow", "Wilhelm Grimm", "Harvey Schmidt", "Henrik Ibsen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Unhappy India?", "answers": ["Michael Chabon", "Jon Krakauer", "Eileen Christelow", "Lala Lajpat Rai"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Smile?", "answers": ["Aleister Crowley", "Gabriel Garc\u00eda M\u00e1rquez", "Jane Cabrera", "Raina Telgemeier"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book South African intersections?", "answers": ["David Goldblatt", "Neal Shusterman", "Lucretius", "Mario Batali"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Babymouse?", "answers": ["Arnold Bennett", "Jennifer L. Holm", "Norton Juster", "Walt Whitman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Babymouse?", "answers": ["Rainer Maria Rilke", "Matthew Holm", "P\u0101\u1e47ini", "Austin Winsberg"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Waverley?", "answers": ["Mark Ortman", "Walter Scott", "Meredith Willson", "William Shakespeare"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Battle Cry?", "answers": ["William Golding", "Michael Wigglesworth", "Leon Uris", "J. Alison James"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Hombre?", "answers": ["Penny Dann", "Amrita Pritam", "Koushun Takami", "Elmore Leonard"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Ching?", "answers": ["Fu Xi", "Jeff Probst", "Edward S. Herman", "Nina Simone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book Maisie Dobbs?", "answers": ["Fran\u00e7oise Sagan", "Astrid Lindgren", "Michael Hollinger", "Jacqueline Winspear"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the following is the author of the book I Am a Rock?", "answers": ["Anthony Swofford", "Jean Marzollo", "Aristophanes", "Michael Camille"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}